- FBI!
FBI! Get on the floor!
Get out of the bed!
FBI! Don't move!
- Freeze!
- Where are you going?
Off the bed!
Hands up! Show me your hands! Cuff him!
Hey. Give me your hands.
Take off these cuffs. I have
the right to an attorney.
You have no right here. Do you
understand? You have no right.
You got Mother Teresa.
You actually bagged that asshole.
Got his number one and number two also.
And two judges, district police cap...
A freakin' deputy mayor.
This is gonna be a
messy day for City Hall.
Yeah.
The Albanians had to be buying
those guys off with more than tail.
Burgos got their computers, so
we're gonna find their money.
Once we start tracking it,
who knows how far this goes?
Thank you, Wilson Fisk.
He's a gift that's gonna keep on giving.
Snitch!
No! No, don't!
No! No! No!
No!
All tier two COs,
we have a 10-49 in
progress in the weight room.
All tier two COs, we have
a fight in the weight room.
Guard! Guard! Guard!
You, up against the wall,
right now! Against the wall!
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --
What did you do, Matthew?
Where did you go last night?
Hey. Don't pull that crap with me.
What happened?
Go away.
I put in way too much
work on you to quit now.
Up. Move your ass.
So you get beat by a guy who
wasn't even trying to hurt you,
and your brilliant next move is
to go out and pick another fight?
Here. Take these.
A word of advice, Mr. Daredevil...
give yourself time to heal, or
you're gonna get yourself killed.
You're probably right.
Is that what you wanted?
I have a special gift, too.
I'm impervious to bad attitude.
So you can throw your self-pitying
bullshit at me all day, Murdock,
and I'll still be standing right here.
Pissed off, maybe, but right here.
You're gonna talk to me.
Why did you become a nun?
I heard God's call.
So you feel like being a nun
is what you're meant to be?
Yes.
Very much.
What if you couldn't be one anymore?
If it were taken from you?
Your point being that if we
can't fulfill our calling,
we might be better off as worm food?
Answer the question.
I'll tell you what I wouldn't do.
I wouldn't lose faith.
I'd find some other purpose.
If you can be anything else, it
was never really your calling.
Just tell me, honestly.
If you could no longer be a nun,
wouldn't you grieve?
Of course I would.
Then please...
go away.
I understand what it's
like to feel lost, Matthew.
It happened to me, too, once.
A long time ago, when I
was still a novitiate...
I left the order for a while.
Why?
I was considering a very different life.
It was wonderful and terrifying.
I struggled to know which
life God wanted me to choose.
I prayed. I looked for signs.
In the end,
I just had to do my
best to figure it out.
Well, there you go.
That is the difference between us.
I no longer care what God wants.
Oh, right.
Almost forgot.
You've seen his true face now.
Those are some fancy moves, Matthew.
Sister Dora turned me in, didn't she?
This has to stop.
My Confirmation is in the spring.
I'm supposed to be
learning the catechism,
and Sister D can't even
defend original sin.
She is not a theologian.
You already know more about
it than she does, I'm sure.
So I can skip catechism?
No.
Come on.
Sit.
How many fights have
you been in this week?
- How many guys complained?
- None.
'Cause no one wants to admit they
got their butt kicked by a blind kid.
So you can't prove that I did anything.
I don't want to, and I don't need to.
It's not about proving
anything, Matthew.
Argumentation is a skill.
Being argumentative is a sign.
A sign like a prophecy?
A sign like you're angry, Matthew.
That's a perfectly understandable
reaction to your situation.
But it's not sustainable.
Or maybe it's a sign that Sister
Dora should stick to teaching math.
You're good...
at arguing and deflecting and
denying you're angry to other people.
But you're gonna have to
deal with your anger, Matthew.
Find a way to... harness it.
- Or it will destroy you.
- Well, if that's God's plan for me,
then I guess that's how it's
supposed to work out, isn't it?
You know, maybe you don't
understand original sin, after all.
God gave us free will, Matthew.
Adam and Eve were not
puppets, and neither are we.
We make our own choices.
That's one reason we pray,
for help making good ones.
You should try it sometime.
I do pray.
I pray all the time. I've
been praying for years.
God doesn't talk to me.
So that's what this is about?
You feel God is... neglecting you?
Matthew, the burning-bush
business doesn't happen very often,
even in the Bible.
He's usually more subtle than that.
You want to hear God, Matthew,
you have to listen more carefully.
Because he speaks in whispers.
Veggie sub.
- No meat.
- Thanks.
You don't want it.
Why not?
When you see the way Ramsey and
Arinori are kissing Hattley's ass,
you're gonna lose your appetite.
They're in her office right now.
Doing what?
Hattley gave you this raid.
But now that it worked,
well, somebody's got
to run Fisk full time.
Right? There he is.
Man of the hour.
You see the client list yet? Holy shit.
A moment, ma'am?
Sure, Ray.
Congratulations. Pristine execution.
Glad to hear it, boss. I got a big ask.
You want Fisk detail. I can't.
He's my kill. I get to eat first.
There's a goddamn buffet
in that conference room.
You can't fill up on that?
That's today. Now, what about tomorrow?
Look, we play Fisk right, there's
plenty for everyone for years.
He can give us every criminal
organization on the East Coast.
Hey, Pryor.
Find out how Burgos is
doing on the computers.
Dozens of agents had their shot at
Fisk. None of them got shit. But I did.
We got some big collars
out of this, Ray.
I'm gonna make sure D.C. knows about it.
Why do I feel like
there's a "but" coming?
Shut the door.
I put you on Fisk detail,
your file is required reading.
You'll be naked. There
will be questions.
I've got answers.
I've got a boss, too.
And he's got a hard-on for
agents in financial holes.
I'm sorry.
No. No way.
Easy, Ray.
No. You tell D.C. that none
of this could have happened
without the unexpected connection
between me and Wilson Fisk.
Because that's the truth.
And then none of the other
shit in my file will matter.
Come on, Tammy.
How am I supposed to get out from under?
Okay, he's yours. But you
need to keep him talking, Ray.
I got this.
He better last years. Because
he goes dry, we're both burned.
- Hey.
"Rostam Kazemi." Mean anything to you?
- Uh, yeah, he's a real estate developer.
- Mmm-hmm.
Actually, his daughter, Neda,
is the mean one on the
Heiresses of Manhattan.
Not that I watch that kind
of crap or anything, but...
No, of course not.
Anyway, he and his daughter were
attacked outside a
restaurant last night.
He's in a coma at Riverbank Hospital,
think it might be a kidnapping attempt.
No, you know what? I think
you should give TJ that story.
He watches her show. He'd love it.
Well, that's... That's great.
That's nice. I'm giving it to you.
No, I'm in the middle of something here.
- Excuse me?
- It's not done yet,
but I'd like to stick
with it if that's okay.
What?
Uh, yeah, here.
What am I looking at?
Uh... They're reports
of respiratory illnesses
among residents of a
particular city block.
They've spiked. They're up,
like, 45% from last year.
- And which particular block would that be?
- 44th and 11th.
- Midland Circle adjacent.
- Karen.
Come on. I know we've done
a lot of pieces on this,
but there are still questions about
that night we don't have answers for.
- You think the answers are in here?
- I don't know. Maybe.
Just give me a couple
days. It's not done yet.
What is it about Midland Circle, Karen?
I mean, it's not just a story, is it?
Look. The work you've done on this,
reporting, the
writing... it's excellent.
It's great. It's some of the best
you've ever done. I'm proud of it.
I'm even maybe a little bit jealous.
But it's done.
So that's what we do now?
We just drop stories because some
socialite who photographs well
is down at the hospital?
That's a story, too.
And I thought that you might be
able to empathize with a young woman
who's been caught up in the
middle of a family crisis.
It's one thing to work a story, Karen.
It's another thing to
let a story work you.
- End of day tomorrow.
- Okay.
How the hell did you let this happen?
Don't try to pin this shit on us.
He's your snitch.
You okay?
They said it was superficial.
I find it quite profound.
Don't start.
We're not playing games here.
It's deadly serious for me.
What? Some guy with a shank?
It's not something I fear a great deal.
But we're not dealing
with one person here.
Word is out.
Everyone knows.
Guards and inmates, it seems they
know I'm cooperating with you.
Which you are going to
continue to do, Mr. Fisk.
This was not a one-off.
You want us to help Vanessa
clear herself of criminal charges,
you need to continue to
deliver actionable information.
Do you understand?
I have suddenly become a
target within these walls here.
Do you understand?
I'm helping you to help Vanessa.
I can't do either of
those things if I'm dead.
- Please, God...
- If you can help, please just...
Help me get this job.
I've got to keep paying them,
or they'll come for Mindy.
Please just call her home.
End her suffering, I beg you.
- Her moans, I...
- Give Derek justice.
Please, God, you know
he didn't do this thing.
That lawyer's no damn good,
but you can touch the jury, God.
Help them to see the truth.
Glad to see you up here, Matthew.
I used to listen to people's prayers.
In here and out on the street.
You know, people asking for
God's help or justice or...
vengeance sometimes.
See, it's always the same.
"Please, God."
I thought that God let
me hear the prayers...
so that I could answer.
So that's what I did. That's
what I was trying to do,
was trying to help people.
But I am not what I was.
Can't do what I used to do.
Give it time.
Whatever your new
reality is, you'll adjust.
When I heard all those
prayers, all those...
suffering people, I
thought it was God's voice.
But I was wrong.
All I ever heard was people in pain.
And all he ever gave any of us was...
silence.
So now you believe your calling
to do what you do was a mistake?
I was deluding myself.
Maybe that's a good
thing to realize, Matthew.
Maybe...
it's time for you to stop.
Oh...
No, Father, uh...
My delusion was thinking God
had anything to do with it.
I'm not as capable as I was, but...
I don't get to choose who I am.
I'm Daredevil.
Not even God can stop that now.
- Excuse me. I'm looking for a dry cleaner.
- Not doing pickups right now.
But we're on 14th Street.
Address is on the side there.
Here's where it gets awkward.
I'm actually looking
for a different place.
I got a whiff of their
delivery van last night.
It didn't smell like this. Not like
chemicals. It was more... herbal.
Kinda grassy, maybe?
Yeah, sure, like that.
I know the place.
How is he?
You're a journalist, aren't you?
- I've seen your picture in the Bulletin.
- Yeah, it's Karen Page.
Not to be a bitch, but I
don't want this in the papers.
No, you're not a bitch. I get it.
Then go.
I'm sorry. I'm really, really
sorry. But you don't understand.
You think because you don't want
this in the papers, it won't be?
If I don't say anything...
They'll make up things
that sound good to them.
And that's what will get written and what
people will talk about behind your back.
For the next year. The next five
years. For the rest of your life.
You talk like you know what this is.
Maybe I do.
You grow up with paparazzi on
your ass, following you to school?
- No.
- Yeah, I did.
You know what I learned?
I learned that anything
I say, anything at all,
you people will turn it into
whatever you want to, anyway.
I'm not like that.
Yeah. Sure.
Believe it or not, I really do
know what you're going through.
Your father almost got killed?
Nope. But people said
that I killed my brother.
God, I'm sorry.
You know, when Kevin died...
everyone wanted to know what happened.
And I wasn't like you, not
paparazzi or anything, but...
it's a small town.
Stuff kinda gets around on its own.
But since no one did know
the story, they made one up.
It was all bullshit.
If you thought about it for ten seconds,
it didn't even make sense, but...
why should that matter, right?
The problem was...
...once the story got
out there, it stuck.
It grew, and it got darker and, um...
meaner.
And the things they said
about my family and about me...
it, um...
sort of tore us apart.
Piece by piece and
lie by lie. And, um...
I didn't really know how
to deal with it back then.
Now I guess it's too late.
You're right.
The truth can't be worse, can it?
I don't know.
I don't know if the truth
is any better, but...
Well, at least it's real.
Okay.
Just take your time.
We were at dinner.
We were trying to patch
things up, you know?
We were walking to the car, and...
these two men grabbed my father.
They tried to put him into
this van to kidnap him.
We only got away because
the other guy attacked him.
What other guy? You
said there's another guy?
Yeah. He came out of nowhere.
He had this black mask over his face.
You're out of your mind.
Fisk's imprisonment would
continue at a private location
under the constant
supervision of the FBI.
That's house incarceration,
usually reserved for white-collar
criminals awaiting trial.
He was shanked by
another inmate hours ago.
Good. He's a cop killer.
That wasn't proven in court.
- Whose fault was that?
- We put on a good trial.
Five counts under RICO was a giant win.
Which you're about to give away.
You're the district attorney, Mr. Tower.
Think of the long game here.
We can't prosecute everything Fisk
is giving us at the federal level.
It's gonna trickle down.
You're trying to buy the NYPD
with collars and me with convictions.
When Fisk's intel leads to the
biggest crime drop in a decade...
- The guy is a piece of shit.
- You're right.
Wilson Fisk is a piece of shit.
After every time I'm in the room
with the guy, I want a shower.
But let's talk about the Albanians
for a minute, what they have done.
Four dead NYPD officers, 12 more
riding desks with disabilities.
One hundred and seven civilian murders.
And even after five task
forces over seven years,
to the tune of $11 million, we got zero.
Those are some shitty numbers.
But here's another one.
With Fisk's intel, we beheaded
the Albanian syndicate in one day.
One single day.
No loss of life, no injuries, no mayhem.
I mean, look at the take.
We got their documents and data,
and we're gonna get their money.
Best of all, we bagged corrupt officials
whose protection they were selling.
A lot of cases they've
been interfering with
may finally get somewhere.
Look, none of us like it. It makes
me want to throw up to admit it.
But New York is safer tonight
because of Wilson Fisk.
Now I need a shower.
If we keep him talking,
Fisk will give up others.
This deal will save lives.
Tell me you're not going for this.
Uncle Foggy!
Okay, easy, easy. Left
pocket. Left pocket.
You're gonna save them
for after dinner, right?
Don't tell your mother! Or my mother.
Hey! Foggy's here!
- Hey!
- Foggy!
Hey there, Counselor.
"How are your briefs holding up?"
What's up?
Christ, that joke gets old.
Gets old?
Listen, Franklin, there's something
I need to talk to you about.
Hi.
- Try a little. I put cinnamon in it.
- Mmm! Delicious. So good.
Is he worse?
Your father's arthritis gets
a little worse every day.
He's having trouble holding onto
things, especially when he's tired.
I see him with the saws and slicers.
Ma, I'm sorry. Isn't there
anything they can do for it?
There's no cure for
getting old, Franklin.
Your father needs to be on a beach,
not slinging meat in Hell's Kitchen.
Forty years is enough already.
I know. You got yourself a life.
A good life.
But maybe it's time you came home.
I'm right here when you need me.
Your brother loves this place,
but Theo can't do it alone.
Come help.
Put those brains to
work for your family,
not every uptown shithead
that comes into your office.
They're not all shitheads, Ma.
I'm not telling you what to do.
You're a grown man. Just think
about it. That's all I'm sayin'.
Okay.
I will. I promise.
Good.
I love you, kid.
Hey! I can smell the candy
from here, Ruthie! Come here.
Where'd you get that?Â Where'd
you get that? Where'd you get that?
- Hey, Pop.
- Hey!
- Do you want a glass?
- Damn sure didn't come to chat.
The suits I understand, Foggy, but...
why you drink this
expensive crap is beyond me.
You know how proud of you I am, Foggy?
You're a big deal.
- Which is what you always wanted.
- Did I?
Ever since you could talk,
you went around telling people
that you owned the store.
They'd play along with it, too.
- Remember?
- Yeah.
I got it, Pops. I got it.
Yeah.
Sláinte.
Your lawyer almost
screwed up the whole deal.
Those terms guarantee my safety.
Beyoncé has fewer demands.
This way, convict.
You want service, you gotta get in line.
Oh... Oh.
Come on, come on. You got a
ticket, you just picking up?
- Me?
- Yeah.
Oh, no, I just ran in 'cause
your clothes smell so good.
See, I got this real
sensitive nose. I thought...
Yeah, we use a totally
organic process, latest stuff.
Oh, cool. You got a flyer?
Not in Braille.
I... I got seeing friends.
Here, have a coupon.
Thanks, I appreciate it.
- Glad I found you. Really makes my day.
- All right.
God damn it. We must have blown a fuse.
Hello! You!
Yeah, I'd like to report an assault.
I didn't see what happened, but
there are a lot of guns here.
Maybe some kind of robbery.
I don't think I ever said it,
but thank you, Theo,
for taking over the shop.
They wanted it to be you.
Yeah.
For a long time, I kinda
wanted it to be you, too.
- You never said anything.
- What was there to say?
You got a head for other things.
You were always getting the
prizes and scholarships and shit.
Anyway, you can't make a
sandwich to save your ass.
Theo, if we need to figure out...
Knock it off.
Go do what you're good at.
You're livin' the dream.
Am I?
You're shittin' me.
I had this idea of how
things were gonna go.
Matt and I talked a
lot about what we'd do.
Open our own firm.
Help people. Get rich.
I was the get rich part.
He was the help people part.
When he was around, I knew who I was.
Now...
Matt was a good guy.
Sláinte.
You can always come back here.
Yeah, great. Thanks.
Hi.
Sorry, I...
Perfect timing.
Now everyone can stop worrying
about my career choices
and start worrying about me
cheating on Marci. Much better.
- Can I to talk to you?
- What's wrong?
I think Matt's alive.
So the guy in the mask,
he wasn't in a, you know, devil suit?
No, but he was wearing a black mask.
- So it could be anybody.
- It could also not be anybody.
Hell's Kitchen is ground zero
for vigilantes these days.
Believe me, I want it to
be Matt, too. But he's...
- gone.
- No, no.
- We need to get past that.
- There is no proof of that.
- And until there is...
- You know how I know he's gone?
Because if it was Matt,
if he was really still alive,
he would've reached out to us.
You know how I know that you
don't really believe that?
You keep saying "gone"
instead of "dead."
Now, don't you want to take a minute
and just be absolutely sure that's not
your best friend out there somewhere?
I wish it was my best friend.
But it's not. He's dead.
Karen, come on. Stay.
What? You.
Your father...
he's in a coma.
He's alive.
Why did you help us?
The men who did this are in
police custody for another crime.
You head down to the 15th Precinct
right now, you can identify them.
You caught them?
You should go.
Thank God for you.
He didn't help you.
I did.
You will be under the strict
supervision of my team.
You will not remove your ankle monitor.
You will not pass beyond
the boundaries shown to you.
You will continue to have a
strictly regulated schedule.
That means eating, sleeping,
shitting, whenever I say.
Do you understand, Mr. Fisk?
I've spent much of my life alone.
And for many years, I pretended that
this was the source of my strength.
I told myself I had free will.
And in that time, I
achieved a great deal.
But I was not fulfilled.
I was longing for a
connection that I could imagine
but I could not achieve.
Searching and not finding.
Until Vanessa.
Until I discovered love.
I thought I would explode
with the sense of power
and freedom that she brought me.
That the world lay at my feet.
But then that passed when I discovered
the great lie at the heart of love.
That what I took for true
freedom was precisely the reverse.
You can build a prison
of stone and steel,
but you merely present the
prisoner with a challenge.
Any truly determined
man will find a way out.
But love...
Love is the perfect prison.
Inescapable.
So you see, Agent Nadeem...
I am always in prison,
wherever I go.
And if these things
help me protect Vanessa,
then they are nothing to me.
I will do whatever I must.
Go left! Left!
Nadeem!
Prepare to fire!
Grenade!
Stay in the car!
Don't shoot! Don't shoot! We surrender!
Convict.
Don't move.
Put him in bay 3.
Excuse me, sir.
Sorry.
- Multiple GSWs.
- First one up...
Goddamn Albanians killed
everyone except Fisk.
Somebody said he's en
route to the safe house.
It's a damn shitshow.
The FBI just let Wilson
Fisk out of prison.
- Synced and corrected by VitoSilans -
-- www.Addic7ed.com --