- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
Help me!
He's back at the church!
All units, 10-34.
Daredevil reported at Clinton Church.
Mobilize level three.
Dispatch code 11.
Emergency services en route.
Dispatch 10-54 at Clinton Church.
This is a multiple-casualty incident.
What the hell did you do?
Get over there.
You need to assume command
of the scene from the NYPD.
Daredevil is a federal fugitive.
Lock down the church.
Lock down the entire area.
We cannot let them escape.
God damn it, I asked you a
question. What have you done?
It's not done.
We are not done.
Matt?
Matt, come on, you gotta get up.
You gotta get up. Please wake up.
Wake up. Hey.
- Karen?
- Can you sit up?
- Yeah.
- Okay.
We gotta go.
- Where is he?
- I don't know. I think he got away.
No.
Jesus. Father...
He killed him. Karen, he killed him.
I know. I know. I'm
sorry, but you gotta run.
- Cops are outside. You have to go now.
- We have to run.
No. No, Matt, I'm gonna stay here,
and I'll tell the police everything.
Karen, the man in my suit,
his name is Ben Poindexter.
He's an FBI agent. He works for Fisk.
So does Agent Nadeem.
They find you, they kill you.
Has anyone got a coat or a blanket?
He killed him.
- Who?
- Daredevil.
He killed Father Lantom.
Who's in command here?
I am. Captain Strieber, 15th Precinct.
Nadeem, FBI.
Daredevil is our suspect.
I'm assuming command.
The suspect is still at large.
We have civilians down on the inside,
the church and surrounding
buildings are on lockdown.
How far out is ESU?
Excuse me?
I saw Daredevil leaving the church.
When?
Moments before you all arrived.
He headed that way.
Well, that lines up.
We have two additional DOA's
in an alley a block from here.
I'm aware of that. Daredevil
came back to the church.
I saw him myself.
We're looking for three suspects.
Daredevil and his two accomplices,
and a white female. Blonde, 5'9".
Her name is Karen Page.
Matt, I'm sorry. I'm so sorry.
Why didn't you run?
Run? How could I run?
God. Karen, if you get caught,
all of this was for nothing.
Crypt gate is locked!
FBI team is on the scene. Fall back.
It won't hold them
forever. They'll be back.
Matt, you're right.
You're right, it's my fault.
I deserved the baton, not Father Lantom.
I should never have come here.
Why did you come?
Because Fisk knows who you are.
I wanted to warn you.
That's what this is about?
Yeah. He already knew that.
Oh, God. Karen, I had him.
I just gave up my one shot
to come here to save you.
What do you mean, you had him?
I was in his penthouse.
Waiting for him.
That was it.
It was...
... the moment.
What do you think you were gonna do?
Shh!
He's back.
Poindexter is upstairs,
and he's with Nadeem.
Clear! Clear! Clear!
Stay frosty.
They're still in here somewhere.
What are you gonna do when you get him?
I did not sign up for this shit.
Yes, you did.
All clear! This room is secure.
Copy.
Search the living quarters.
Please wait here.
Eternal Father, I beg you...
welcome Paul into your holy embrace...
and do not punish him
for my stupid decisions,
for my weakness, my sin, and for
what I have brought unto us all.
Sister, we need access to every
area of the church grounds.
Now.
I'm sorry, Sister.
I know you're in mourning,
but we need your help.
I'm sorry.
Oh, Lord.
Sister, step aside.
Cut it.
- Clear!
- Shit.
What about the rectory?
There's also a door to
the roof. It's that way.
Let me show you.
Okay.
They're gone.
All right. They're gone.
I guess we'll just wait here until...
until they leave.
Why is Fisk hunting you?
Had a plan.
Went to go see him.
You went to see Fisk?
Yeah, I thought maybe
I could provoke him,
turn his emotions against him.
To what end?
Make him attack me in front of the FBI.
Jesus, Karen.
Yeah.
Don't worry, it didn't work. He...
caught me off guard, asked me
how long I'd known your secret.
I swear I tried, but he just...
He read it in my face.
You tried to outsmart Fisk?
Provoke him into making a mistake?
Fine, okay, right. You're
right. I was an idiot. Sorry.
No, you were brave.
Anyway, he didn't take the bait.
What was the bait?
I told him a secret of my own.
You remember that friend
he had that got shot?
Uh...
Wesley?
I killed him.
That's why he sent Poindexter after me.
- I was stupid and...
- and reckless,
and now Father Lantom
is dead because of it.
Because of... because of me.
Why didn't you tell me?
I don't know. You...
You always, uh, treated me like I was...
innocent.
That was nice... It was nice
that you thought of me like that.
What were you gonna do to Fisk?
Kill him.
- Your turn to judge me.
- No.
No, I'm not. I get it.
Trust me.
Just makes me, uh...
It makes me sad for you.
It has to be done, Karen.
Okay, you're gonna have
to listen to me here.
Okay, listen to me.
Okay, I never told you
why I left Vermont, right?
Why I left home.
Okay, see, there was a car crash.
And...
Um, I killed my brother, uh,
because I was... I was high
- and I was drunk and I was angry...
- Jesus, Karen.
... and I shouldn't have been
driving, and it changed everything.
No matter what I do...
there is no atoning for that.
Okay? There is no way
to come back from it.
What if... it is the way back?
For me?
I can't let Fisk go.
Killing anyone...
even Fisk...
it will change everything that you...
that you feel about yourself.
For the past two years,
ever since his unjust conviction
on racketeering charges,
our client has maintained his innocence
and fought to clear his good name.
One hour ago, the Second
Circuit Court of Appeals
overturned the
conviction of Wilson Fisk.
Having seen the proof
that they were wrong,
the Department of Justice will
not be going forward with charges.
As of tonight, we are proud to
announce that justice has prevailed
and Wilson Fisk is
once again a free man.
I know that most of you find
this difficult to accept.
That's only because
you've been manipulated...
poisoned into believing the
news media's fake story...
that I am evil,
that I am a criminal.
Quite the opposite is true.
Because I challenge the system...
because I've told the truth and tried
to make this city a better place,
the people in power
decided to tear me down...
to tear me down with false allegations.
They sent someone to frame me.
Daredevil.
The killer who's now
showing his true colors,
who has tried to murder people in
newspaper offices and churches...
attacking our sacred institutions.
Believe me.
Daredevil is our true public enemy.
Agent Nadeem?
Detective Mahoney.
I'm taking over the murder
investigation on our side.
Great. We'll share what
we've got ASAP. I promise.
Thanks. But between you and me,
there's something off about all of this.
What's that?
Well, a number of
witnesses claim Daredevil
was trying to kill Karen Page.
And your people are making
her out to be his accomplice.
There's more to this story
than you're aware of, Detective.
Thanks for bringing it to my
attention, but this is our crime scene.
We'll let you know if we need anything.
Dex, this is getting out of control.
Someone needs to call Kingpin.
Dex?
Hello?
Yeah?
What?
I'm saying we should
get in front of this.
Someone needs to call Kingpin.
And say what?
That we failed?
"We"?
There something that you
want to say to me, Arinori?
Hey, this isn't helping.
Dex, they're in the wind.
And we're not gonna find 'em tonight.
I'm gonna release the ESU and
open the scene to forensics.
No. No way.
You get the NYPD to go to
every house in the neighborhood.
Door to door.
We do not stop until we find them.
Dex, they're gone.
Fine, call it off.
And you call Kingpin
and tell him you're the reason
that Karen Page is still breathing,
that you gave up.
Okay. A few more hours.
Sister, do you mind if I ask
you a couple of questions?
Do you know the suspects?
As far as I'm aware, the only
one you've identified by name
is Karen Page.
And, yes, she and I are acquainted.
Do you know where she might have gone?
I thought you believed the suspects
were still hiding in the church.
We do. I do. I meant where
on the church grounds.
May I ask you a personal
question, Agent Nadeem?
Okay.
Do you consider yourself a moral person?
I like to think so.
I try to be.
My good friend died here tonight,
protecting Karen Page from evil.
If you're the kind of
man you claim to be,
do you really want to help it find her?
Thank you.
What? What is it?
Thank God.
It's not safe for you to come out yet.
Yeah, we know. I can hear 'em.
I can come back with food,
but in the meantime, you
should get cleaned up.
We have fresh clothes.
Donations for the poor.
Uh, thank you.
Uh, Sister...
for what it's worth, I'm so
sorry. I shouldn't have come here.
This is not your fault.
Father Lantom didn't deserve this.
Few of us get what we deserve.
These should fit you.
I'll come back as soon as
I can. You'll be safe here.
No, we won't.
They brought in search dogs.
Search over here.
Track. Track.
Not me, fellas. The bad guys.
All right.
Wait.
Tell them what you saw.
- The man in black is next door.
- What?
I saw him go in, slam
the door. It was him...
- Where?
- The orphanage.
Please tell me we got
all the kids out of there.
I don't know.
Come on, let's move.
Yeah.
They're taking the dogs next door.
Buys us some time.
Jesus, Matt.
Couldn't put it on in front of her?
You know, something just kinda hit me.
Watching you... wall
yourself off from her.
You know?
Uh, yeah. She told me.
Said she felt ashamed
about what she did.
And that... everyone you
ever cared about left you.
- Can we not do this now?
- Is that why you
- insist on doing everything alone?
- I don't insist...
- Pushing Foggy and me away.
- I'm not.
I told you, I'm tryin' to protect you...
I think you're trying
to protect yourself.
You wanna talk about this right now?
There are people tryin' to
kill us, and you wanna...
Just shut up for a second, Matt, okay?
Look, I was never gonna
leave you up there,
and I'm not leaving you now.
Neither will Foggy.
Despite the fact that you've
been a complete asshole to him,
he'd still follow you over a cliff.
Yeah.
Okay. So, what, you agree?
That could actually work.
I don't get it. What could work?
Foggy.
Mr. Fisk's people said you had to
call a press conference and read it.
Jesus.
You're calling him "Mr. Fisk" now?
"I was acting under duress
when I falsely and publicly accused
Wilson Fisk of criminal activities.
Daredevil threatened
the lives of my family,
but in light of recent events, I
now see that I did the wrong thing,
that I must stand up for what's right."
- I can't say this.
- You have to.
It's complete bullshit.
You know what's bullshit, Foggy?
The fact that me and Mom and Dad
are caught up in this
in the first place.
The only reason these people
tricked us into that bank loan...
You knew it was fraud
when you signed it.
Okay, yeah. But it only happened
because Fisk wanted to get to you.
Everything that's happened, the
suppliers cuttin' us off, the loan,
all that shit happened because you
wanted to be the big-time lawyer
instead of hangin' around
here with us losers.
Come on. That's not fair.
No, it's not. None of it is.
We didn't have any say in this, Foggy.
You went and pissed off the
biggest mob boss in the city,
but we're the ones paying for it.
Or we will if you don't do what he says.
If I read that statement to
the press, Fisk wins, Theo.
He's already won, Fogg.
Now, do the right thing.
The right thing for your family.
Hello?
Matt?
The deputy AG has ruled that you
continue to be a valuable DOJ asset
who deserves ongoing protection.
Because they're terrified of
the PR hit if you get killed.
Thank you, Agent Hattley.
That will be all.
Well, where is Vanessa?
In the air. Her plane
took off an hour ago.
Then there's only one
thing left for me to do,
which, apparently, I have to do myself.
We doubled the offer, threw in
incentives, but the owner wouldn't sell.
Not at any price.
Then I'll visit her in person.
I'll make a more compelling offer.
All the way up to the rectory, right?
That's what they said.
Sorry, sir, this is an active...
Hey, are you Foggy Nelson?
Guilty as charged, Officer...
- "Minelli."
- It's an honor to meet you.
I signed our union's endorsement letter.
I hope you kick Blake Tower's ass.
With people like you backing
me up, how could I not?
Hey, listen, I'm here to
talk to Detective Mahoney.
You think you could...
Move!
Nelson?
What the hell are you doing?
Agent Nadeem, pleasure to see you again.
I asked you a question.
What are you doing here?
You know, just observing the hard
work of our men and women in blue.
That's some weak bullshitting.
You wanna try that again?
Okay. You caught me.
Truth is, I'm killing time.
Killing time for what?
Why do you keep looking at her?
Because I need to kill
a few more seconds.
Okay, I'm good.
Agent Nadeem, I'm here for my client.
- Your...
- Client.
Don't shoot! She's unarmed.
This is why I'm here.
To surrender my client.
Good.
To the NYPD.
Karen Page, you are under arrest.
Cuff her.
What the hell are you doing?
She's ours, Detective.
Like hell.
She's a federal suspect.
She's a suspected accomplice to murder.
That's state law.
And she's here to surrender to the NYPD.
- Shut up.
- I'm saying, as the only attorney here,
- I could help clear...
- Put a sock in it, Nelson.
These feds know the
law. She's our suspect.
They can file a writ and
maybe talk to her later.
I will not let you take her.
You and what army?
Hey, we're on the same team here.
Detective, a word?
What part of "our crime
scene" do you not understand?
Ben, we're all cut up
about what happened here.
A word. Please.
You need to stand your people down.
Listen to me very carefully.
If we take Karen Page into custody,
she'll be dead before she reaches HQ.
No, don't react.
Just get her the hell
away from us. We clear?
Crystal.
Detective Mahoney will
take custody of the suspect.
Bullshit!
We'll have her back in an
hour. Hattley will pull strings.
- No.
- You can't kill her here anyway.
You messed up, Ray.
You really... really messed up.
Mrs. Falb. My name is...
I know who you are.
Take off your shoes.
It's beautiful.
It certainly is.
It's peaceful and so...
It's been through quite
a bit over the years.
But it's home now.
I hope you're not here to
offer me more money for it.
- Would it change your mind?
- It would not.
I understand you became
aware of the painting
when it was taken away
from me by the government.
Yes.
Ironic, I suppose.
It was a government that took
it from my family in 1943.
So, then, you are particularly
suited to understanding my situation.
The painting was given to
me by the woman that I love.
When I'm with it, I am with her.
She must be an amazing woman.
Yes.
Yeah, she's given me much in
the short time I've had with her.
She brought focus to my
life. Love, if you will.
This painting is bound up in that love.
It's part of me. It's part of us.
My years on this
earth... have taught me...
there is nothing more
important than love.
I didn't have much of it.
And when it was offered to me,
I was too afraid to accept it.
I understand.
Well, then, you will
understand me when I say this:
that painting was not hers to give.
She was unaware of the provenance.
She gave it with love.
It was not taken with love.
I was a toddler when the
wolves came to our door.
The gestapo demanded everything we had.
Including that painting.
My father fought them...
... and they shot him in front of us.
Do you know what it's like to see
your father take his last breath
on the floor in front of you?
As they marched my family
across Poland to the ghetto...
my mother went hungry to feed us.
But of the seven members of my family,
we were the only ones who survived.
I am deeply sorry for
everything you've suffered.
This painting is my connection
to the people I love.
I know who you are, Mr. Fisk.
You are a wolf, too.
Men like you took away my
family, took my ability to love...
and almost took my life.
You will take nothing more.
You have been through so very much.
Vanessa would want you
to keep the painting.
Is that supposed to matter to me?
No.
But it matters to me.
What kind of psycho kills a priest?
This makes me sick.
Come on out of there.
The FBI is going to freak when
they find out you let us go.
Yeah, well, they can
kiss my police-blue ass.
Seriously, are you gonna be okay?
I had to see it with my own eyes.
Fisk really has turned the goddamn feds.
- Some of them.
- Can't believe no one saw it coming.
Well, actually, some of us did.
Yeah, that's true.
Nice takedown on Blake
Tower, by the way.
I posted the video on my profile page.
Brett, I'm flattered.
Even if he did crush
your ass at the end.
He didn't crush my ass.
You ran out of there
like a scared little...
- Nah, uh... it's my fault.
- Yeah, whatever.
You guys aren't alone
in this, you understand?
Fisk put a lot of my brothers
and sisters in the ground,
and none of us have forgotten that.
If you can find a way to
bring down that son of a bitch,
every cop in the city
is gonna have your back.
Thanks, Brett.
Take care of yourself.
Okay, so how do we play this?
Simple. We convince Matt to
take his head out of his ass.
So it looks like you
needed my help after all.
Yeah.
Yeah, I did, Foggy. You're right.
Do you have any idea how much
life has sucked for Karen and me
while you were off doin' your own thing?
No, but I'm sorry, Foggy.
Maybe I was wrong
to... to push you away.
Okay, it's insanely
hard to fight with you
if you keep agreeing with me.
Good, 'cause I don't
wanna fight with you.
Look, the way I've treated you,
the way I've treated you both...
You've deserved better.
Yes, we did.
Yes, you did.
Okay, so where do we go from here?
I don't want to leave you,
but I can't ask you to be
accomplices to what I have to do now.
What does that mean?
Um...
It means that, uh,
Matt's gonna kill Fisk.
That building falling on you
really did mess up your head.
We put him in prison,
Foggy. Look what happened.
It's not gonna be the same this time.
They're gonna throw him
in some supermax hole...
- Come on.
- ... where he can't compromise anybody.
- I know you're not that naive.
- It's called having faith in the system.
Something you used to have.
It's called facing the reality
that some people are
so rich and powerful,
the system simply can't handle them,
that they actually are above the law.
That's the bullshit that people
like Fisk want you to believe.
Nobody's above the law.
The only thing powerful enough
to take down scumbags
like him is the law.
He's twisted it into something
that actually protects him.
Federal law, maybe,
but we can build a state case
that even Blake Tower can't deny,
force him to take it to the grand jury.
Fisk has been five steps
ahead of us at every turn.
You really think he's
gonna allow that to happen?
Hey, you're right. You're
right. Maybe just hear him out.
Fine. I'm telling you,
it's not gonna work.
You want to give the law
another try, sure, I'm all ears.
Simple.
Step one, we work together.
Step two, we come up with
a plan. And step three,
we execute that plan.
That's genius. Come up
with that by yourself?
So I'm still working out the details.
What about this?
What about we find
ourselves another witness?
Someone who will flip on Fisk.
But unlike Jasper Evans,
we keep 'em alive this time.
Someone who knows the details
of Fisk's criminal operation...
who has nothing to lose.
Okay?
No.
No, we find someone who
has everything to lose.
Copy that.
Karen Page has been found.
NYPD took her into custody.
The police? How?
It was Agent Nadeem's call.
Your jacket.
- Sir?
- Give me your jacket.
Pull over.
Get rid of the body.
Yes, sir.
Seema! Are you here?
What's the matter?
Dad?
It's okay. It's okay, Sami.
I saw the broken vase,
and I got worried.
Dad, sorry. I knocked it over.
Mom said she was gonna
clean it up later.
Are you mad?
No. No, of course not.
- We have to pack. Now.
- What's the...
Just for a few days, okay?
I have to work. I want
you to go away, okay?
Someplace fun. Like Disney World. Yeah?
But it has to be right this minute.
It's okay, Sami. It'll... It'll be fine.
- We can pack together. Come on.
- Go. Go, go, go, go.
- What's going on?
- I'll explain everything when you're safe.
- You're scaring me.
- Be scared later. Now, just hurry.
Stop.
This way.
Get back.
The sliders.
Take Sami into the bathroom
and lie down in the tub.
Now!
Obviously, I'm here to help you.
I sold you out to Fisk.
I know you didn't want to.
But I did.
So maybe you're here because you
wanna be the one that kills me
before Fisk gets around to it.
If we're gonna get your
family someplace safe,
you're gonna have to trust me.
I can't trust anybody.
Well, I trust you.
You saved Karen Page's life tonight.
So I owe you one.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -