- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -
There is no corpse.
There's no corpse.
I heard you.
Remind Felix Manning that I
do not tolerate loose ends.
Yes, Mr. Fisk.
But the body was probably
just swept away in the current.
Even if Murdock somehow
escaped from the cab,
how does a blind man swim to shore?
This look like a blind man to you?
We investigated him thoroughly.
His associates.
Medical and school
records all check out.
All confirm that Matt Murdock
lost his sight at age nine.
Yes.
Nevertheless...
a man capable of that
could have survived.
And he threatened to come
between Vanessa and I.
It's time for the
government to honor our deal.
Thanks to my client,
the Albanian Syndicate has
been completely wiped out.
Their counterfeiting ring,
their Dark Web child pornography.
And the Jalisco connection
Mr. Fisk divulged last week
gave the DEA an early
and very white Christmas.
And in exchange for
his ongoing cooperation,
the DOJ will not be filing
charges against Vanessa Marianna.
Mr. Fisk is also entitled to the
return of certain personal belongings,
supervised movement within the hotel.
He'll get everything
he was offered. In time.
That time is now, Special Agent Nadeem.
Unless you'd like my
client to stop talking.
FBI has sacrificed a great deal for me.
And I will continue to cooperate
and trust you'll honor your word.
There's a criminal I've employed.
A facilitator.
On my behalf, he's
laundered and hid money,
bribed law enforcement
and court officials,
orchestrated perjured
testimony, manufactured evidence.
Who is he?
A lawyer. Matthew Murdock.
Alpha Team on approach.
FBI. Get back in your
apartment and close the door.
Stack up.
Breach.
FBI!
Clear!
Murdock's been home.
Recently.
It was so nice to see you again.
Take care.
Felix Manning?
You haven't returned my calls.
Karen Page, from the Bulletin.
Before I go to print,
I'm obligated to offer
you a chance to comment
on your involvement in
laundering money for Wilson Fisk.
Look, if you talk to me off the
record, help me connect some dots,
I promise I will keep
your name out of it.
But that is only if you talk to me.
You're a fixer, Mr. Manning.
You're a freelancer. Other
clients, a lot to lose.
Once this story breaks, Fisk
is gonna hang you out to dry.
If I were you, I would
start looking out for myself.
Karen Page.
Daughter of Paxton and Penelope.
239 Kings Road, Fagan Corners, Vermont.
You had the back room. My guess, Dad
wanted his little girl to be safe.
Sadly, he should've been more
worried about his little boy.
Drug addicts really do
destroy families, don't they?
Off the record,
you're incorrect.
About what I do for a living.
I don't fix problems.
I make them disappear.
Karen Page?
- Who are you?
- Don't move.
Uh... I have a weapon in my purse.
And a concealed carry permit.
Keep your hands exactly where they
are and follow my instructions.
Now turn around.
Okay. Okay.
What do you want from me?
What happened?
Why'd you bring me here?
I asked him to.
Is Matt okay?
You wanna tell me what's going on?
Ms. Page, I get that you
ask questions for a living,
but, for now, I'll be the one asking.
When's the last time you
heard from Matt Murdock?
Um...
- Months.
- You haven't seen or spoken to him in months?
Uh, no.
He give you any indication
when he'd be back?
Uh, no.
Or whether he'd be back at all?
No.
Then why have you been paying his bills?
He's a friend. Someone had
to do it while he was away.
So your friend, a blind man who
you haven't spoken to in months,
just ups and disappears, and you
don't file a missing persons report?
I figured he'd come
back when he was ready.
Can you think of any reason why
Matt Murdock would go on the run?
No.
You were a secretary
for Nelson and Murdock.
Mmm-mmm. Office manager.
And when did the firm first
start working for Wilson Fisk?
Um...
We never worked for Wilson Fisk.
Is that your signature?
Do you remember depositing
this retainer check for
a company called CGI?
Yes, I do. Um...
Look, Matt and Foggy took on
one case for them. That's all.
According to my source,
CGI was a front for Fisk.
Well, we didn't know that at the time.
But you do now.
So you see how your last answer
wasn't technically accurate?
Okay, we never knowingly
worked for Fisk.
They hired us through someone else.
Who?
Some executive.
Hang on.
Was it this guy?
James Wesley. You remember him?
Uh, yeah. I think that was him. Why?
Just trying to put the pieces together.
Okay. Uh... Well, here are some
other pieces for you to put together.
Um...
Felix Manning. Red Lion
National Bank. Vancorp.
Any of that ring any bells?
I don't follow.
Well, instead of letting
Fisk use you and the FBI
to retaliate against innocent
lawyers who put him in prison,
why don't you ask him if he
hired a fixer named Felix Manning
to launder money through Red Lion?
Ask him if he's the true owner
of a shell company called Vancorp.
Why would I do that?
Because it just bought
the Presidential Hotel.
Where are you getting this from?
I ask questions for a living. I
just ask better ones than you do.
Like, has your so-called prisoner
just bought the prison
you're keeping him in?
Has he bought?
So this is what? Just a theory?
You have any proof?
Fisk is using you, Agent
Nadeem. That's what he does.
Is that a no?
Am I under arrest?
Not at this time.
Then I'm done answering
the wrong questions.
Is this everything?
Everything Felix's investigators
were able to dig up on short notice.
Uh...
This will take some time.
I brought an audiobook.
Dex, ready to go?
Game starts in 20. Traffic's
a nightmare. We gotta hustle.
What's the deal? You don't
even got your uniform on.
You all right, buddy?
Trouble in paradise?
Does the headmaster know you're
drilling a hole in his pile of bricks?
He doesn't like it.
He gives you a hard
time, you send him my way.
It's damn fine practice.
Hey, I got you a little something.
I was gonna wait until after the game...
100% leather.
That's steerhide in the
pocket and cowhide in the palm,
so it's nice and soft.
Try it on.
An all-star pitcher
deserves some all-star gear.
Come on, let's go break it in.
Wait.
Real quick, can I show
you my new wind-up?
All right, showboat.
Let's see it.
You're in the zone, Dex.
Keep throwing those heaters.
Strike!
Strike! Strike!
All right, kiddo. Pack it in.
Let's give that arm of yours a rest.
You're pulling me?
- I'm gonna let Kanon finish it out.
- But... but no one's gotten a hit off me.
I know. You're killin'
it out here. No question.
But I gotta give other
kids some field time.
You can't do this. It's not
fair! You gotta let me keep going.
Keep it together, okay?
Take a few deep breaths.
Big gulps of air.
I need...
I need to keep going.
If I pitch a perfect
game, then they might...
Dex...
you could pitch a billion perfect games.
It won't bring your parents back.
Okay.
Hit the pine.
Grab a Popsicle.
We'll talk later.
Well, this has been
nice so far, hasn't it?
Talking like this.
Now that we've gotten to
know each other a little bit,
I wonder if we could
talk about Coach Bradley?
What happened at the field?
How did it make you feel?
Sad?
Maybe a little scared?
I wasn't sad.
Why not, do you think?
He was a jerk.
How so?
How was Coach Bradley a jerk?
He never let me do what I wanted.
Didn't know shit about pitching.
He was your coach for a long time.
Was he always such a jerk to you?
What about last year
when he named you MVP?
Was he a jerk then?
No. He used to be awesome.
Dex, tell me...
And be honest.
We like honesty around here.
When you hit Coach Bradley...
was that an accident?
Whatever you say stays
between us. That's the law.
No.
It wasn't an accident.
Am I in trouble?
No.
It wasn't your fault.
But I just told you,
I did it on purpose.
That doesn't mean it was your fault.
It's confusing, isn't it?
Here, let me put it like this.
This is you, right?
Yeah.
This is fantastic.
But you see how alone you are?
It's just you, surrounded
by all this emptiness.
It's been that way for most
of your life, hasn't it?
Yeah.
I mean, most kids,
they have moms or dads
to teach them right from wrong,
to show them how to behave.
My parents mostly got mad at me.
Yes.
Then they died.
And there were things
that you never learned.
You see?
Not your fault.
Good news is, you've got me now.
Now, we've got a lot of work to do,
but I think that it is going to be fun.
We are going to establish some routines,
learn to stay calm.
And first things first,
we're gonna practice empathy.
What's that?
That means being kind to
someone when they're in pain.
So let's say, for example,
that my cat got sick this
morning and I was upset.
What would you say to me?
How about something like,
"I'm sorry. That sounds hard."
I'm sorry. That sounds really hard.
Look at you!
You even put a "really" in there.
I like a fast learner.
I think we are gonna make
a terrific team, you and me.
Oh.
Nothing marks an occasion
like a little bubbly, huh?
It's a... a Cava, actually.
Spanish champagne.
It was a little farewell gift from
the chiropractor down the hall.
Tomorrow is my last day in the building.
Here. Go on.
I'm not 21.
Good for you.
It's been quite a challenging day.
Quite a few goodbyes.
Lots of...
longtime clients.
That... That's hard.
That's really hard.
And then there's this,
our last session together,
which I've been dreading
since my prognosis.
Then don't leave.
We can keep meeting. I
can keep getting better.
Dex...
You can't leave.
You are gonna be fine, Dex.
We prepared for this.
You are gonna get a job
with a nice, rigid structure.
You're gonna stick to your meds.
And if you get off track,
you can... listen to these.
This is every session we've had.
Cycle through them again.
When we remind ourselves
of how far we've come,
we're less inclined to slip back.
And one last thing.
This is a, uh... a colleague of mine.
He's a fine therapist, with a lot
of expertise in your particular...
I don't want another therapist!
Are you trying to scare me?
No.
Not scare you.
Then what is your intention?
And be honest.
I want...
I want to kill you.
Say more.
Why do you want to kill me?
To put me out of my misery?
To punish you.
I'm not quite sure what I've done wrong.
I want to kill you for dying.
For leaving me.
Death always wins, Dex.
Eventually.
But when it comes quietly and
naturally, it can be a beautiful event.
Which is why we never
hasten it with violence.
I can't do this alone.
You remember what I did?
Last time I was alone?
Then find someone.
I don't want another therapist!
Any good person with
a decent heart will do.
Someone to look up to.
Your internal compass isn't broken, Dex.
It just works better when you
have the North Star to guide you.
Suicide Prevention, this is Dex.
Who am I speaking with?
Hi, Craig. How can I help you today?
I'm sorry. That's hard.
That's really hard.
Why don't you tell me a little
bit more about how you're feeling?
That's a lot to deal
with. I'm glad you called.
You're doing amazing.
Tell me, Craig,
are you thinking about taking
your own life right now?
Okay.
Do you have a plan?
What kind of gun do you have, Craig?
I'm familiar with the M11.
Did a couple years in the army.
Got real cozy with the M11.
It's reliable.
Let me ask you a question, Craig.
If this asshole stepdad of yours
is giving you so much grief,
why take your own life?
Why not...
Take a deep breath, Craig.
We're gonna work through this together.
I'm not going anywhere.
If I may ask, Mr. Fisk,
without getting into specifics,
what's this all about?
Right now, I am New York's scapegoat.
Downstairs, there are
protesters chanting prayers
to drive me out into the wilderness.
The attention that it brings
is an impediment for my plan.
Fortunately, the public
is easily distracted.
Which makes the solution
for my problem quite simple.
The city needs a new villain.
And I think I might've found him.
Can I start you off
with something to drink?
Looks like you need a little more time.
I'll grab you a water.
This is gonna sound random,
but did you used to work at
the Brooklyn Suicide Hotline?
Yeah. Yeah, I did.
That... was a tough job.
It was.
You probably don't
remember me. I'm Julie.
Dex.
Yeah, of course I remember you.
Small world, huh?
I haven't seen you in here before.
It's... it's my first day, actually.
I got offered double the
pay to leave my last job
if I could start here immediately.
Not that I'm complaining.
What about you? Are you
staying at the hotel?
No. I live here.
In New York, not in the hotel.
The FBI has an office upstairs.
We're guarding Wilson Fisk.
A G-man.
Excuse me, miss! Hello?
I need to go help that table so
they don't fire me on my first day.
What time do you get off?
In about an hour.
Do you wanna hang out after?
Catch up?
Uh...
Yeah.
That... That'd be great.
Hmm.
I got your coppa, your prosciutto,
your mocetta, your sweet soppressata.
All you can eat. Free!
For anybody who promises
to vote for Foggy Nelson,
my less handsome brother.
You can't do that, Theo.
It violates election law. It's
an illegal inducement to vote.
I don't see Mrs.
Wobschall calling the cops.
May I borrow a pen?
Is that an actual ballot, Mrs. Callahan?
I just voted for you.
Absentee.
When Wilson Fisk set off those
explosives in Hell's Kitchen,
I lost my husband.
Everything that matters, gone.
Except my vote.
I'm counting on you, Foggy.
You get that son of a bitch.
I will. I promise.
Thank you, everyone.
And I'll be here till close
to answer any questions.
Yeah, I got a few.
Like, what's the secret ingredient
in your world-famous Nelson's sub?
A soft robiola.
Perfect. Uh, team at
work is gonna love that.
Uh...
Give me six.
Uh, Theo can help you at the
counter. Is there anything else?
Yeah.
When's the last time
you saw Matt Murdock?
Who are you?
Crashing my campaign event,
trying to intimidate me,
dropping the names of my friends...
I'm not backing off my criticism
of the feds' love affair with Fisk!
You seem like a decent guy, Mr. Nelson.
You care about people.
About doing the right thing.
I'm guessing that's why
you ditched Matt Murdock
as your law partner in the first place.
Am I correct?
You really think I'm gonna
answer a question that leading?
To be clear: did you
dissolve your partnership
because Mr. Murdock took
on Wilson Fisk as a client?
If you're referring to a single case
where we represented a client
who allegedly worked for Fisk
even though we didn't
know that at the time...
the answer's no.
It had nothing to do with it.
Nelson and Murdock
represented a lot of clients,
for whom all work was
completely ethical and legal
and protected by
attorney-client privilege.
When's the last time
you saw Matt Murdock?
Two nights ago.
Where?
A bar in Hell's Kitchen.
And what did you discuss?
That we hadn't seen
each other in a while.
- Did he tell you where he was going?
- No.
- Where you could find him?
Did he tell you anything?
That he was sorry.
About what?
That our friendship
isn't what it used to be.
So you didn't knowingly
give him your bar ID?
What?
Of course not.
Why would I?
So he could enter a prison,
falsely using your identity,
and make contact with an Albanian gang
linked to the murder
of nine federal agents.
I...
I didn't give him my ID.
Nor was I aware of anything
that he was planning.
But with all due respect,
I think you have Matt Murdock all wrong.
Yeah, well, uh...
I don't think I do.
I think Matt Murdock
is hiding a double life.
Lawyer by day and criminal by night.
And you and Ms. Page
both know all about it.
It makes you uncomfortable.
And complicit.
And that's why you're no
longer law partners or friends.
Because once he's finally caught,
you know you're on the hook
as an accessory to his crimes.
Or, if you're lucky,
simply aiding and abetting.
Remind me, Special Agent Nadeem,
what's Matt being charged with?
Nothing so far.
Great.
Then the only thing I'm aiding
and abetting is your exit.
Don't forget to vote.
Every day?
FDR Drive's my favorite route, too.
There's nothing in the world like
a winter run on the East River.
Between your workout
habits and new gig, it's...
it's almost like you're stalking me.
Damn. The secret's out.
So...
why aren't you in social work anymore?
Uh... Tried to pursue
my dream as a dancer.
It actually was going pretty
well until I tore my ACL, again.
I'm sorry. That must've
been really hard.
But you were brave to go
for it in the first place.
I, um...
I didn't have a backup plan.
My parents made the mistake of telling
me I could be anything I wanted.
Must've been nice to hear,
even if it didn't work out.
My parents were never
really that involved.
Sounds like you didn't
need the message anyhow.
You did great all on your own.
So, what's it like
working for Wilson Fisk?
I don't work for him. I work
for the federal government.
Must be scary to be up close and
personal with someone so dangerous.
It is what it is.
Do you think a killer like
that deserves a second chance?
You worked at the
hotline for three years.
I think you of all people would believe
everyone deserves a second chance.
How did you know I worked
there for three years?
You were only there for one.
You mentioned it earlier.
You quit to do ballet.
Did I also mention ballet earlier?
Specifically?
I guess I... I just assumed.
Anyway, um...
It's late. I should get home.
You're ditching me?
No, not at all. I...
I just have to go feed my dog.
You don't have a dog.
How do you know that?
Julie, you're misreading this.
Let me pay for dinner.
We'll go for a walk in
the park. I'll explain.
Dinner's on me.
Julie.
You're very special to me.
Let go of me, Dex.
- Please.
- I said let go!
Just being at Matt's apartment,
and his bloody clothes...
And I just... It threw me.
Nadeem's smart. I probably
gave him everything he needs
to figure it out.
Wait. You told the FBI
that Matt is Daredevil?
No, no. Of course not.
They know he's hiding something.
It's not what they
think, but this is bad.
This is really bad. Infinitely bad.
- We could all go to jail.
- Foggy...
I should've never let
Matt tell you his secret.
This is my fault.
I'm not gonna let you pay
for our shitty mistakes.
If it comes to it, I'll plead
in exchange for your immunity.
Foggy...
You always see the good in people.
But you put us on such high pedestals,
you can't see who we really are.
I didn't tell the FBI Matt is
Daredevil. I did something worse.
Karen, breathe.
I'm in trouble.
Tell me what happened.
I'm gonna need attorney-client
privilege before I can.
Okay, um, give me five bucks.
Good enough. I'm officially your lawyer.
Do you remember the... the Healy trial?
And there was that...
that guy from... from CGI
who offered us a stupid amount
of money to take his case?
Yeah, how could I forget that creep?
His name's James Wesley.
He worked for Fisk.
He disappeared shortly after that,
and they think Matt had
something to do with it.
That's crazy. Matt had
nothing to do with that.
I know. But if they keep investigating,
they're gonna find out that I did.
What?
I killed him.
Shit. Shit.
It's good to see you,
Dex. How was your week?
I'm scared, Dr. Mercer.
Scared? What's making you scared?
Alpha Team on approach.
FBI. Get back in your
apartment and close the door.
Stack up.
Breach.
FBI!
Clear!
Murdock's been home.
Recently.
Command post, we're
clear. Suspect's not here.
NYPD has been advised. Citywide BOLO.
Suspect Matthew Murdock to be
considered armed and dangerous.
- Synced and corrected by chamallow -
- www.addic7ed.com -