Where is it?
I don't know.
Where is the Black Sky?
You have three limbs left.
And other appendages no man wants to lose.
Where is the Black Sky?
It's gone.
They...
They put it on a ship.
Where's the ship headed?
New York City.
Swear to it.
Upon my family.
They're better off without you.
Devil, my shapely Irish ass.
Guy's a coward.
Would and I wouldn't give for the
chance to rip that corny mask off and...
And what?
Punch him... in the face...
with my... fisticuffs.
I don't know, he seems,
uh... pretty fisticuffy.
Please tell me I don't detect a hint
of admiration for that terrorist.
This is just all speculation. Nobody
knows if he's a terrorist or what.
You're absolutely right.
Terrorists have causes.
They claim responsibility.
Al-Qaeda wanted the world to know
exactly what kind of assholes they were.
This guy? Not a peep.
All terror without the "-ist."
You know what they call that? Nut job.
Hmm, maybe.
How's your side?
Downgraded to agony.
All right, what do you think, Matt?
I think Foggy'll be pitching
for the Mets by mid-season.
I'm being serious.
So am I. Have
you seen their bullpen?
Come on, you telling me this
dickhead blowing up our backyard
doesn't piss you off?
What happened to Hell's Kitchen,
to you and to Elena, and to
all the people that were hurt...
yeah, it pisses me off.
But this man, whoever he
is, whatever his motive,
he shouldn't be tried and
convicted in the press.
We're lawyers, we know that's
not how it's supposed to work.
So, uh, hypothetically,
if this guy got caught...
needed counsel, Nelson and
Murdock would offer to defend him?
Hell no.
It would be his right.
What about my right to
punch him in the melon?
They pulled a piece of
glass out of my side.
Elena needed 12 stitches.
And you want to Perry
Mason the guy responsible?
I wanna make sure the right
person pays for what happened.
The whole thing's moot.
After shooting those cops, police
are probably looking to settle things
the old-fashioned way
if they catch up to him.
Yeah, it's more than likely.
Just a thought, but we may wanna go
a bit peppier at the end of the day.
Leave on a note slightly
higher than deeply depressing.
She's right. You're
bringing us down, Murdock.
Me?
High note! Softball!
When are we getting a
company team together?
We have three employees.
At least two of them aren't blind.
Naysayers, each and every one of you.
Karen, come on.
Batting practice, you
and me, Chelsea Piers.
- What do you say?
- Um, I...
Or not. Totally cool.
No, no, I would, I
would. It's just that I, um...
I have this, uh, thing.
Go, do that thing.
Not a problem.
Okay, so, um... see you tomorrow.
We'll be here, ready
to high note and stuff.
Good.
Smooth.
Admittedly, I'm a work in progress.
Did you know she has mace on her keychain?
Is that a bad thing?
You ever worry about her?
Worry, like, something
she's not telling us?
Everyone has secrets, Foggy.
I don't. I'd like some.
Your kind... like with
Hottie McBurner-Phone.
I mean, I assume she's hot. Is she hot?
Oh...
How would I know?
This again.
You always know.
I mean, you guys getting serious?
Should I dust off the
tux I'll need to rent?
No, uh... it didn't work out.
Oh.
I'm... I'm sorry, man.
Yeah, me too.
Hey, look, I'm gonna order in tonight,
get a jump on this tenement case.
You want me to stay?
No, I'll be all right. Thanks, buddy.
See you in the morning.
Hey, Matt...
her loss, man. Seriously.
Owlsley, Leland: Financial Advisor...
at the prestigious firm
of Silver & Brent...
The funds have been
reallocated as requested.
All the arrangements
made per your agreement
with the guy we're not
supposed to blah blah blah.
Business may continue?
In the best possible way... uninterrupted.
So, uh, what are you going
to do with it when it arrives?
What, you think I'm a
doddering pencil pusher
who moves enormous amounts of money with
no clue as to what it's connected to?
The numbers are like tea leaves.
Nobody reads them like I can.
You're laying out major
reserves to clear the docks...
to make sure the police
don't come within 10 blocks.
More to bribe the comptrollers
to guarantee straight greens.
Know how much all that costs?
I do.
There is a point to all your words?
Yeah, I got a...
What happened to the Russians...
We need to be careful, all of us.
I look out for you... you look out for me.
All I'm saying.
Each man must stand... for himself...
or fall with the unworthy.
What the hell does that mean?
Prick.
Oh, God!
What do you want? My wallet?
You know what I want. Tell
me about the man you work for.
I work for Silver & Brent.
I'm gonna ask you again.
Think about your answer.
Who do you work for?
I told you, I work for Silver and...
You work for Wilson Fisk...
moving his money around.
Which means you have
records, proof of who...
Asshole.
You just gonna lie there all night?
He's getting worse.
When we first took him in, Matthew's
problems seemed less severe.
Now he's in so much pain.
Doctors, clergy, no one has
any idea what's wrong with him.
We heard about your work
with special children
and thought maybe you could help.
Not for free.
His father left a sizeable inheritance.
What about the mother? Is she dead?
No, she's...
Well, that's another story. Here we are.
Make the check out to cash.
I'll take it from here.
They think you're getting worse.
But... you're not, are you, kid?
You're getting stronger.
Let's get started.
So what kind of training is this?
You like ice cream?
Yeah.
Then shut up and eat it.
I'll ask the questions.
First thing you gotta understand is
nobody feels sorry for
you and nobody ever will.
'Cause when it comes to being born lucky...
you won the friggin' lottery.
I did?
What did I say about questions?
"Shut up."
Good.
How old were you when you got blinded?
- Nine.
- Nine?
So you had nine whole
years of looking at movies,
blue skies, up girlies'
skirts that I never had.
I was born blind.
You don't hear me whining about it, do you?
No.
So, you're nine years old, walking
along, minding your own business
and whammo!
Get hit by a truck,
killed dead on the spot.
I wasn't killed.
You lived?
Praise God, it's a miracle.
So you survive the truck
and get this chemical shit in your eyes.
What next?
I hear things.
What kind of things?
Everything.
Coughs and fights and cats meowing.
Sometimes blocks away.
I can sense things.
I know where things are and when they move.
But I can't see.
You know what they call stuff like that?
Gifts.
The special kind.
The kind that very few people have.
Or deserve.
I never thought of it that way.
Well, that's because you're stupid.
I'm not stupid, I'm smart.
Because you taught yourself
how to run your little fingers
over the bumps and read Braille?
Smart don't come out of books, kid.
Smart is making the right
decision at the right time.
Like now.
What's it gonna be, Matty?
You gonna spend your life crying and
rocking yourself to sleep at night?
Or are you gonna dig deep
and find out what it takes to
reshuffle those cards life dealt you?
Your call.
Good choice, kid.
No one's bought me ice
cream since my dad died.
What's it taste like?
Vanilla.
Everybody can taste vanilla.
Pay a little more
attention, use those gifts.
You know what you got?
Sugar grains, vanilla bean,
milk from three different
dairies from two states...
ugh...
batch of chemicals straight
off the periodic tables and...
dirt off the guy's hand
that served it to you.
He spent his morning gardening.
Whole world around you,
Matty, and it is friggin' huge.
And all you need...
are the guts to let it in.
Try.
That dog, what's his story?
He's hungry...
his stomach's growling...
and he's dying to eat the hot dogs
that guy's carrying just upwind of him.
Not bad.
What about the girl?
Her skin's... Her skin's too hot.
Her heart's beating fast.
Is she sick?
Worse.
She's in love.
And the old man?
He's...
He's dying.
And there's nothing you can do about it.
Big world... not all of
it flowers and sunshine.
And the only way guys
like you and me can survive
is to grab it by the
throat and never let go.
If I ask you a
question, will you hit me?
Depends on the question.
How did you find me? How did you know?
Old bitty at the orphanage
thinks it's her idea.
But it wasn't, was it?
Maybe it's one of my gifts.
Or you just got lucky.
That's not an answer.
You catch on quick.
You're going to help me?
No, I'm gonna train you.
How to control your gift,
make it work for you...
use it, and how to fight.
My dad never wanted me to fight.
Your dad ain't here. You'll
need skills for the war.
What war?
We'll get to that
part... when you're ready.
I don't even know your
name. What do I call you?
Stick.
Are you gonna lie there all
night or get up off your ass?
Jesus, kid.
I'm gone five minutes, you turn
this place into a shit show.
You've been gone 20 years.
What are you doing back in my city?
Your city?
Hell's Kitchen hates your guts.
They have you pegged as a cop
killer and some kind of mad bomber.
Yeah, I'm taking care of it.
An old guy just lit you up.
You ain't taking care of shit.
Why are you here?
To save you...
and everyone in the Kitchen
from a horrible death.
More or less.
Paper trail on Union Allied's a bust.
Whoever's pulling the strings
busted up the one big corporation
into a bunch of little ones.
It's an old game.
Spread the records far and
wide, discourage investigation.
God. I mean, it's like...
It's like trying to straighten
out a bowl of spaghetti.
Well, you could always let it go.
Not gonna happen.
I already told you that.
Stop complaining. This is the job.
Researching, gathering facts.
It's long and boring and complicated,
and half the time you still come up empty.
Well, you're just a little ray of sunshine.
Just giving you the lay of the land.
For every exposé I've had published,
there were a dozen that didn't pan out.
All right, all right, so I'm
the new girl on the block,
I don't know what I'm doing, I get it.
What about you? What'd you find?
Ah, bits and pieces. Yakuza...
Wait, the Japanese mafia?
Triads, too. Drugs, I think.
Then there's the bombings
that took out the Russians.
And you think it's all
connected to Union Allied?
Doesn't matter what I think.
Only matters what I can prove.
Wait, what about the cops that got shot?
I mean, you really think
that was the guy in the mask?
I was standing right next to
one of them when it happened.
Detective named Blake.
Didn't like each other very much.
Yeah, I met him...
when they brought me into the precinct.
I see why you didn't get along.
Did what I could.
If he comes out of a coma, maybe...
maybe he'll thank me, tell me
what really happened out there.
Till then...
the man in the mask pops up...
do me a favor, run the other way.
He saved my life, Ben.
How do you know he wasn't
there just to, um...
hurt somebody else?
I... I never... never
thought about it like that.
My experience... there
are no heroes, no villains.
Just people with different agendas.
Yeah, and one of those was to kill me.
Mmm-hmm.
It was.
And you're not careful, maybe
they'll want a second crack at it.
The only way I'll ever feel safe again
is if the people that you are
talking about are put away.
Then we better try harder to
straighten out that spaghetti.
So...
if we can connect...
the tenements, and the
shootings, and Union Allied...
that something you'd take to your editor?
Yeah.
Probably bring home a Pulitzer.
But, uh, I think it's a long shot.
Well, I was a mean three-point shooter
on my high school basketball team.
I like the long shots.
This isn't a game, Karen.
I... I know that.
Anything happens to
you... it's gonna be on me,
and, uh...
I don't want to be responsible for that.
I can't.
I'll be okay.
They're not gonna win.
What a shithole.
You have any idea what I pay in rent?
Expensive shithole.
You had a woman in here.
That's none of your business.
When's she coming back?
- Never.
- Good.
You got a warped perspective on the
whole good/bad thing, you know that?
Women are a distraction.
Just like... furniture, apartments...
Whoa.
Silk sheets.
Cotton feels like sandpaper on my skin.
You'd be better off
sleeping on real sandpaper
than surrounding yourself
with all this bullshit.
This is my life and I made
something of it, without you.
That's the part that really
pisses you off, isn't it?
No, Matty. No, I'm proud
of you, I really am.
The things you've done, what
you've made of yourself, but...
this is...
Surrounding yourself with soft
stuff isn't life, it's death.
Someday those silk sheets
are gonna crawl up behind you,
wrap themselves around your
throat and choke you to death.
You're a warrior.
Yeah...
that's not all I am.
A warrior, heir to the Spartans,
baddest of the bad-asses.
They knew what they had
to do and they did it.
And what was that?
Cut it loose, all of it.
Cut yourself free...
from the women, the
comforts, the fancy job.
The job's not that fancy.
Do you have friends? People you care about?
Yeah, two.
Cut 'em loose, for their sake.
Break their hearts if you
have to, just do it quick.
I'm not gonna do that.
Then they will suffer and you will die.
Relationships are a luxury men
like you and me can't afford.
Is that why you left?
Huh? To protect me?
I had my reasons.
I was a kid.
You still are.
"Boo-hoo. Stick left me.
Think I'll bury my sorrows
between the legs of a supermodel."
Don't push it, Stick.
Or what?
I'm trying to teach you how to stay alive.
Christ, you're worse than your old man.
Born to lose Battlin' Jack.
At least your daddy got
paid when he hit the floor.
You're hurting me.
Make me stop.
- I can't.
- Then quit.
Murdocks never quit.
Then beat me.
I've got all day, kid.
You're just a bully.
World's full of 'em. What
are you gonna do about it?
Feel the breeze.
You got heart, kid.
But heart's not enough.
You've got to control that rage.
You said anger's a weapon.
Anger is a spark, good.
Rage is a wildfire, out of
control, therefore useless.
Just like you laying there.
I thought Murdocks never quit.
It's my fault! It's my fault!
I did it, I killed him!
Killed who?
My dad.
They paid him to lose against Creel.
But... But I wanted him to win.
So he did because of me.
Because of me.
I just wanted him to come home.
But he didn't, and he never will.
We all pay for our choices, kid.
Maybe your old man fought for
you, maybe he did it for himself.
The only thing you know
for sure is he's gone now.
But I'm here.
Now, get up.
Time to stop taking a
beating and start giving one.
Get up.
Get up!
Come on, kid. Show me
I'm not wasting my time.
Took you 20 years to learn
how to get out of that one.
Yeah, I've learned a lot
since you've been gone.
- Like what?
- You're a dick.
That's true.
You got any beer?
Yeah, in the fridge.
I'll bet...
it's that German piss, isn't it?
So you gonna tell me why you're here?
Or is the suspense supposed to kill me?
It's the war, Matty.
Never-ending war.
With who? You never
got around to that part.
Now, the Japanese, mostly.
Look, I don't want you tearing up
Hell's Kitchen going after the yakuza.
Yakuza?
You don't know what's going
on in your own backyard.
The guy that was yappin' with
that old man you slapped around,
he's pretty high up.
He goes by a lot of names.
Using Nobu this time around.
So, Nobu,
you want him so bad, why'd you let
him get away back in the garage?
I don't want him.
I want what's on the ship he's
meeting at the docks tonight.
Right, Owlsley was talking about that.
What's Nobu bringing
in? Drugs or something?
A weapon.
They call it Black Sky,
the bringer of shadows.
What kind of weapon?
The kind you don't want in your world.
Just say it.
- Say what?
- Say that you want my help.
I want you to help yourself.
Nobu and his guys are in tight with Fisk.
You hurt them, you hurt baldy...
You know about Fisk?
I know a lot of shit.
This beer, for example, sucks.
After all your talk about
cutting friends loose, and...
now you need one.
I don't need a friend. I
need a soldier. Committed.
Not some bleeding heart idealist
hanging onto half measures.
You don't know anything
about what I'm doing here.
Kid, in war, people die.
If it's not you, it's the guy next to you.
How many men have you
killed protecting this city?
You're still afraid to cross that line.
Someday, it's gonna come
down to you or the other guy.
If it's not Fisk, somebody else.
What're you gonna do then?
Yeah, a Russian asshole asked
me the same thing recently...
right before he died.
Are you the one that put him in the ground?
No.
Half measures, Matty.
Ah, screw it.
Ride with me tonight...
help me destroy Black Sky,
keep it off the streets,
and I promise you this...
Wilson Fisk will know the taste
of fear the day he faces you
'cause he'll know that you
kicked the guy he's afraid of
right in the nuts.
What do you say, kid?
One rule...
you don't kill anybody.
I swear I will not kill anybody.
Pussy.
Uh...
How's your head?
I'm alive.
It's enough.
How much do I owe you for the groceries?
No, no,
no, no, no. Put that away.
I don't want your money.
No, I don't take charity.
All right.
You can pay me if you want...
with information?
What can I tell you?
A lot, I hope.
I'm working on a legal case...
Oh, yes, yes...
with the handsome lawyer.
Yeah, um, Matt.
No, Mr. Foggy.
Oh.
You
think Foggy is handsome?
I see the way he looks at you.
Never is a man more good looking
than when he is in love.
Oh, Christ.
Oh, uh...
I'm sorry.
Um...
Moving on, um...
I'm
trying to make a connection...
between a construction company
and the repairman that
did this to your apartment.
Why don't you ask Mr. Tully?
He sent them.
I can't find him.
His lawyers say he's on vacation.
I live like this
and that fat shit is lying on a beach?
Ugh. Oh.
Excuse me.
No, no.
I think...
it's pretty damn appropriate in this case.
Do you have papers from the repairs?
Receipts? Anything you had to...
Sign?
No, I'm sorry.
I just called Mr. Tully,
and he sent them over.
Can you tell me what they looked like?
Yes.
One was bald.
Okay.
And the other
had a big tattoo on his arm.
A tattoo?
Of what?
Not a picture.
It was like a...
pattern.
Ugly. Went up to his neck.
Thank God he's no son of mine.
Thank you, Elena.
That might help.
All of this makes me worry.
No.
No, no, no. Elena...
They...
They're the ones that should be worried.
If I can find a connection...
to the men that did this and the company...
...then we
will have their dicks in a vice.
Sorry.
How long
have you been like this,
Miss Page?
Um...
Ever since...
I got to New York.
Oh.
Adiós.
So, why you bothering the old woman?
Get off of me!
- Ahh!
- She gonna spray you.
Maybe I take that away from you,
empty the whole thing in your face.
Burn your eyes out so you don't go
snooping where you're not supposed to.
- Ahh!
- Stupid bitch!
Foggy? Oh, my God.
Wait... what are you doing here?
- What are you doing here?
- Are you following me?
- Yeah.
- Why?
Because you were acting
weird. I was worried about you.
I can take care of myself.
Let's discuss that away
from the maniacs, okay?
- Come on!
- Oh, shit.
How many do you read?
I'm picking up a dozen heartbeats.
Slow, steady, not even a flutter.
There's one more.
Stronger...
different.
Nobu.
They're armed.
MP7s with suppressors.
Huh.
Somebody wants things quiet.
We'll be quieter.
- You remember how to use these?
- I won't need 'em.
Yeah, you will.
Thin out the herd.
- I'll take care of the Black Sky.
- How?
Just do your job, I'll do mine. Move.
Kill him!
Go!
Break.
What rules the body?
My mind.
What's your strongest weapon?
My body.
Connection, mind, body?
The mind controls the body,
the body controls our enemies,
our enemies control jack shit
by the time we're done with them.
Right.
Fighting is just the start.
You have to control your feelings...
your deep down inside feelings.
- How?
- Meditate.
You mean that thing where
you pretend not to sleep?
Yeah. Yeah, that one.
Open yourself up to it... learn it,
make you way stronger, more focused.
Even heal your wounds faster.
You can do that?
How do you think I'm still alive, kid?
I'll learn how, just like you.
Good.
Tomorrow we start with knives.
Try not to get stabbed.
- Stick?
- Yeah?
I have something for you.
It's a bracelet.
From the wrapper on the ice cream
you got me when we first met.
You remember?
I do.
Your training is over.
I can't help you anymore.
What?
Why?
I expected too much of you.
You promised me you
weren't gonna kill anyone.
Yep.
Then what the hell was that back there?
The mission.
That's what your war's
come to? Killing children?
That thing in the
container was not a child.
I could hear his heartbeat.
It was light and fast. He
hadn't even hit puberty.
- You're emotional.
- Yeah, no shit.
If you'd have focused
beyond your crybaby feelings,
you would've sensed
what that kid really was.
He was just a kid.
You're blind as you ever were.
Maybe you should've stuck around
and finished training me yourself.
I needed a soldier. You wanted a father.
Well, I guess we're both disappointed then.
I guess we are.
You take care of yourself, Matty.
I'm not gonna let you kill that kid.
Oh, he's already dead.
I caught up with the van while you
were dicking around with Nobu's men.
I put an arrow in that thing's heart.
You can't even tag an old man.
Get up.
Get up!
Get out of my city.
Maybe there's hope for you yet.
Nice catching up.
Eh?
You can keep the sticks.
You're gonna need 'em.
What part of "Don't tell anyone
about this" didn't you understand?
Foggy's not just anyone... all right?
He's a kick-ass attorney,
and sooner or later we're
gonna need one of those.
And he just plain kicks ass.
When the need arises.
You can trust him, Ben.
He's one of the good ones.
Show him the board.
All right, Ben has everything laid out...
all of the, uh, possible
connections... starting at the bottom...
and moving up.
The king of diamonds?
The man at the top.
Any idea who he is?
No.
But I think he might have been
the one behind Union Allied.
There's another player on the field.
Man in black.
You think he's working for the king?
No.
No, he never would have helped
me expose Union Allied if he were.
If that's the case...
they're working against each other.
So the question is...
which one trumps the other?
It's done.
Black Sky...
no longer a threat.
For now.
What about Murdock?
Stubborn, immature...
Still a real pain in the ass.
Will he be ready when the doors open?
I have no idea.
sync and corrected by Caio
resync by GoldenBeard
www.addic7ed.com