Don't you move!
Don't you freakin' move!
Interlock your
fingers behind your head...
and get on your knees.
On your knees! Do it! Do it now!
Don't you move. I'll put a bullet in you!
Last chance, asshole!
I will not hesitate to put you down!
On your knees, do it!
Keep your eyes on him.
All
right. Nice and slow.
- You got him?
- Yeah, yeah.
Cuff the son of a bitch.
What about this asshole?
Take care of him like we
were told. No witnesses.
Ahhh!
How bad are you hurt?
Central! 15 Eddie!
Shots fired! Shots fired!
Two suspects on foot!
- What's going on?
- All right, listen up, everybody!
We have reports coming in of multiple
explosions all across Hell's Kitchen.
- Hey, Henricks, call PD, get a statement.
- Yeah.
Taylor, reach out to
your guy at public works
and see if gas or methane
had anything to do with this.
What are the locations?
You see me talking here, Urich?
I'm just saying, it'd help if we knew
where we were going to cover this.
Caldwell, give me that list. Where are you?
Please. Come on, come on.
All right, locations are as follows,
44th and 11th, 48th and 9th,
47th and 12th, 42nd and 10th.
- It's not gas.
- How do you know that?
Places that were hit, all
controlled by the Russians.
Ben! Ben!
Yes.
Yes, it is.
I'll let him know.
- Vladimir is in the wind.
- How?
Our friend in the black
mask, he was beating on him,
but stopped Officer Corbin and
his boys from finishing him off.
Then he wasn't trying to kill Vladimir.
Based on what we know, probably
trying to get him to talk...
about you.
Blake was clumsy, letting
the mask get his phone.
I had just texted him the
addresses for the sweep.
We'll deal with Blake later.
We need to contain this.
Vladimir and the mask won't
make it out of the area.
The sweep will pick them up.
Gao put her trust in me.
She gave me her help.
She's going to be disappointed the
situation hasn't... concluded...
as neatly as promised.
What are you gonna tell her?
The truth. Lying to
that woman is impossible.
She'll want to know what our next move is.
Letting the police do their jobs.
That's what I pay them for, isn't it?
There's scumbags in the corridor.
We got two more over there.
You go check on them, okay?
- Every one.
- Yeah.
We got something here.
- He don't look so bad.
- Yeah, all things considered.
Swear to God, that asshole
knew I was a righty.
Oh, that hurts?
English!
Where's Vladimir?
I don't know!
Where would he go, huh, if
he didn't want to be found?
- He's got a girl somewhere maybe?
- I don't know.
I don't know!
I swear! I swear, please, please...
Stop!
Yeah, yeah, all right.
You find anyone alive,
shoot 'em in the head.
- Got it.
- Roger that.
Don't move.
You've been shot.
That sounds pretty bad,
but I don't speak asshole.
I'm going to kill you for
taking my brother's head.
You got the wrong guy. I don't kill people.
Not even scumbags like you who deserve it.
You dropped Semyon off roof.
Put him in coma.
Yeah... but he was still
breathing, wasn't he?
Your mask.
I found it... and what
was left of my brother.
- I didn't kill your brother.
- Lie!
You think I'm the one that blew
your operation to shit, too?
You're being played... by Fisk.
The man you work for.
Look, I don't know what you've been
told, but it's more of Fisk's games.
He's trying to put you
in the ground. I'm not.
Choose a side.
I choose my own.
Not an option.
Fisk made sure of that.
What do you want?
Fisk...
on trial for everything he's done.
Then you're a fool.
Yeah.
And you're bleeding out, so... here we are.
And if I believe you...
and give you what you want to know...
what do I get out of it?
Payback.
I have counterproposal.
Suck my dick.
Vladimir...
Though no one's made official statements
about the nature of the explosions,
the NYPD is urging everyone to stay inside
until authorities are
clear on the nature of...
We need help!
Hey! Hey!
I got an elderly woman over
here and she's bleeding bad!
- Where's she hurt?
- Are you a nurse?
Yeah.
Pretty bad laceration.
- What's her name?
- Mrs. Cardenas. Elena.
We'll wait here for you, Mrs. C!
She's gonna... She's gonna be fine.
- I'm just glad we were with her.
- Yeah.
Early reports from the city...
Jesus, look at this.
It's like a war zone out there.
We better call Matt
and make sure he's okay.
Yeah.
Foggy, you're bleeding.
Huh?
Oh, that explains it.
- Explains what?
- The stabbing pain in my side.
Foggy!
Sit.
Here, just stay here. I'm gonna
go and try to find somebody, okay?
- I'll just, uh... yeah.
- Shit, what happened?
Let's get these people triaged and
coded, and get Central on the line.
We need to reroute incoming
casualties to Mercy or St. Mary's.
What are you doing here?
I heard you were in a car accident.
And since when do you drive?
- I made a very bad decision.
- That's my whole life.
Good to have you back.
Anybody see Shapiro? Shapiro?
Please tell me all this isn't
you dealing with the Russians.
Wasn't me, but I don't think you
have to worry about them anymore.
You call just to tell me that?
No, I need your help.
I found someone who has intel
on what I've been looking for,
but he's been shot.
So call 911.
Can't. Police are the ones that shot him.
Thinking they'd like a
crack at finishing the job.
You want me to come
out to you... in all this?
No, I want you to walk me
through stabilizing him.
It's not as easy as it looks
in the movies, you know?
I don't really go to the movies.
I like records, though.
All right.
There's something else you need to know.
The man I'm trying to save...
it's Vladimir.
The shithead that had me beat up?
That's who you want me to help?
Look, you have every right
to tell me to go to hell,
but he's important, Claire.
What he knows could bring Fisk down
and save more people like
you from getting hurt.
Claire?
- Is there an exit wound?
- Thank you.
Uh, no.
The bullet's still inside him.
It's still half a degree hotter
than the surrounding tissue.
Is there any kind of first aid kit?
I'm in a warehouse. Abandoned.
Tell me what's there, anything you can use.
All right, hang on.
Uh, half a box of nails... broken glass...
uh, wood, duct tape, old
roadside emergency kit,
- lot of plastic sheeting...
- The kit, are there any flares in it?
Yeah, two.
All right... you're
gonna cauterize the wound.
Shouldn't I dig the bullet out first?
Remember what I said about
this not being a movie?
You cut him open and start
digging around, you'll kill him.
This way at least he has a
chance of not bleeding out
before you get what you
need out of him and...
it'll hurt like a son of a bitch, so bonus.
All right, how do I do this?
Just light the flare, hold it close to
his skin until the entry wound seals.
Okay, I'm gonna put you on speaker.
All right, I got it.
Don't let up... no matter
how much he screams.
Professional advice or personal?
Little of both.
All right, cauterizing the wound.
Did it stop the bleeding?
- Thanks, Claire. I gotta go.
- Matt?
Central, Post 41. Pick up of a 10-10.
Northwest corner of 4-7 and 12.
Abandoned building. Gimme an 85.
10-4, Post
41. Additional en route.
Show me your hands!
Show me your hands, now!
He can't hear you.
I'm gonna take my knee off your throat.
Stay quiet, answer my questions,
or your night's gonna
get a hell of a lot worse.
Understand?
Who do you work for?
The City of New York.
I'm gonna ask you again.
Think about your answer.
Who do you work for?
The City of New York. I
got two months on the job.
Call Central.
Tell them it was a false
alarm. No need to send backup.
I do that... you let me walk?
Eventually.
Central, Post 41 K.
10-4, Post 41.
Second floor! Perp in
mask! Wounded civilian...
10-4,
Post 41. 10-13, 10-13.
Abandoned building, 47th
and 12th, second floor.
- Roger that. Adam responding.
- Fifteenth Squad en route.
Where's Sullivan? Anybody got eyes?
Take it down, Pinski.
Me and Hoffman are HNT on this.
Secure the perimeter and
try not to piss yourself.
We gotta do this right.
This is a hostage job.
Nobody goes in and nobody comes out.
Let's go. Move.
You think he's in there?
Sullivan told Central
it was a "masked perp."
Russian was with the dickhead
last we heard, so yeah,
I'm thinking he's the wounded civvie.
- All right, I'll make the call.
- Hey, hey, hey. Whoa.
- Christ.
- Where do you think you're going?
Let's see some ID.
All right, all right. Go ahead.
Detectives!
Thought IAB'd have you riding a desk,
after that thing with the
Russians at the station.
You see what's going on here?
Nobody's riding a desk tonight.
- Can I get a statement?
- Yeah.
The world's a shitty
place. You can quote me.
Where's ESU?
Had their hands full with
that building that went up.
Carl, don't talk to him.
What's the matter with you?
What about the cop in there?
Officer, uh... Sullivan?
How the hell you know that?
How long I been doing this?
Long enough to be a pain in the ass.
Just doing my job.
And we're doing ours... so
stay back and out of the way.
You know, this thing goes sideways, I
can't promise you don't get caught up.
Thanks.
I'll keep my head down.
Yeah, you do that.
I'll let him know. Wait for instruction.
The man in the mask has turned up.
Assaulting a cop in an
abandoned building on 12th.
One of ours?
No, some kid fresh out of the academy.
- What about Vladimir?
- Holed up with the mask.
Blake and Hoffman have
assumed HNT on scene,
secured the perimeter,
waiting for the go-ahead
to take the building.
Give it.
I wanna get this behind us.
There's a complication.
A reporter from the Bulletin.
Turn his head.
It's Ben Urich.
The Union Allied article.
If he picks up on anything
doesn't smell right...
it could be a problem.
Problems are just opportunities
that haven't presented themselves.
You reach out to all of
our contacts in the media.
I want everyone in Hell's Kitchen
to see what's about to happen.
You've been busy.
The building's surrounded.
Ten officers... four dogs.
More coming.
- How do you know this?
- Lucky guess.
- We could have used that.
- I'm not big on guns.
Great. Little stick, much better.
- What did you do to me?
- Road flare.
Cauterized the wound.
You... burned me?
Yeah, I had to stop the bleeding.
No!
Bullet's still inside you.
Wouldn't move around, if I were you.
You expect me to say thank you?
If I didn't need you alive, we
wouldn't be having this conversation.
So you just stand there
and let me die, huh?
But you couldn't kill me yourself.
Is that where you draw the line?
Tell me what I want to know about Fisk.
You think you're different...
from me?
From him?
But you'll get there.
Sooner or later... we all do, men like us.
A man like Fisk just took
out your entire operation.
And he may not own all the cops,
but he owns enough that you
won't make it into a prison cell.
Right now, I'm your only shot at
getting out of this building alive.
His lapdog came to us first.
He told us his employer had taken note.
He complimented...
us on our business.
Invited us to be part
of something bigger...
to expand...
if we entered into an agreement.
What did Fisk offer?
Police looking other way...
aid from politicians...
and access to Chinese and their heroin.
- He's working with the Chinese?
- You really don't know anything, do you?
Just snapping at scraps falling from table.
I want names.
Everything you know about them
and how they connect to Fisk.
There's only one name that matters.
The man that can tie it all together.
Who?
Have you heard of the name...
Leslie Shumway?
No, he work for Fisk?
American schools...
Almost as bad as Russian.
Come on.
Leslie Shumway was an accountant...
to your... Al Capone.
Okay, you know who Fisk's money man is.
Not just Fisk. He handled it...
for all of us.
Who is he? Where do I find him?
We were going to rule this city...
my brother and I.
Vladimir, the name!
His name...
is...
His name is...
This is not how I die.
This is not how it happens.
You see that, old timer? That's
you not mattering anymore.
Television's been around a
while. Maybe you've heard.
- Ah, funny guy. -
Yeah, a real crack-up.
How's it feel, Urich, knowing
that your day's passed?
You're like the freaking dinosaurs,
watching that big rock crashing into 'em.
I still got a few good stories in me.
Maybe you two'll pop up in one of them.
Night's young, never
know what might happen.
We good? You framed up?
Kyle, authorities have cornered
the suspects in the bombings
that occurred earlier this
evening in Hell's Kitchen,
believing they may have taken
a police officer hostage.
While they haven't released the name
of the police officer in question...
Matt, it's Karen, again. Uh, where are you?
Would you just please give
us a call when you get this?
He's still not answering.
- Did you try his apartment?
- Three times.
All right, let's not jump
to things people jump to.
Well, he's a blind guy in a war zone.
Seems like jumping's a
pretty reasonable option.
You don't know him like I do.
Sometimes I even forget he can't
see, the way he zips around.
So you're not worried?
I'm gonna go look for him.
Whoa, whoa. No, no, no,
no. The hell you are.
Lay back.
I'm the closest he has to
family. He'd do the same for me.
I know... and I love that about
you guys, but don't be an idiot.
Wouldn't be the first time.
You've played the hero enough for one day.
You're here, and safe.
So let's keep it that way, okay?
I am gonna go check downstairs...
make sure Matt hasn't been brought in.
- Karen?
- Yeah?
Hell of a first date, huh?
I've, uh...
actually had worse.
This is
Matt Murdock. Leave a message.
Matt? It's Foggy.
Where are you, buddy?
That wasn't very smart.
But it was fun...
watching you bleed.
You think this is a game?
If it was...
you'd be losing.
No...
Come on.
I'm not done with you yet. You hear me?
I'm not done with you yet.
What...
You died.
I brought you back.
You lied, huh?
You can't even stand there and let me die.
No.
Not until you give me what I need on Fisk.
Emergency Service Unit is en route.
Blake and Hoffman are clearing a channel.
Come on, let's go! Move! Move!
They're good
shots. Then shoot.
Tell those guys, they
shoot anyone who moves.
We got ESU on the scene.
Everybody switch your
radios to channel five
and maintain radio discipline.
- What happens next, Detective?
- Don't know.
Maybe you finally get
a story worth printing.
Let's go, fellas.
What are you doing?
Finding us a way out.
I'd like to speak
to the man in the mask, please.
Hello.
Are you there? Can you hear me?
- Who is this?
- I think you know.
You've been asking about me.
I thought it was time we spoke.
- Say your name.
- You first.
That's what I thought.
You and I have a lot in common.
We're nothing alike.
That's what you'll tell yourself.
You're feeding off this
city... like a cancer.
I want to save this city, like you...
only on a scale that matters.
Now tell that to the people you've hurt.
Young man...
life is not a fairy tale.
Not everyone deserves... a happy ending.
I'm gonna find you...
and I'm gonna make you
pay for what you've done.
No, you are not.
Not that I don't admire
what you're trying to do...
to change the world...
with nothing but desire
and your own two hands...
secure in the knowledge that
you're doing the right thing,
the only thing.
That's something that I do understand.
But we both can't have what we want.
So...
your part...
in this drama, by
necessity, comes to an end.
It's gonna take a lot more than
a voice on a radio to stop me.
It's not me you need to worry about.
It's the city you just
blew the hell out of.
You...
You think anyone's gonna believe that?
You're running around in a mask,
holing up with a known felon in
the wake of a series of bombings.
There's that police officer
you're holding hostage, so...
yes.
Actually, I do.
But it doesn't have to be this way.
The Russian...
is he alive?
I'm still here, you fat shit!
Does that answer your question?
It's a one-time offer.
You kill the Russian,
and we'll call the night a push.
You know what he's done...
to women...
to children...
To the people of this city
that you claim to care about.
But do you know how much he enjoyed it?
You just confirmed how important he is.
That must worry you, what he might tell me.
Which means he hasn't
told you anything yet.
You're a child playing at being a hero.
No, no, I'm not trying to be a hero.
I'm just a guy that got
fed up with men like you
and I decided to do something about it.
That's what makes you dangerous.
It's not the mask.
It's not the skills.
It's your ideology.
The lone man...
who thinks he can make a difference.
I'm glad we could talk.
I...
I respect your conviction...
even if it runs counter
with... with my own.
Yeah, keep telling yourself you've won.
It'll make what I'm gonna do
to you so much more satisfying.
Your part ends tonight.
And if that's true,
others will take my place.
They'll see what I was trying
to do and they'll make sure...
No, they won't.
The city will burn you in effigy.
Your name, your very existence...
will be met with abhorrence and disgust.
Do it.
You guys don't seem to be
doing much hostage negotiating.
How many times, Urich?
I told you, back off!
You know, this is bullshit and you know it.
You want to start giving me
some straight answers, Detective?
Huh, Detective? You gonna
start being straight with me?
Blake!
Shit!
Get an EMT! Go! Go!
Go!
- What did you do?
- What you forced me to do.
Goodbye.
I'm afraid we won't speak again.
Fisk...
Fisk!
Fisk, answer me!
Tell our friends to roll the tape.
...authorities ask
that you contact them immediately.
A deadly shooting just moments ago
as three of New York's finest have
been gunned down in Hell's Kitchen.
We still have little information as to who.
We are just getting word
of a fast development
in the investigation into
the Hell's Kitchen explosions.
Turn it up.
Hmm?
Turn it up. I want to hear this.
The authorities have
just released some video.
This is taken just moments
after the explosions
that stunned Hell's
Kitchen earlier tonight,
pulled from a security camera.
And authorities believe this man
is responsible for the bombings,
possibly as part of an ongoing
feud with the Russian mob.
Oh, my God.
That's him.
The same man suspected of
having just shot and killed
the three police officers
- at the scene of a standoff...
- That's the guy who saved my life.
This guy?
Jesus...
You're lucky he didn't kill you.
I don't understand why he
would do something like this.
- He just didn't seem like...
- ...some sort of mask...
I don't know, he just didn't...
General rule...
guys who wear masks have something to hide,
and it usually ain't good.
Battleground of Hell's
Kitchen, one has to wonder
whose side is this man on?
It's really not a good time.
On the news... they're saying
that you shot those cops.
No.
It was Fisk.
It's all Fisk.
What's going on out there?
Hang on.
Claire.
Um...
- What you said, before I left...
- I was...
I'm sorry, I just...
No, don't be. It turns out you were...
You were right...
about me.
I just don't want you getting
caught up if it goes that way.
If we don't get a chance to talk again...
you take care of yourself.
Matt?
Matt, wait!
Clear!
Told you.
This is not how I die.
Second floor clear.
Officer Sullivan is dead.
- I say again, Officer Sullivan is dead.
- What the fuck? No!
This way.
Where are we?
Access tunnels.
The city was built on a network of
these, most of them sealed up years ago.
All right, we have to keep
moving, find a way to the street.
Freeze!
Let's go.
There are five more coming.
All working for Fisk,
probably not even real cops.
We don't have time for this.
I think...
maybe I stay.
We can still make it out of here.
- You turn evidence on Fisk, we can...
- He controls...
all police...
judges.
There's only one way to
stop him, you know this.
No.
I'm not a killer.
The moment you put on the mask...
you got into cage with animals.
Animals don't stop fighting.
Not until one of them is dead.
What Fisk did to me...
he'll do to you.
And he will do it...
to everyone you care about.
Will you feel the same way then?
Or will you be man...
and do what you know you must do?
The dermo who controls
money, his name is...
Leland Owlsley.
He will give you what you think you want.
But it won't be enough.
You know that now, don't you?
Go.
Got something!
Move! Move! Move!
Sync and corrected by Caio
resync by GoldenBeard
www.addic7ed.com