[soulful music playing]
[inaudible]
[theme music playing]
[sniffling] Give me a minute, okay?
Mrs. Urich?
Um... I'm Karen.
Karen Page. I don't know if Ben ever...
Karen, yes.
He talked about you all the time.
He did?
He thought you were something else.
The way you wouldn't let go
until you got to the truth.
He admired that.
We never got around to having kids,
too busy with this or that, but...
if we had, I think he would
have wanted one like you.
[voice breaking] Mrs. Urich, I...
I think it's my fault...
what happened to Ben.
I pushed him into a story
that he didn't want...
Ben Urich never got pushed into
doing anything he didn't want to do.
He was a reporter.
That's what he lived for.
[voice breaking] And he
passed doing what he loved...
what he had to do.
We should be getting back.
It was nice to meet you, Karen.
Is there... Is there
anything that you need?
- Anything at all that I...
- No.
Ben's taken care of all that.
He took out a policy years back when
that river water story turned ugly.
He always took care of me.
[sobbing] Still is.
[Lantom] How you holding up?
Like a good Catholic boy.
That bad, huh?
He was a good man.
And he's gone...
because I haven't stopped
what's happening to this city.
[Lantom] Can't put that
on yourself, Matthew.
You've done everything you can.
A lot you probably shouldn't have.
And here we are.
[Karen] He just stood there,
like he was his friend.
Like he had nothing to
do with what happened.
I thought Ben said he
didn't have any evidence
Ellison was taking money from Fisk.
No, but it makes sense.
I mean, it explains...
[sighs]
Do you know what makes this worse?
Foggy.
Didn't even show up.
You said he left a message.
Yeah, he left a message...
saying he had something more important
to do than come to Ben's funeral.
Come on, he wouldn't say that.
- Yeah, well, it's what he meant.
- [Matt sighs]
It's my fault, Karen...
all of this with Foggy.
No, everyone shares the
blame in a relationship.
That's... just the way that it works.
No, not always.
Why don't you go home, get some rest, huh?
I can't.
[Karen sighs]
Every time I close my eyes, I see...
What if he finds out that I...
That I was with Ben...
at Saint Benezet.
What if he finds out that
I spoke to his mother too?
If that happens, we will deal with it.
How?
I mean, the news barely
mentioned what happened to Ben
because Fisk pays off the media.
And the police haven't
arrested anyone for it
because Fisk pays them off, too.
Foggy was right.
How do you stop someone like
that, someone who has so much?
It just means he has more to lose.
- He's gonna find out what I did.
- No.
He's going to find out,
and he's gonna come after me
just like he came after Ben.
I told you I would keep you safe, Karen...
when he came after you over
Union Allied. That hasn't changed.
Everyone that's taken money from him,
everyone that's helped
him tear this city apart...
they're all gonna get
what's coming to them...
along with Wilson Fisk.
[Vanessa] Wilson?
You should be in bed.
I was calling for you.
I'm sorry, I...
I didn't hear you.
[sighs]
Anything interesting?
Just a transfer of funds.
Wesley made the arrangements for
me to get you out of the country.
- You know I won't leave without you.
- I'm not asking.
I'm just reviewing them, and
then I'll move the funds back.
Is everything all right?
It's just the numbers, I...
I'll have Leland take a look at them...
well, just to make sure.
[Leland] Senator Cherryh's cleared
the last of the zoning hurdles...
after squeezing us for another extra 10%.
Bright side, you'll be able to build
whatever you want on your properties now.
Everyone's been paid
off, everyone's on board.
But we will need to find a
replacement for Gao's heroin trade.
Without it,
we might have some off-the-books
cash flow issues down the road.
What's the word on what happened with her?
Looks like she's in the wind.
Wouldn't have expected it, but maybe
she's not the ally we thought she was.
Mmm, maybe she's not.
What's this?
I asked Wesley to transfer funds
for me the night before we found him.
I thought financials was my job.
Yes, that's why I wanted
you to have a look at these.
There seem to be some
irregularities with my accounts.
Of course there are. I move
money around all the time.
It's a shell game to keep the
SEC off our backs, it's nothing.
Your hand's shaking.
[Leland scoffs] 'Cause
it's freezing out here.
Then why are you sweating, Leland?
[sighs] All right, okay, Jesus.
I figured you'd find out sooner or later.
What's a guy gonna do?
Wesley found out, didn't he?
He confronted you...
and you shot him.
I have no idea what happened to
Wesley. I wasn't a part of that.
But you had something to do
with the benefit, didn't you?
You and Gao?
She's gone, you're stealing from me.
It's not what you think.
You tried to kill me.
[sighs]
The poisonings at the benefit
were just to make it look like
someone was trying to get at you.
But you were never the target.
[inhales sharply] Vanessa?
Do you blame us?
Just look at what's happened
since you took up with her.
[sighs] You've been
distracted, emotional, erratic.
We just wanted to nudge you back on track.
But...
obviously that went south, so...
we will be parting ways...
and I'll be taking half
your assets with me.
[yelling] You think that I would let
you walk away after what you've done?
That's exactly what you're gonna do,
because I have Detective Hoffman.
Hoffman never left the city after he
murdered his partner in the hospital.
I scooped him up, squirreled
him away for a rainy day.
If I don't check in every 24 hours...
Hoffman gets dropped off to the Feds...
tells them all the shit he's been up to.
Hoffman, he's...
he's a frightened little worm.
He would never risk going against me.
Ten million buys a lot of courage.
He thinks he's going
into witness protection,
get the money on the other side.
Now, I know you'll get to
him before he cashes in,
but by then the damage will
already have been done...
and everything you've been fighting
so hard for will come tumbling down.
Yeah, but you would get
caught up in that as well.
I've spent my entire life...
hiding assets overseas for pricks like you.
My son and I will be
just another transaction,
disappearing into the tax-exempt ether.
But I'm a fair sort.
That's why I'm only taking half your money.
You go your way, I go mine.
Not what I'd call win-win...
but it's as close as
we're gonna get with this.
So...
we on the same page?
I, uh...
No...
I don't think we are.
- [Taser buzzing]
- [screams]
[groans]
You hurt her!
Wait, wait!
You hurt Vanessa!
[Fisk breathing heavily]
Sweep the city.
Find Hoffman and put a bullet in his head.
[grunting]
[panting]
How'd you know I was here?
Known about your outlet for a while.
I didn't say anything because I thought
it had something to do with your dad.
Now I know better.
[grunting]
Thought you'd be out punching people
in the head, or whatever you do.
I was. Paid Ben's editor a visit.
- Ellison?
- Yeah.
Karen thinks he's working for Fisk.
Did he talk?
[panting] No, never got close.
Wife and kid picked him
up outside the office.
Try it again tomorrow night.
Looking like you have some anger
issues. Wanna talk about it?
You're not my priest, Foggy...
who you might have met if you'd
shown up for Ben's funeral.
Karen upset?
I told her this was my fault...
all of this between you and me.
[sighs] I just nodded.
You could tell that, right?
Yeah, I could tell.
I was on my way to the
service and I got a call...
from Marci.
From Marci?
She's been helping me...
copying files from Landman
and Zack on the quiet.
Whole stack of documents
on their dealings with Fisk,
- and Owlsley at Silver and Brent.
- [slams fist]
Ben is dead, Foggy, because
he got dragged into this.
And now you're doing the same with your ex.
- We're being careful.
- This has to stop.
Fisk has to...
I have to stop this...
before there's no one left to bury.
Matt...
Matt!
Last time you went after
Fisk, I found you half dead!
More than half.
You go after him in the mask
again, he might kill you.
Or you might kill him,
which would probably have the same
effect on someone as Catholic as you are.
What am I supposed to do?
How do I stop him?
By using the law, Matt.
Like you told me and Karen to
do. That's how we take him down.
We?
Thought Nelson and Murdock were over.
There's nothing I want more than to
find a way back to where we were, but...
[sighs]
I don't know if we can.
No, we can't.
But maybe we can find a
way to move forward, Foggy.
Things are bad enough around here.
Last thing I need is to be seen
chumming it up with the enemy.
Especially ones bringing cigars for my mom.
These are the good ones.
So all the other times
you were buying cheap?
How are things bad? What's going on?
You hear about that warehouse
fire a few days back?
[Foggy] That Chinese place?
[Brett] Yeah, it turns out
it was full of illegal immigrants
and a shit ton of heroin.
And that guy in the mask was there.
I had a run-in with him leaving the scene.
- What happened?
- I got my ass beat.
But this guy, I mean, I don't know,
what he said, it got me thinking.
- I heard he has that effect on people.
- He was working with Ben Urich.
How do you know that?
Because we were working with
Ben, too, on the same story.
Where are you with the
investigation? Any leads?
You know I can't be
talking to you about that.
Story Ben was working
on was about Wilson Fisk.
[Brett] Yeah, the man in
the mask talked about him.
He said half the cops in
the 15th are in his pocket.
You believe him?
No, I've seen things make me wonder.
Ben found Fisk's mom.
Told him some things Fisk
wouldn't want out there.
And you think he killed him for it?
Does it match up with
anything you can't tell us?
[Brett] No, no, forensics couldn't
pull a single print at the scene.
Not even Urich's.
All his files and notebooks are
gone, hard drives wiped clean.
Fisk's mom got the same treatment.
Gone, no record of her at the
care facility Ben found her at.
Looking for you inside, Sarge.
- Yeah, yeah, I'll be in in a minute.
- [officer] Yeah, I'm still here.
Give me the rest of it.
[Brett] I've been gone ten minutes
and already they're looking for me.
[officer] Christ, I thought he
was at the bottom of the river.
I'll reach out to the C.I.'s,
see if anybody's got a line.
Owlsley has Hoffman stashed in the
city. We'll find the little rat shit.
[Brett] Look, I gotta get back.
- Nothing else you can give us?
- No, I've said too much already!
And this guy isn't even listening.
- Just standing there, man.
- I'm sorry.
What were you saying?
It don't matter. The way
things are going around here,
I'm thinking about taking an early pension.
Move my mom somewhere warm.
Be a shame.
The only cop on the force
we know for sure is honest.
Never see Serpico?
Honest cops are usually the
ones get shot in the face.
- Another dead end.
- No, it wasn't.
The cop on the phone, I had a
run-in with him before in the mask.
He works for Fisk?
He was talking to someone about
Hoffman. They're looking for him.
Detective Hoffman? He's alive?
From what I could tell, Owlsley
has him holed up somewhere.
Fisk wants him found, bad.
Hell yeah, he does. Hoffman
could blow this thing wide open.
Only if we get to him first.
[Foggy sighs]
You know what doesn't make you
want to gouge your eyes out?
Cold cuts, Italian meats, cheeses.
Why did I become a lawyer again?
To make lots of money.
[laughs]
That didn't work out so good, did it?
[chuckles] Not so much.
Could have had my own deli,
an apron with my name on it and everything.
- [Karen chuckles]
- What?
Oh, it's just this. It's
the way it should be.
What, Foggy talking about cured meats?
[chuckles] Nelson and Murdock.
It's a start.
Uh, you, uh, find anything?
Well, there's thousands
and thousands of pages, I...
How'd Marci even get this out of
Landman and Zack without anyone noticing?
She can be very... distracting.
- Hmm, I bet.
- [chuckles]
Concentrate on anything
pertaining to Silver and Brent.
Uh, liens, development, property holdings,
anything that might point to
where Owlsley is holding Hoffman.
The corruption, the bombings,
the cops that got shot,
Hoffman knows it all.
He turns, it won't just bring Fisk down.
It'll prove your man in the mask isn't
the asshole everyone thinks he is.
You really think he'll go
against Fisk, even if we find him?
A lot of friction between Fisk and the
other players he's been working with.
[inhales sharply]
Bombed the hell out of the Russians,
the Yakuza went underground,
Chinese heroin went up in flames.
Now Owlsley's making a move.
You don't get to be the man on top
without making enemies
looking to tear you down.
It's just something Ben told me.
He's right. You don't.
So how'd you find out about
Owlsley? You never said.
[Foggy stammers]
Your... pal in the mask.
You saw him?
Oh, my God. When? Where?
[stammering] You know the alley down by...
- [Matt] At the alley by the, um...
- Yeah.
Where we used to, um...
All that matters is he...
he really seems like he's
trying to do the right thing.
- I told you I had a feeling about him.
- [Foggy chuckles]
[sighs] It could take us a
week to sift through all this,
and we have no idea if
these records are complete.
Even if they are, it doesn't mean that
Owlsley's using company
funds to stash Hoffman.
Owlsley's a man of financial privilege.
I never met one that used his own
money when he could use someone else's.
I'll call Marci,
see if she found anything else
might help narrow the search.
Wait, wait.
All right, this is a rundown of all of
Silver and Brent's real estate holdings.
There's 187 just spread
out across New York State.
We already looked at that.
Well, yeah, but the same rundown dated
for the next day, it lists only 186.
Silver and Brent liquidate and
acquire new properties all the time.
One of them probably just sold that day.
Well, I mean, that's what
I thought, but... look.
Look at the balance after the
property disappears from the record.
It hasn't changed.
So, if it was sold, wouldn't that
be reflected in the profit-loss?
Unless someone's trying to hide the fact
the property's been taken
off the records altogether.
No shift in profit-loss,
maybe no one notices.
Or it could just be a clerical error.
- Where's the property?
- Uh...
53rd and 10th.
Hell's Kitchen.
Right, stay here, keep looking through
the documents in case we're wrong.
I'll go to the 15th and
tell Brett what we found.
Couldn't you just call him?
Fisk might be tapping the police
lines for all we know. Keep working.
[Foggy] Hey, hey, hey.
You're not going to the 15th, are you?
I trust Brett, but he's just one
cop. He couldn't handle it alone.
But you can?
I know how you feel about what I do, Foggy.
This is the part where law meets reality.
Either I put on the mask or we
risk losing Hoffman and Fisk wins.
[door closes]
[cell phone ringing]
Yes?
Thank you.
Send the closest team.
No survivors.
[thunder rumbling]
[man 1] All right, all right.
We got subs from Marchioni's.
[man 2] I thought it was pizza.
[man 1] Eh, too hard
to carry with the boxes.
There's a, uh, chicken parm...
Give it here.
- He call yet?
- No.
Still got eight minutes.
Owlsley don't call by then,
- we can get out of this dump.
- Yeah.
[Hoffman] I don't know,
it kinda grows on you.
You got my meatball sub?
[man 1] Yeah, uh...
Here you go.
- [gunshots]
- [grunts]
[officer 1] All clear.
[officer 2] Check over there.
[officer 1] Clear.
Hey, Carl.
Been wondering where you got to.
- [gunshots]
- [man grunts]
[man grunting]
[Masked Man panting]
[shuddering]
You have an opportunity here, Detective.
By turning evidence on Fisk,
you can set things right.
If that's what you want.
If not, you can sit here
playing with yourself
until Fisk sends more men to kill you.
[Hoffman whimpering]
Decide.
It won't make a difference.
He owns the cops.
- I'll be dead before I can testify...
- Not all of them.
Turn yourself in to Brett
Mahoney, you can trust him.
And he knows a couple of lawyers that
can't be bought. They can help you.
Yeah.
Thanks for the tip.
[panting]
I'll be following you to make
sure you get to the precinct alive.
Try to run, try to do anything
other than what I just told you,
you'll wish I never saved
you from that bullet.
[indistinct conversations]
I need to make a statement.
[Foggy] As we stated on the phone,
our client is willing to be
placed in protective custody
and waive all considerations for immunity.
- In exchange for what?
- Nothing.
Detective Hoffman regrets his involvement
in Wilson Fisk's criminal enterprise
and seeks only to unburden himself
in the eyes of God and
the state of New York.
Detective?
[sighs]
I've taken money, a lot of
money, to do things for...
For Fisk.
I'm not the only one.
There's cops, lawyers, judges...
[laughs]
At least one senator I know of.
Start from the beginning.
Names, dates, I want it all.
[Karen chuckles]
[Hoffman] My partner and
I were first approached
by a man working for Wilson Fisk...
18 months ago.
[operatic music playing]
[inaudible]
[music crescendos]
[reporter1] Senator!
[reporter 2] Senator Cherryh!
[reporter 1] Senator, how
do you respond to allegations
that you accepted payoffs from Wilson Fisk?
[Cherryh] I have done
nothing wrong and neither...
no further comment.
Other prominent figures...
a temporary strike when they
walked out of their jobs...
[Fisk] Make the arrangements.
- Wait for my call.
- What they're saying on the news...
They're coming for me, Vanessa.
- So we have to leave now.
- It's too late.
- There's nothing we can do...
- No!
There's nothing that we can do to
keep this from happening. Nothing.
[sighs]
I need you to do something for me.
Listen very carefully.
[siren wailing]
[indistinct chatter]
Do you understand everything I've told you?
- [exhales] Yes.
- There's one more thing.
- [banging on door]
- [man] Federal Agents!
We have a warrant for
the arrest of Wilson Fisk.
- I don't have a lot of time.
- [man] Open the door.
[door breaking]
Wilson Fisk, you're under
arrest for racketeering.
- You have the right to remain silent.
- I want to ask you...
Anything you say can be used
against you in a court of law.
- Vanessa...
- You have the right to an attorney.
- You are my heart.
- If you cannot afford an attorney...
- You're everything.
- One will be provided to you.
Do you understand these rights?
[inaudible]
[reporter 1] Mr. Fisk?
[reporter 2] Mr. Fisk?
How do you respond to the allegations
that you were involved
with the Ranskahov brothers
and that you were
responsible for the bombings?
[reporter 1] Senator Cherryh has stated
that he will be exonerated by the facts.
Do you feel the same?
Mr. Fisk, what about your better tomorrow?
Mr. Fisk?
[reporter 2] Any kind of statement?
Please, any statement whatsoever?
[reporter 3] Mr. Fisk, can you tell
us what you know about the Russians?
The man once hailed as the
savior of Hell's Kitchen
is now believed to have been involved...
[Foggy] Now everybody knows what
kind of asshole Fisk really is.
[Matt and Karen laughing]
And we are the ones that made
it happen, the three of us.
- And Marci.
- And Marci, God bless her designer pumps.
Maybe she's not that bad after all.
Woman does have a way of growing on you.
See, this right here...
in this office.
This is what's important.
Knowing that the people
I care about are safe,
and having some sense of
closure for the ones we've lost.
For Elena.
For Ben.
And everyone else that
son of a bitch has hurt.
[Foggy chuckles]
- Cheers.
[sirens wailing]
I was thinking about
a story from the Bible.
Did I tell you to open your mouth?
Let him talk. Don't mean nothin'.
I'm not a religious man...
but I've read bits and
pieces over the years.
Curiosity more than faith.
But this one story...
There was a man.
He was traveling from
Jerusalem to Jericho...
when he was set upon by men of ill intent.
They stripped the traveler
of his clothes, they beat him,
and they left him bleeding in the dirt.
And a priest happened by...
saw the traveler.
But he moved to the other side
of the road and continued on.
And then a Levite, a
religious functionary, he...
came to the place, saw the dying traveler.
But he too moved to the other
side of the road, passed him by.
But then came a man from
Samaria, a Samaritan, a good man.
He saw the traveler bleeding in the road
and he stopped to aid him without
thinking of the circumstance
or the difficulty it might bring him.
The Samaritan tended to
the traveler's wounds,
applying oil and wine.
And he carried him to an inn,
gave him all the money he had
for the owner to take care of the traveler,
as the Samaritan, he...
continued on his journey.
He did this simply because
the traveler was his neighbor.
He loved his city and all the people in it.
[sighs deeply]
I always thought that I was
the Samaritan in that story.
It's funny, isn't it?
How even the best of men can be...
deceived by their true nature.
What the hell does that mean?
It means that I'm not the Samaritan.
That I'm not the priest, or the Levite.
That I am the ill intent...
who set upon the traveler on a road
that he should not have been on.
[brakes screeching]
[tires screeching]
- Go, go!
- Oh, shit!
[officer] Take cover! Take cover!
[guns cocking]
[muffled gunfire]
Tac One! Tac One!
Requesting sitrep! How copy?
We're taking fire! We're
taking fire! Requesting backup.
What appears now to be
some sort of firefight
involving the FBI transport
carrying Wilson Fisk.
Uh, Janet, can you confirm
what we're seeing here?
Jesus, we were idiots, weren't
we? Sitting here, celebrating,
thinking that it would be
that easy with a man like him.
Let's get out of here before they
close down the streets or something.
[Matt] Get her home. [Foggy] Okay.
No, no, where are you
going? We're not leaving you.
Back to my place, make some
calls, see what I can find out.
- We'll drop you.
- You live on the other side of town.
I'll be all right.
Hang on, I'll get him a cab.
- Wait, Foggy...
- [Matt] Taxi!
[Foggy] You heard what's
going on out there.
You can't go up against
that in your black pajamas.
- I won't be.
- Matt...
I know I haven't earned it, not yet anyway,
but I'm asking you to trust me,
Foggy. I know what I'm doing.
All right.
Go be a hero. Just don't
get killed doing it, okay?
Where you headed?
[indistinct radio chatter]
[officers grunting]
[man] Perimeter secure. Retrieving package.
I don't know who you assholes think
you are, but if you don't back away,
I swear to God, I'll put a
bullet in this fat son of a bitch!
Let's get you out of here, sir.
Package acquired.
[man] Move! Move!
Go!
If anyone tries to follow,
on the ground or in the air,
take them out.
[distant sirens wailing]
Haven't had enough time to get
all of it through the process.
[sighs]
Black parts will give the most protection.
Red might deflect a knife,
depending on the angle...
might not.
It'll do just fine.
Thank you, Melvin.
Betsy?
She gonna be safe now from Mr. Fisk?
I made you a promise.
I intend to keep it.
[sirens wailing]
[officer on radio] All units, be advised,
do not approach subject if sighted.
Notify ESU forthwith.
Repeat, do not approach.
[engine starts]
Package is en route. I say again...
[over radio] the package is en route.
ETA 18 minutes. Prepare for extraction.
Copy that.
- Sir?
- Thank you.
I know this has been a
difficult chapter in our lives.
[Vanessa] We'll be together,
that's all that matters.
Now, if I'm not there by
your side in 20 minutes...
I want you to leave.
I'm not gonna let them take
you away from me, Wilson.
If I'm not there by that time...
there isn't anything you can
do to stop that from happening.
But it won't be the end,
Vanessa. [stammering] It's...
it's just an inconvenience.
Nothing will ever keep us apart.
[sighs]
Fifteen minutes to the drop.
Repeat, 15 minutes to the drop...
- [thudding]
- [tires screeching]
[panting]
[groans]
You were right...
what you told me over the radio that night.
Not everyone deserves a happy ending.
You?
[gunfire]
[grunting]
I wanted to make this city...
something better than it is.
Something beautiful.
You took that away from me!
You took everything!
I'm gonna kill you!
Take your shot.
[yelling]
[grunting]
[Fisk] Come on! Come on!
[grunts]
[yelling]
[groaning]
This city doesn't
deserve a better tomorrow.
It deserves to drown...
in its filth!
It deserves people like
my father! People like you!
[groans]
[both grunting]
This is my city... my family.
- [panting]
- [Fisk laughing]
You really think that this will...
change anything?
You think one man in...
a silly little costume...
will...
will make a difference?
[laughs]
[yelling]
- [panting]
- [sirens wailing]
Police!
Show me your hands!
Do it!
- Show me your hands!
- [panting]
I told you before, Sergeant...
I'm not the bad guy.
Holy shit, it's you.
This man was a fugitive from
the law, and I stopped him.
We good?
Fifteen Sergeant Central.
Be advised,
Wilson Fisk under K, north
alley four-six and ten.
[dispatcher] Copy that.
[inaudible]
Thank you, Sergeant.
Hey, so what am I supposed to
call you when I file my report?
[Karen] Daredevil.
That's what they're calling him now.
The man in the mask.
Daredevil?
Sounds like he's gonna jump Snake
River Canyon on his rocket cycle.
[laughing] It kinda does, doesn't it?
Okay, okay.
I thought it was a bit goofy at
first, but it kinda grows on you.
And it's better than the
Devil of Hell's Kitchen anyway.
Not wrong there.
[Karen] I cannot believe
this is the same guy
that stopped that Union Allied nut
from stabbing me in my apartment.
That is a serious upgrade.
I don't know, I think
the horns are a bit much.
There! Done!
What do you think?
I think I'm glad I fished
it out of the trash.
Me too.
Nelson and Murdock.
- Avocados at law.
- [chuckling]
"Avocados"?
It's a long story.
Which I do not have time to tell you.
Promised Marci I'd help her find a new job
since most of the partners at
Landman and Zack are under indictment.
Oh? You two getting back together?
No. I don't know.
Maybe.
[both laugh]
Well, thank her for us.
For everything she did
helping bring Fisk down.
Fisk still needs to go to trial.
Just getting a court date on a
case this big could take a year.
- That long?
- He's where he belongs,
that's all that matters.
And we put him there.
Yeah, we did.
Hell of a sign.
Now all we need are clients.
One day at a time,
partner. One day at a time.
Guess that means we
should get back to work.
- Hey, Karen.
- Yeah.
There's been something in your voice.
[stammers] It's been there for a while now.
I thought whatever it
was, whatever's been...
I thought it would get better
once Fisk was put away, but...
it hasn't, has it?
[sighs]
We put him away, yeah...
but it won't bring back Elena...
or Ben...
or erase what we've been through, or...
what we've had to do to get here.
Yeah.
A lot of decisions I'd give
anything to go back and change.
[breathes deeply]
But I can't.
None of us can.
It's like I told Foggy, all
we can do is move forward...
together.
Come on.
[inmates speaking indistinctly]
[sighs]
[woman screaming]
[dramatic music playing]
- Sync and corrected by Caio -
Resync by GoldenBeard
www.addic7ed.com