Seven o'clock a.m.
Matt wouldn't understand.
You know what he would say.
That we're awesome?
No, that we're being stupid.
I prefer the term
"foolheartedly provocative."
Yeah, that's lawyer talk
for stupid. You want coffee?
If we're gonna be Nancy Drew-ing together,
I think a certain level
of honesty is required.
What? You don't like my coffee?
No, I hate it.
I appreciate the effort, but
the technique, or lack thereof...
My God, you are such a dick.
On occasion some dickery may leak
out, but doesn't mean I'm wrong.
Well, it means somethin'.
Okay, let's say we keep Matt in the dark.
How long do you think...
I should grow my hair? Matt,
what's your take on that?
- Mullet? Full pony?
- Holy shit.
- Did you fall down again?
- Oh, it's nothing.
- Don't tell me what?
- Damn it!
You heard that?
Guy's like a bat.
Not blind like a... I mean,
you know, with the hearing.
- Bats aren't blind, Foggy.
- They're not?
It's a myth.
So, we're good.
- Karen.
- Yeah?
What don't the two of you want me to know?
We're investigating Union Allied.
Remind me to keep you
off the witness stand.
- You can't be doing that.
- Why not?
For starters, you signed legal papers
and took money to leave it alone.
No, I signed papers saying that
I wouldn't go public and I won't.
- We have someone lined up for that part.
- What part?
Breaking the story that, uh...
Look, whoever is behind Union Allied,
or whatever they call themselves now,
they are trying to
strong-arm people like Elena
so that they can sweep
their homes away from them
and build condos no one can afford.
And what do you think's gonna happen
when these "whoevers" find
out what it is you're up to?
- We already took care of it.
- Took care of what?
The, uh, guys who busted
up Elena's apartment.
They, uh, came after me when I
was leaving her place last night.
Are you okay?
Yes.
Foggy was following me.
- Mmm-hmm. Why? Why were you
following her? - She was acting funny.
- No, there was no funny.
- There was a little funny.
This is what I'm talking about.
There are things out there.
You can't be doing this. You're
gonna get yourselves hurt.
No, I have already been
hurt by those bastards.
You know, I don't care what I signed
or how much money they
paid me to forget. I don't.
And I'm not just going to
stick my head in the sand
and let it happen to somebody
else because I am scared.
Which I am... a lot.
And if you could see her
face, you'd know she means it.
Yeah, I kind of got that.
Right, who else is involved?
Who's helping you break whatever it
is you think you're gonna find out?
Ben Urich, from the Bulletin.
The one who wrote the Union Allied piece?
Karen's been working with
him. He seems like a good guy.
Yeah, everybody
does, until they aren't.
No, I trust Ben as much
as I do you or Foggy, Matt.
I know what I am doing.
I am not some kid...
Then don't act like one. Both of you.
I know you're just trying
to do the right thing here,
but we have to be smart about this.
We?
First rule, no more skulking
around, asking to get hurt.
We do this, it's gonna be on
our turf. The legal system.
That's not nearly as
heroic as you might think.
I don't want anyone to be a hero,
Karen. I want you to be safe.
And I want to protect this firm and
everything we're trying to build here.
We know the law. We'll
use it to our advantage.
Agreed?
Do we have a choice?
Not so much.
Yeah, okay.
So, what's the second rule?
I don't know, I'm making
this up as I go along.
I understand your position.
You need to understand mine!
He questions
the validity of your position.
I say it is of piss and shit.
Well, I'm sorry you feel that way.
Nevertheless, my point is valid.
You made guarantees.
- Which I met.
- The Black Sky is dead.
You asked that the docks
and your transit path
be clear of police interference.
Did you observe any police?
No.
Of course not, because I'm a man of honor!
It will be difficult to
locate another Black Sky.
They are extremely rare.
Perhaps you should have told
me the importance of your cargo
before you lost it.
He's asking
if you'd like to renegotiate
the terms of your relationship.
I'm...
sorry if I offended you.
My apologies.
You get that last part?
Yes, threats are clear in any language.
He needs to be taught some manners.
Leave it alone.
If the Russians had
spoken to you this way...
They aren't the Russians.
No, the Russians actually contributed.
Leland's financials, Gao's product,
and Vlad and Anatoly's distribution
until we absorbed that facet.
What do Nobu and his
men bring to the table?
What... What are they in all this?
A necessary evil.
I just... I don't like the way
he speaks to you, that's all.
Especially now, when
everything's going our way.
That's exactly when
you need to be cautious.
Can you please turn that down?
Your mom don't like music.
- I like it.
- That's 'cause you got taste.
I love music. Just not so loud.
What the hell good is
it if you can't hear it?
- Right, Willie?
- Right!
Never trust the quiet ones.
Those are the pricks that
are always up to something.
You cut it too short.
What did I tell you?
Sorry.
Sorry, what?
Sir.
Respect. You gotta give it if you want it.
Don't forget that.
Make the next one longer.
You want your pop's face in the dirt?
- No, sir.
- Damn right.
You see that? That's our ticket.
Once you get on the city council,
everybody wants to put a
little somethin' in your pocket.
Remember Mr. Flores from up the street?
- No.
- 'Course not.
You know why? 'Cause he got on the council
back when you were still
shitting in your pants.
Bill!
But he ain't around no more.
One year after he got voted in,
packed up, got himself a real house.
Really?
Just like we're gonna buy.
This city? It's everything.
It's right there.
All you gotta do is put your
mind to it and make it happen.
You want a sip?
- He most certainly does not.
- Huh?
My dad let me take a sip from his
glass before I could talk. Go on.
Go on. What are you lookin' at her for?
I said it's okay. Take a big one.
Go on.
That's it.
Bill, what are you doing? Jesus!
Come on, it's funny. He's a man.
Let him be a man.
- You worry too much.
- Somebody has to.
How are we paying for all this?
Got it covered. I took a loan.
A loan?
- What'd the bank make you put up?
- No, no, no. Screw the bank.
Rigoletto floated me.
- Rigoletto?
- Who's that?
Nobody, forget it.
It's an investment, Marlene.
You gotta spend money to make money.
Once I get on the council,
this is all taken care of.
- I don't know about all this.
- You don't know about nothin'!
You gotta take risks.
You want something out of life,
you gotta put yourself out there.
You gotta put yourself out there, Mom!
You see? The
kid is smarter than you.
Yes, honestly.
I've spent most of my time abroad in Asia.
Yes.
I would.
Maybe, we...
We...
Could you please hold on a second?
Wait.
I'm so sorry. I need to take this.
I know, me, too. Good night, Vanessa.
Yes?
We have a situation.
- Nobu?
- Detective Blake, he just woke up.
Our contacts in the media tell us
that it's gonna be tonight's lead.
Has he said anything we
need to be concerned about?
No, he's conscious, but
his injuries were extensive.
I'm hearing he can't speak yet.
That changes,
unlikely he's gonna be
overjoyed we had him shot.
Yes.
Well...
take care of him.
That poses an issue.
There's a detail on his floor.
Twenty-four hour presence,
in case the man in the mask
tries to finish the job.
Are any of them ours?
Two... but not on the door. They
try to get in, it'll be noticed.
What about his partner, Hoffman?
I can reach out, but they go back,
since before the academy. I, uh...
I doubt he'll be receptive.
Set a meeting...
and I'll speak with him myself.
Understood.
This is pointless, Matt.
We should be out on the streets,
cracking names and taking skulls.
- I think you have that backwards.
- Not the way I do it.
Five minutes out there
and you'd end up in intensive care.
Hey, I handled myself pretty damn skippy
against baldy and his tattooed gorilla.
- Tell him, K.
- No, you did.
What? I'm... What, I'm "K" now?
- Trying something
new. - Mmm-mmm. Don't.
Wait, this is interesting.
Confederated Global Investments.
The company that hired us to
defend that bowling alley nut?
Yeah. Karen, do you have
a list of the subsidiaries
you were able to track
down through their check?
Uh, yeah, yeah, I think so.
Yeah, yeah, I got it.
Can you tell me if...
Westmeyer-Holt Contracting is on the list?
Um...
Yeah. Yeah, it is.
There are half a dozen
complaints against them
for doing the same thing
they did at Elena's tenement.
Confed Global's trying to
force renters out of tenements?
What about Elena's
landlord? That Tully guy?
I mean, he's gotta know
something about this.
- See if I can track him down.
- Use the phone.
Oh, come on!
- I'm making that rule number two.
- Your rules suck.
- I want that on record.
- Fine, noted.
Oh, my God.
- What do you got?
- Uh, no, it's not, um...
The New York Bulletin online
just reported that that cop that got
shot, he just regained consciousness.
- Detective Blake?
- Yeah.
Guy's a real dick.
Still, he didn't deserve a
bullet from that masked douchebag.
Okay. Nobody knows
what really happened out there.
Detective Blake might.
Be interested in what he has to say.
Yeah, so would I.
We can't allow this to happen.
I know that you have...
feelings regarding this matter.
I respect that.
But if Detective Blake
chooses to speak out of turn...
the result would be...
unpleasant, for you and for me.
Out of turn? You shot him.
Technically, we paid
someone else to shoot him.
Do you know what made us go down this path?
What led to a decision of such finality?
If you're worried about me, I
know how to keep my mouth shut.
If we doubted that, we wouldn't
be having this conversation.
Being informed...
knowing facts as they are...
not how we wish to perceive them,
can tip the balance between life and death.
Unlike you, your partner was
inconsistent in his attention to detail.
Well, that masked asshole beat
him senseless and broke his arm.
It wasn't his fault.
Yes, I forgave him for
that. What I find indefensible...
is we were not alerted...
that the addresses we
provided had been compromised.
They were given to ensure that any
Russian who survived the bombings
would be properly attended to.
Not to aid the man in the mask
at locating Vladimir Ranskahov.
That led to an unfortunate complication.
One that your partner was
directly responsible for.
Yeah.
So, how long before I do
something that pisses you off?
Oh, the answer to that
is entirely up to you.
See, he's more than my partner, right?
He's my friend.
I've known him since I was
a kid. That's 30, 35 years.
How much...
are each of those years worth to you?
Hmm?
In round figures?
- Hey.
Good news, right?
Yeah, he always was a tough son of a bitch.
Yeah. Hey, you gotta sign in.
Oh, yeah, sure, sure.
- And I gotta check the bag.
- Yeah.
Mmm, meatball?
Yeah, from Marchioni's.
He loves that place.
I don't know, I thought
it might trigger something.
- Yeah. Well, come on in.
- Thanks.
I'm sorry.
What are you doin'?
I need you to listen to
me. We don't have much time.
Whatever your partner
just injected you with
has already reached your heart.
You're gonna be dead soon.
And there's nothing anyone can do about it.
But you can make the man responsible
for this pay for what he's done.
Hoffman!
Tell me everything you
know about Wilson Fisk.
- Hoffman! Open the door!
- Is it my turn for this?
Hoffman, what the hell
is going on in there?
- Go! Go!
- Get in there!
Move, move, move!
- Move!
- Come on! Let's go!
Go!
Look at my face. I can't go
into the office like this.
I'm afraid to go anywhere with that
masked psychopath running around.
My son was coming to visit.
I had to tell him,
"Nope, stay out of New
York, Lee. Shit's goin' on."
I'm 73 years old.
You know how many times
I have left to see him?
I apologize for the inconvenience, Leland.
I'm not looking for... Are you done?
This thing itches like a son of a bitch.
It'll keep you safe when he's finished.
What's this coated with?
Polyethylene, glycol, silicate.
- Hydro-clusters form when kinetic
energy... - Yeah, great. I'm a 46" long.
- That'll be all, Mr. Potter.
- Okay.
You need anything else, Mr. Fisk, sir?
- Not today, Mr. Potter. Thank you.
- Okay.
Kid's half an idiot.
It's the other half that counts.
So...
what am I supposed to do here? Seriously?
He knows who I am.
He found me once, he'll do it again.
I'll move you someplace
safe until it's resolved.
- I'll put six men on you.
- Make it a dozen.
If he drops me off a roof,
an awful lot of money is
going along for the ride.
- That sounds like a threat.
- No, just stating the obvious.
Never thought I'd have to with you.
Is it taken care of?
Yes, but there was a complication.
Well, there's a word I'm
hearing more and more.
What happened?
Right after Hoffman injected Blake,
he was incapacitated by our masked friend.
When Blake was still alive?
And talking, according to Hoffman.
That's
great. That's wonderful.
So we have no idea
what the guy you had shot
might have said to the whack job
you had framed for it?
- No, but there is
an upside. - Mmm-hmm.
Hoffman was able to spin it.
Told everyone he was assaulted
by the man in the mask,
then he finished what
he started with Blake.
So we're not exposed on that front.
Well, let's have a parade.
This guy, Hoffman, how much does he know?
We're taking care of it, Leland.
Well, that fills me with warm comfort.
Situation's being handled, all right.
Just not by you.
You're gonna
be all right, Wilson.
It's okay, honey.
Have some Zuppa, okay?
- I'm not hungry.
- You eat it.
It'll make you feel better.
- Are you having some?
- Sure, baby.
Mmm.
Do you think it's true? What Bernie said?
You can't listen to people like that.
You have to just block them out.
The hell happened to you?
It's all right, I've got this.
You feed him too much of that shit.
You want him to get
fatter than he already is?
- Bill!
- Come on, what happened?
- It was that Bernie Walker kid...
- Am I asking you?
What did he do?
He was knocking your signs down.
I told him to stop, but he wouldn't.
He said I was a loser... just like my dad.
Get your coat.
Get your coat!
Hey!
That him?
You been knocking down my signs?
Yeah, so? Election's over.
Doesn't give you the right to destroy
other people's property, does it?
Oh, you're not running your mouth now, huh?
My boy said you had plenty to say to him.
I put myself out there.
You think it's my fault they
don't see it, what I could bring?
You wanna call me a loser
to my face, you little shit?
I didn't call you a loser, man.
Oh, my boy's a liar now, huh?
He say it, or not?
- Speak up when I'm talking to you.
- He said it.
No, I didn't. My dad did.
I was just repeating it.
You think that's funny?
Huh? What a man tries to do?
- How he puts himself out there?
- Whatever, man, Jesus.
Hey! Hey, I'm talking to you.
Dad!
Say something funny!
Say something funny! Go ahead!
Dad, stop!
Huh?
- Come here.
- Dad...
Come here. Come here.
Come here.
It's people like this
that wanna keep you down.
Keep you afraid.
You have to show 'em that
that can never happen.
You gotta show 'em that you're a man.
Kick him.
Don't give me that look like your
mother. You do what I tell you. Kick him.
Kick him!
Kick him again.
Keep kicking him! Kick him!
Harder!
Kick him! Kick him!
Yes?
Gao reached out. She'd like a word.
- Send the car around.
- She's coming to you.
Now.
Can you be here before she arrives?
I'm already on my way.
Thank you, Wesley.
She
approves of your choice of tea.
I picked it up on my last
visit to your country.
I thought you might enjoy it.
She
says she didn't come for tea.
He does not need you to form my words.
Do you, Wilson?
You speak English.
I speak many languages.
How many?
All of them.
And you speak my tongue,
do you not?
How long have you known?
Since the beginning.
It is the clever man who plays the fool.
And a foolish woman...
who does not recognize it.
Tell me,
has Nobu guessed you
speak Japanese as well?
I don't believe so, no.
You may leave us.
Wait outside.
Nobu
isn't very happy with you.
That man is never happy with anyone.
True.
But...
I have heard Leland...
is equally displeased.
It's under control.
How do you think...
I knew where you live, Wilson?
This is one of your most guarded secrets,
yes?
The king in his castle.
Did I divine the location
from bones and spells,
chanted beneath the moonlight?
No.
I discovered it because...
you have become sloppy.
And emotional.
Just as the Russians became,
in their final moments.
Recent events have been trying,
I admit.
But I promise...
I am not here to pluck
flowers from a thicket.
This is a courtesy,
because you have shown me respect.
Restore your house to order.
Or I will begin dealing...
with Nobu and Leland directly.
Gratitude for the tea.
Get out.
Sir, if there's anything I can bring...
Get out!
Think of the man you wanna be.
You sit here and you stare at that wall
and you think about that.
You're my son.
You should be a king,
not some fat little pussy.
Sit.
What'd I say? Don't look
at me, look at the wall.
Don't take your eyes off till I get back.
It's late, where are you going?
I gotta take care of
something, what's it matter?
Can't it wait till tomorrow?
No, Marlene, it can't, all right?
I gotta talk
to Rigoletto... tonight.
- Oh, Jesus.
- Don't worry.
- How much you owe him?
- Don't worry about it.
- How much?
- I got it covered.
That's all you need to know.
You know, I told you, you shouldn't
have borrowed money from him.
But no, you had to be the big shot, huh?
You had to have your face plastered all...
It's not enough I get that shit out there?
I gotta get it in my own
house? In my own house?
- Bill! No, no, no, no, no!
- Shut up! Shut up!
- Shut up!
- No, please!
- Shut up! Shut up!
- No, please! No!
Shut up!
I didn't call for you.
No, I just thought you
might need something.
If I needed you, I would've asked.
I don't think that's always true, sir.
We'll be all right. Thank you.
I like your place.
Not sure about the table.
- Looks like you aren't, either.
- Please go.
If that's what you really want.
He's worried about you... your friend.
Ah, he shouldn't be.
You made a promise...
to always be honest with me.
What is it?
I'm afraid.
Of what?
The way you'd look at me if you knew.
Tell me.
Shut up! No, please!
Shut
up! I don't wanna hear it!
- I lost because of you!
- No!
- Because of this family.
They see it!
They see you and that little
bastard and they laugh!
- And you don't believe in me!
- I do.
- And you see what happens?
- No!
- You see what happens?
Oh, God, no!
You don't believe in me! Shut up!
Stop it!
What are you gonna do
with that, fatty? Huh?
Huh?
That's what I thought.
You believe this kid? He
gets that shit from you.
Oh, God.
Keep kicking
him! Keep kicking him!
Keep kicking him!
Wilson...
- It's okay.
- Mommy.
It's all right. It's all right,
baby. It's all right.
It's all right. It's okay. It's
okay. It's okay. It's okay, baby.
It's okay.
Okay.
Get the saw.
We carried him in bags down to the river.
One every night, for the next week.
Everyone in town knew that
he owed money to Rigoletto.
So, I guess they thought that...
he'd left town to avoid him.
My mother, she sent me
to live with relatives
on the farm that I told you about.
It wasn't your fault.
You were protecting your mother.
I didn't do it for her. I did it for me.
That's
why I still wear these.
To remind myself that I'm not
cruel for the sake of cruelty!
That I'm not my father!
That I'm not a monster!
Am I?
No, Wilson.
You aren't.
But soon it won't matter.
There are people out there
that want to expose me.
They don't understand what
I'm trying to do for this city.
They want to drag my
name through the streets!
They want to destroy everything
that I'm trying to accomplish.
And are you going to let them?
No.
It was a total bust. No, I...
Ellison. Ellison, no...
He's a crazy old man in a tinfoil hat.
And why are we chasing
a story like this anyway?
What?
Shit.
Look, can I call you back?
I'm drowning out here.
Yes, yes, okay. Fine.
We need to talk.
Do you know who I am?
The Devil of Hell's Kitchen.
Do you believe that?
What they're saying about me?
You've been in an awful lot of wrong
places at the wrong time lately.
But I've heard the other stories.
About the man in the mask, helping people.
Sounds like maybe there's
more than one side to you.
I didn't blow the hell out of the Russians.
And I didn't shoot those cops.
So, what?
You want me to write your side of this?
No, I want you to expose
the man responsible.
The man who's tearing this
city apart, piece by piece.
You got a name?
Wilson Fisk.
- Never heard of him.
- Because he doesn't want you to.
That's what makes him dangerous.
Living in the shadows,
no one knowing who he is.
Said the man in the mask.
- I'm trying to protect this city.
- Maybe.
But right now they hate you. And
have no idea who this Fisk guy is.
You can change that.
So could 100 other reporters.
Why me?
There are good people who trust you, Ben.
I have faith in their judgment.
Union Allied.
Guessing that was you who dumped that
guy on the doorsteps of the Bulletin?
I think he's connected to Fisk.
That woman you saved that night?
She's a good kid.
Still believes you're a hero,
despite what everybody's saying.
People like her are why I do this.
If I do the smart thing and say no?
Then I'll have to stop him some other way.
That has a ring of finality to it.
I'm not a killer.
I keep telling people that.
But that could change, couldn't it?
What do you got?
Bits and pieces.
Russians... Triads... Yakuza...
all funneling money through
a man named Leland Owlsley.
The Wall Street guy?
How'd you get all this?
How do you think?
So all you got is what
you've beaten out of people?
- I can't print that without credible...
- Detective Blake...
I was at the hospital when he died.
Yeah, they're saying
you sent him on his way.
It was his partner, Hoffman.
They both worked for Fisk.
Blake gave Fisk up, before he went.
You get this on tape?
Somebody else in the room
to corroborate what he said?
I need reliable sources.
A bunch of "he said, she said"
is not gonna put this guy away.
We don't need to put him away.
Just drag him into the light.
Give him nowhere to hide.
Once the city knows who he is...
they'll tear him apart.
And this is the guy at the
top. You sure about that?
I'd bet my life on it.
You're betting mine now, too.
Tell me everything you know.
"'You get what you deserve.'
It's an old saying.
One that survived the
years, because it's true.
For the most part.
But not for everyone.
Some get more than they deserve.
Because they believe they
aren't like everyone else.
That the rules, the ones
people like me and you,
the people that work and struggle
to live our lives, just live,
don't apply to them.
That they can do anything
and live happily ever after,
while the rest of us suffer.
They do this from the shadows.
Shadows that we cast.
With our indifference.
With a pervasive lack
of interest in anything
that doesn't directly affect
us, we, in the here and now.
Or maybe it's just the shadow of weariness.
Of how tired we are,
struggling to claw our way back to
a middle class that no longer exist,
because of those who take
more than they deserve.
And they keep taking,
until all that's left for the rest of us
is a memory of how it used to be
before the corporations
and the bottom line decided
we didn't matter anymore.
But we do.
You and I, the people of this city...
we still matter.
There's someone in Hell's Kitchen
that doesn't share this belief.
He's been among us for quite some time.
You've never heard his name.
You've never seen his face.
He's stayed in the shadows.
Because men like him, men that
want to control our city, our lives,
fear the light and what it reveals.
This man must no longer be
allowed to operate in the darkness.
If he has nothing to hide,
let him step forward."
I'm not very good
at this, out, being in public.
But I felt the need to
speak up for this city
that I love with all my heart.
No one should have to live in fear.
In fear of madmen...
who have no regard for who they injure.
In fear of the Devil of Hell's Kitchen,
who has inflicted untold
pain and suffering.
This masked terrorist and
psychopaths of his kind,
we must show them
we will not bow down to their
campaign of coercion and intimidation.
We must stand up to them.
As this man, my dearest
friend, Leland Owlsley,
a pillar in the financial community,
stood up when he was recently assaulted.
But this assault was for no other
reason than to send me a message.
A message warning me to stop.
To give up my dream that
I have for this city.
A dream of a better place.
A place for its citizens to feel safe.
To feel pride.
I tried to do this quietly,
not wanting to draw attention.
The last thing I wanted
was for anyone close to me
to become a target from those
who do not share my dream.
For those who will have this
city stay exactly as it is,
mired in poverty and crime.
But I know now it was
foolish to make that decision.
That I can no longer do it alone.
That I cannot keep living in the shadows...
afraid of the light.
None of us can. None of
us should be forced to.
We must do this together.
We must resist those who
would have us live in fear.
My name...
is Wilson Fisk.
And together, we can make
this city a better place.
- Sync and corrected by Caio -
Resync by GoldenBeard
www.addic7ed.com