Thank you Stan
Sub by darelik
You know what time it is?
Can't sleep.
There are terms for that.
Yeah, but then I'd be sleeping.
Dreams again.
Wanna fight?
I slipped.
Right, you slipped. As a result of me punching you in the face.
I was already slipping
when you happen to punch
me in the face.
The two of those are not related.
Tell me about this dream.
Anything new?
No.
Let go of the past.
I remember my past.
It's causing you doubt.
And doubt makes you vulnerable.
Control it.
Lose control again and you'll have to
commune with the Supreme Intelligence.
There's nothing more dangerous
in a warrior than emotion.
Humor is a distraction.
Anger.
Anger really serves the enemy.
120 days elapsed from the T
Has anyone ever seen what the Supreme
Intelligence really looks like?
No one can look upon a Supreme
Intelligence in its true form
You know that.
Our subconscious chooses
the way they appear to us
So it's sacred.
It's personal.
No Kree divulges it.
Ever.
Who do you see?
Your brother.
No.
Father.
Your old commander.
Vers.
It's me you see, isn't it?
I see what you're trying to do.
Is it working?
Yes.
But you won't succeed
in changing the subject.
What is the point
of giving me these
if you don't want me to use them.
I want you to use them.
The Supreme Intelligence
gave me the responsibility
of showing you
how to use them.
I know how
If that were true you could've
knocked me down with them.
Control your impulses.
Stop using this and start using this.
(It's) on you
To be the best version of yourself.
Vers.
Intelligence.
Your commander insists
that you're fit to serve.
I am.
You struggle.
with your emotions.
With your past, which fuels them.
You were just one victim
of the Skrull expansion
that has threatened our
civilization for centuries.
Impostors who silently infiltrate
and take over our planets.
Horrors that you remember
and so much that you do not.
It's all
blank.
My life.
You're supposed to take the form of
who I most admire.
But I don't even remember
who this person was to me.
Perhaps this is a mercy.
Sparing you from a deeper pain.
Freeing you
to do what all Kree must.
Put your people's needs before your own.
We've given you a great gift.
The chance to fight for
the good of all Kree.
I want to serve.
Then master yourself.
What was given can be taken away.
I won't let you down.
We'll know soon enough.
You have a mission.
Serve well and with honor.
This can't be good.
Must be another Skrull attack.
If it is, it's big.
Has the Skrull ever simmed you?
Once.
It was deeply disturbing.
Why?
Because I started into the
face of our mortal enemy
And the face staring back was my own.
Maybe if they were more attractive
Then it would be less disturbing.
You think you're funny
I'm not laughing
You never laugh.
I laugh.
On the inside.
I'm not doing it now.
It's funny coz objectively speaking
you're quite handsome.
Why, thank you.
Listen up team.
Knock it off.
Right.
Prepare
for
a Search and Rescue of our spy, Soh-Larr.
The Skrulls have invaded
yet another border planet.
This time, Torfa
Soh-Larr sent us a warning,
the signal was intercepted
and his cover's blown.
The Skrull General Talos have
sent kill units to find him.
Should they reach him before we do
the intelligence he's
acquired over three years
is as good as theirs.
The accusers will bomb a Skrull
stronghold here in the south.
We slip in,
we locate Soh-Larr,
then we get out
leaving them none the wiser.
The Torfa populace
We are not to interfere
with them nor them with us.
Nothing compromises the
security of our mission.
Proceed with caution.
Follow protocol before extracting him.
This is a dangerous mission.
We must all be ready
to join the Collective
if that is our fate today.
For the good of all Kree
For the good of all Kree!
Vers, track Soh-Larr's beacon.
Att-Lass, Minn-Erva, (find the diversion?)
Locals on the periphery.
Maybe a dozen.
Minn-Erva.
Do you read me?
Anybody copy?
Damn.
His beacon's coming from that temple.
- Let's move.
- No.
This is a perfect spot for an ambush.
Only one way in.
Only one way out.
We can get past the locals.
We don't know if they are locals.
Too risky.
You don't have to go with me.
I'll go alone.
No, you won't.
Right.
We keep a close radius.
We lose comms, meet me back at the helio.
Come on.
Att-Lass, you getting this?
Copy. I see them.
Get back!
Commander!
Back.
Back!
Minn-Erva
Do you have eyes on this?
Get back.
Minn-Erva!
Does anybody copy?
I don't wanna hurt you.
Move back.
Stay back!
They're locals.
I found two dead.
No grave.
They're just starving.
HGX-78
2RT-7-9
AXX
Get back.
Skrulls!
Vers!
Incoming!
How did you know
the code?
How 'bout I tell you my secret
when you tell me yours?
Let's open her up!
Where
are we? (S??)
Where's your head at?
In the clouds.
Where's yours?
On my shoulders?
'Bout to show these boys how we do it!
You ready?
Hired for disaster, baby!
That's right.
This can't be right.
Go back even further
You're too fast!
You need to go slow!
Who is this person?
Are, are we in the right...
What the hell do you think you're
You don't belong out here!
I think we went back too far
You let him drive.
Let me drive, (Santa? lol)
You're not strong enough!
You'll kill yourself.
DAMN!
They'll never let you fly.
Uh, am I the only one that's confused here?
You're an AC(?) pilot.
But you're too emotional.
You do know why they call you cockpit
don't you?
Huge rumble,
throughout the cosmos shook the moon.
and the sun, the stars in the sky.
And so, they (well all) away.
Through up throughout the night
Did you see that?
Star ?bright?
Get your butts inside. It's time to eat.
Prepare for take off, Lieutenant Trouble.
Woohoo!
Charming memory.
Hang on.
I think I got it.
Goose likes you.
She doesn't typically take to people.
Early start to your morning?
Ahh, late night actually.
I can't sleep when there's work to do.
Sound familiar?
Flying airplanes never feels like work.
Wonderful view, isn't it?
I prefer the view from up there.
You'll get there soon enough, ace.
Wait, wait, wait. That's her.
Get it back.
Stand by.
Sound familiar?
Wonderful view, isn't it?
I prefer the view from up there.
You'll get there soon enough, ace.
What's that on her shirt?
I couldn't make it.
Wonderful view, isn't it?
I prefer the view from up there.
You'll get there soon enough, ace.
Focus
Excuse me?
Look down
Focus!
Pegasus.
Doctor Wendy Lawson, that's her!
Do you hear that?
Do we have a location?
Got it.
Now track Lawson until we
find the energy signature.
Interesting.
Unh.
Hold on.
Go back right before this.
Go back.
There's no beep flashing.
That's it
Now let's see where you're headed.
That's it. Look at the coordinates.
Focus!
Open please.
That's it. That's it.
Almost there.
?Almost there? Don't fight.
Focus!
Get her back. Get her back, now!
Do we have
any information we can act on?
Just that Lawson was somewhere
on planet C-53
We're on our way.
Then dig, dig, dig, dig deeper.
Lawson is our link
to that Lightspeed engine!
Everything we're after.
Oh!
I'm gettin' something.
Try that again.
Not yet!
What did you do to me?
Now, we're just after a little information.
What did you put in my head?
Nothing that wasn't already there.
But those aren't my memories.
Shiiiit, it's like a bad trip in there
I'm not surprise you
can't keep it straight.
They really did a number on you.
Enough of your mind games.
What do you want?
We're looking for the location of a Dr. Lawson
and her Lightspeed engine.
I don't know any Dr. Lawson.
Then why is she in your head?
?Figured would? happen to know how
these things come off, would you?
No?
Fine.
BAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAAA
Hey!
You do know why they call you...
Leaving so soon?
We're just getting to know each other!
Vers to Starforce Command
Do you read me?
Hello?
Do you copy?
Hi. I'm Vers. Kree Starforce.
Is this C-53?
Do you understand me?
Is my universal translator working?
Yup. I understand you.
Oh, good.
Are you in charge of
security for this district?
Sort of. No.
The movie theater has it's own guy.
Where can I find communication equipment?
Thank you.
Track the pod, find the girl.
She knows more than she knows.
Hey!
This one's taken.
Come on.
Vers.
Verify. CTC-39.
GRXC-16 hundred.
I'm fine. Thank you for asking.
Is everyone okay? What happened?
Skrull ambush.
I thought we lost you.
Did you find Soh-Larr?
It wasn't Soh-Larr.
Talos simmed him. Even knew his code.
That's impossible.
That code was buried in his unconscious.
Skrulls messed with my mind.
The machine that they used.
I...I think it's how they
extracted Soh-Larr's code.
Vers, where are you?
I'm on planet C-53.
The Skrulls are looking
for someone named Lawson.
Who?
She's...
who I...see.
She's what?
Vers.
Vers. What?
She's a scientist.
They think that she's cracked
the code on Lightspeed tech.
I have to get to her before they do
or else they'll be able
to invade new galaxies.
No.
You've been caught once already.
How far is C-53?
Closest jump point is 22 hours.
Vers, hold your position
until we get there.
Keep your comms online so we can contact...
No! What if they got ahold of her before...
I'm sorry.
The long distance company (?)
(?)...for the number you have dialed.
Vers.
Please (?) your call
with the (?) code
Vers!
If the Skrulls got to
her, she's compromised.
She's stronger than you think.
Ever been to C-53?
Once.
It's a real shithole.
Did you call us here?
Beacon activated.
'Scuse me, miss.
You know anything about a lady
blowing a hole through the roof
of that Blockbuster over there?
Witness says,
"She was dressed for laser tag."
Oh..
Yeah, I think she went that way.
Uhh...
I'd like to ask you a few questions.
Maybe, give me the 4-1-1
on the late night dropbox.
Could I see some identification please?
Vers. Kree Starforce.
We don't carry our
identification on little cards.
Vers!
Star-Force
How long you plan to be in town?
Oh, I'll be out of your hair
soon as I drag down the Skrulls
that are infiltrating your planet
Skrulls?
Shapeshifters.
They could transform to any
lifeform down to the DNA.
Oh boy.
You boys don't have
any clue do you?
Whoa, whoa, whoa. Hold on.
How do we know
you're, not one of those
shapeshifters?
Congratulations, Agent Fury.
You've finally asked a relevant question.
Oh! Congratulations to you, Starforce lady!
You're under arrest.
Rook!
Rook! Let's roll!
Did you see that weapon?
I did not.
Hey!
Suspect on northbound train
in pursuit.
Trust me, true believer.
Trust me...
Ooooo hhhh......
Train's heading for a tunnel up ahead.
Let's greet them at the station.
Mr. Fury, this is Agent Coulson.
Uhm. Uh, I'm still here at the Blockbuster.
And uh...
Where'd everybody go?
I've finished collecting evidence.
Official S.H.I.E.L.D. activity.
Stay back.
Nice scuba suit.
Lighten up, honey, huh?
Got a smile for me?
All life on Earth
is carbon-based
Not this guy
Whatever he runs on
is not on the periodic table.
You're saying he's not from around here.
Yeah. How's your eye?
I'd say fine.
But it can't believe what it's seeing.
You said
this thing looked like
Coulson
Talked like him too
That woman said that there were...
...more?
The word she used was infiltration.
You believe her?
Not 'til I saw this?
What's your plan?
To find Blockbuster hero.
I got word on a motorcycle thief
that fits her description.
If she can tell us why
these lizards are here
maybe she can tell us how
to kick 'em to the kerb.
Good.
Do it alone though.
We can't trust anyone.
Not even our own men.
Yes, sir.
Wow!
They are ugly bastards, aren't they?
Yeah, well. He's no Brad Pitt, sir.
Safe journey to the beyond, my friend.
I will
finish what we started.
I wouldn't get too close there, boss.
No one in or out.
♪ I'm only happy when it rains ♪
♪ I'm only happy when it's complicated ♪
♪ And though I know you can't appreciate it ♪
♪ I'm only happy when it rains ♪
♪ You know I love it when the news is bad ♪
♪ Why it feels so good to feel so sad? ♪
♪ I'm only happy when it rains ♪
♪ Pour your misery down ♪
♪ Pour your misery down on me ♪
♪ I'm only happy when it rains ♪
♪ I feel good when things are goin' wrong ♪
♪ I only listen to the sad, sad songs  ♪
♪ I'm only happy when it rains ♪
What can I get 'cha?
Where was this photograph taken?
I dunno, an airport?
Where's Pegasus?
That's classified.
Not unlike the file I started on you.
But I see you changes(?)
up a bit since then.
Grunge is a good look for you.
Did you have a rough day, Agent Fury?
Is cool.
You know.
Had a space invasion.
Big car chase.
Got to watch in an alien autopsy.
Typical 9 to 5.
So you saw one.
I was never one to believe in aliens.
But I can't unsee that.
This is getting a little awkward
but, I gotta ask.
You think I'm one of those green things.
Can't be too careful.
You are looking at
100% red-blooded Earth man.
I'm afraid I'm gonna need proof.
Are we talking cheek swab or urine sample?
No. The DNA will match.
Want my AOL password?
Skrulls can only sim recent
memories for host bodies.
Oh. Ho-ho.
You wanna get personal.
-Where were you born?
-Huntsville, Alabama
Technically, I don't remember that part.
Name of your first pet.
-Mr. Snoopers
-Mr. Snoopers?
That's what I said.
Did I pass?
Not yet. First job?
Soldier. Straight outta high school.
Left the ranks a full bird colonel.
-Then?
-Spy.
Where?
It's the Cold War. We were everywhere.
Uh, Belfast, Bucharest, Belgrade, Budapest
I like the B's coz I can make it rhyme.
-Now?
-Been ridin' the desk the past
six years, tryin' to figure out where
our future enemies are comin' from.
Never occured to me,
they would be comin' from above.
Name a detail so bizarre,
a Skrull can never fabricate it.
If a toast is cut diagonally
I can't eat it.
You didn't need that, did you?
No. No, I didn't. But I enjoyed it.
Okay. Your turn.
Prove you're not a Skrull.
And how is that supposed to prove to me
you're not a Skrull?
That's a Photon Blast.
And?
A Skrull can't do that.
So, full bird Colonel turned
Spy turned S.H.I.E.L.D. agent
must have pretty high security clearance.
Where's Pegasus?
♪ A lonely mother gazing
out of her window ♪
Okay.
The Skrull's ?some? alien races
to infiltrate and take over planets
And you're Kree.
A race of noble warriors.
Heroes.
Noble warrior heroes.
So uhm, what do Skrulls
want with Dr. Lawson?
They believe that she developed
a lightspeed engine at Pegasus
Lightspeed?
Gotta admit. That's not the
craziest thing I've heard today.
Well, still early.
And you. What do you want?
To stop the Skrulls before
they become unstoppable.
And?
Look.
War's a universal language.
I know a rogue soldier when I see one.
You got a personal stake in this.
Government property.
Turn your vehicle around.
Nicholas Joseph Fury.
Agent of S.H.I.E.L.D.
Place your thumb on the pad.
One moment.
Nicholas Joseph Fury.
You've three names?
Everybody calls me Fury.
Not Nicholas. Not Joseph. Not Nick.
Just Fury.
What did your mom call you?
Fury.
What did you call her?
Fury!
What about your kids?
If I have them, they'll call me Fury.
You're cleared for access.
Thank you.
Uh, hold up.
You look like somebody's disaffected niece.
Put that on.
What is it?
It's the S.H.I.E.L.D. logo.
Does, uh, announcing
your identity on clothing
help with the covert part of your job?
Said the space soldier who ?
on a rubber suit.
Lose the flannel.
How can I help you?
We're Agents of S.H.I.E.L.D.
We're looking for a woman named Lawson.
A Doctor, Wendy Lawson.
Do you know her?
Follow me.
Hm.
You familiar with the
phrase "welcome wagon"?
No.
Well, this ain't it.
Is that a communicator?
Yeah.
State of the art two-way pager.
Who're you paging?
My mom.
Don't worry.
I didn't mention you.
Whoo Hoo Hoo!
After you!
Impressive.
Ohh, you should see what I
can do with a paper clip.
Mmmm...how are you? Hm??
Just look at you!
Aren't you the cutest little thing?
Aren't you cute?
And what's your name, huh?
What's your name?
Goose.
Cool name for a cool cat.
Fury.
Hm?
I'll be back.
Oh! Get my fingerprint out.
Just let me unravel the...
You sat there
and watched me play with tape
when all you had to do
I didn't wanna steal your thunder.
Ah! Lawson.
Lawson's plan for the Lightspeed engine.
I wonder why they terminated the project.
Uhm.
Maybe because she's...
cuckoo.
Kreeglyphs?
Huh?
Lawson is not cuckoo.
She's Kree.
Well...
She's dead.
What?
Crashed an aces aircraft
during an unauthorized test flight.
Took a pilot down with her.
That's why security here's so unfriendly.
They're covering up a
billion-dollar mistake.
Oh, and your Lightspeed engine?
It's toast.
When did this crash happen?
Six years ago. 1989.
Who was the pilot?
Uhm.
Most of this thing's redacted, but
but there is a testimony here from a
Maria Rambeau?
Last person to see them alive.
Received text:Keller
You okay?
Mm-hm
?Back in 10?
This isn't about fighting wars.
It's about ending them.
I know Lawson was Kree.
She was here on C-53 and
died on a plane crash.
Do you know anything about this?
I just discovered a mission
report sent from C-53
There's only so much I'm
cleared to tell you, Vers.
But
Lawson was an undercover Kree operative
named Mar-Vell
She was working on a unique energy core.
Experimenting with tech that apparently
could help us win the war.
Is she still here?
She's cooperating with
the investigation, Sir.
- You men, stay here.
- Yes, sir.
I wanna question her alone.
Excellent work, Nicholas.
Does it say anything about me?
- Anything about you?
No, of course not? Why would it be?
I found evidence that I had a life here.
On C-53?
Mar-Vell is who I see when I
visit the Supreme Intelligence.
I knew her.
And I knew her as Lawson.
- This looks like Skrull simulation, Vers.
- No, it's not.
- Because I remember. I was here.
- Stop. Remember your training.
Know your enemy. It could be you.
Do not let your emotions
override your judgment.
She's on sublevel 6.
I'll get off on 5. Take the stairs
in case she makes a run for it.
Do a pincer move. Like we did in Havana.
Right! Like we did in Havana.
We're nearing the jump point.
Leave your beacon on so I could find you.
We'll get to the bottom of this, Vers.
Together.
Okay.
Vers!
- Fury's colluding with the target.
- Then why did he call us in?
All I know is we take him in too.
Dead or alive.
Dead or alive?
Go! Go, go!
Was it something I said?
Umm-mmm.
Ohhh!
Now, you know.
I don't really need these to see.
But! They do, kind of, complete the look.
Don't you think?
- You called them in?
- I had to, (?).
- Coulson! You have eyes on 'em?
- They're not down here.
Let's try the den(?).
What?
Your communicator.
You obviously can't be trusted with it.
- Do you know how to fly this thing?
- Uh, we'll see.
That's a yes or no question.
Yes.
That's what I'm talkin' about.
We got a stowaway.
Meow!
Meow!!
Hang on, Goose.
Goose.
Oh. Oh, Goose.
Who's the good kitty, huh? Huh, Goose?
Yes. That's right. Who's a good kitten,
Goose? You the good kitten, that's right.
See anyone you know?
Funny story.
I worked on (?).
No memory.
That was six years ago.
So you think you're the pilot
that went down with Dr. Lawson?
I'm saying the last person to see
them alive could probably tell us.
- Maria Rambeau.
- Mmm-hmm.
So, how do we get to Louisiana?
Due east. Hang a right at Memphis.
That agent that stopped the
Skrulls from finding us.
Coulson. Good new guy.
- Guess he don't hate me yet.
- Yeah, well. Give 'em time.
I guess he had a feelin', you know.
Went with his gut against orders.
It's a really hard thing to do.
But, it's what keeps us human.
- I get in trouble for that. A lot.
- Oh, I see that about you.
Rescuing the guy who sold
you out to the Skrulls.
I'm guessing that's not standard
Kree operating procedure.
Well, I won't tell your
boss if you don't tell mine.
- Ronan.
- The accusers completed their operation
But the greater mission was a
failure, thanks to your team.
It was a trap.
To lure our operative Vers to Torfa
- and kidnap her.
- Give us the location.
- We'll take care of the terrorists threat.
- By bombing them out of the galaxy.
No. We'll handle this.
A sum of Skrulls anywhere is a threat to Kree everywhere.
Where are they?
Lost.
They are lost, for now.
- But we will find them.
- Do so.
Or we will.
Maintain the course to C-53.
♪You Gotta Be by Des'ree♪
Excuse me. I'm looking for Maria Rambeau.
Auntie Carol? Mom! It's Auntie Carol!
I knew it. Everyone said you were dead.
But we knew they were lying.
I'm not really who you think I am.
That is the craziest shit I've ever heard.
Green transforming aliens?
- There's no such thing.
- You're absolutely right, young lady.
There's no such thing.
'Coz if there were,
we would wanna keep that to ourselves.
You don't believe me?
No way! That's so cool!
Whoa ho! She could do a lot more
than just make tea with those hands.
- Like what? Show us!
- Maybe later.
I have some of your stuff. I will get it.
You wanna give her a hand with that?
Hm?
You don't remember anything?
I see...flashes.
Little moments.
But I can't tell what's real.
If I could just piece together
what happened that morning.
Maybe it will all make sense.
You woke me up.
Banging on my door at dawn. The usual.
Back then, we had to get up so early.
The Air Force there wasn't a
lot of women who fly combat, so
testing Lawson's plane was our only
shot at doing something that matter.
You wanted to race to base in your old Mustang.
And I didn't wasn't about to argue coz I knew my Camaro would dominate.
But you cheated. Took a shortcut.
- Since when is a shortcut cheating?
- Since it violates predetermined rules of engagement.
- I definitely don't remember those.
- Hmm, course you don't.
When I got to the hangar,
Lawson was...agitated.
She said, she had lives to save.
She was trying to take the ACs
up herself but you said that...
There are lives at stake
I would fly the plane.
Yeah.
Yup. Big hero moment.
The kinda moment we've
both been waiting for.
The doc was always unique.
That's why we liked her. But now you're
saying she's from another planet?
I know this must be hard for you.
Oh, this part right here?
No.
Nah. Umm-umm.
What's hard. Is losing my best friend.
In a mission so secret,
they act like it never even happened.
Hard. Is knowing you were out there
somewhere too damn stubborn to die.
And now you come up in here after six
years. With your supercharged fire hands.
And you expect me to call you...I
don't even know what...Vers?
Is that really who you are now?
I don't know.
Come look!
(sound of stomach gurgling)
This is me and you on Halloween.
I'm Amelia Earhard.
And, you're Janis Joplin.
Oh, this is you when you were little.
You didn't know (?) your parents, so
So Mom said, we became your real family.
This is us on Christmas.
I got my peanut butter slippers.
This is another picture of
you when you were little.
...you've always...Oh,
and this is right after you graduated...
This is you... Air Force... good day...
This right here is our favorite guy...
Oh, wait. I forgot.
Your jacket.
Mom doesn't let me wear it anymore
after I spilled ketchup on it.
That was all that survived the crash.
Or so we thought.
- Don't answer that.
- It's just my neighbor.
They can change into anyone.
- Hi there.
- What do you want?
- Uhm...
- Hey, Tom. This is my friend, Carol.
Oh, pleased to meet you!
Yowza! Heh heh.
Static electricity out here's no joke.
Oh, I noticed that peculiar bird
you got parked by the road. And I...
I was just wondering if you mind if I
bring the boys over for a closer look-see?
- A closer look-see.
- Yeah. - To see the bird
Parked out by the road? Hmm.
You are really working overtime
to sell this one, aren't you...
Talos?!
I'm sorry. Tom. This really isn't
a good time.
I'll come by tomorrow. Okay?
- Uhh...
- O-kay.
You know you really should
be kinder to your neighbors?
You never know when you're
gonna need to borrow some sugar.
Hang on a second! Before you just
swinging(?) those jazz hands around.
Making a mess of your friend's house.
- It's a lovely home.
- Oh my god.
What the hell?
No one's gonna hurt your girl.
Just, don't kill me.
We got a really complicated situation.
I'm about five seconds from complicating
that wall with some ugly-ass Skrull brain.
I'm sorry I simmed your boss. But now
I stand before you as my true self.
- Without deception.
- And who is that out there?
Okay! That's a fair point.
But I'm sure that you understand,
I have to take some precautions.
I saw you, "crush" twenty of my
best men with your hands bound.
I just wanna talk.
Last time we talked I ended
up hanging from my ankles.
That was before I knew who you were.
Before I knew what made you
different from the others.
I have an audio recording from Pegasus.
With your voice. From a plane crash.
Six years ago. On a device,
I believe you call, a blackbox.
They told me it was destroyed in the crash.
How'd you get it?
She don't understand. Young lady, I have
this precious girl that kinda loves me to
get into places I'm not supposed to be.
Call me young lady again and I'm gonna put my
foot in the place it's not supposed to be.
Am I supposed to guess...where that is?
Your ass.
Okay, I get it. We're all a little on edge
here. But look, I just need your help.
To decode some coordinates.
If you sit down and listen to this.
I assure you, it'll be worth your while.
Call your buddy back inside
and I'll listen.
Deal.
Oh my god. Get that thing away!
How'd it get in here?
The cat? This isn't what
you're afraid of, is it?
That's not a cat. That's a Flerken.
A Flerken! Ha ha ha ha ha!
Mom?
- Monica.
- Why can't I listen too? - Sshh!
- What's happening?
- It's loading.
Punch in the coordinates
5229 negative 4-7.
- 84768, 0 point 2.
- Copy that.
- Where are we going, Doc?
- My laboratory.
- Your laboratory? What do you mean?
- Oh no. Is that...
Wait. What is that? It's not showing up on my radar.
Go Carol. Slide!
- (?) Who the hell are they?
- Those are the bad guys. Fly faster now.
Yes, ma'am.
- What do they want?
- Me. My work.
I never should've
brought you along.
Here comes some Gs.
They're firing backwards. Hold on.
Pull up! Pull up! Pull up!
Stay with me, Lawson.
- Carol! Maria! Do you copy?
- Yeah. I copy.
- We hit ground.
- Carol, are you okay?!
- Do you copy?
- Yeah, I copy!
Doc!
Your blood...it's...
it's blue.
Yeah, well, yeah.
How's my hair?
Help me out, will ya?
I gotta destroy it before they get here.
Lawson.
Do you remember what I said about our work here?
What it's for?
To end wars?
Yeah.
But the wars are bigger than you know.
Damn it.
My name is not Lawson
My real name...is Mar-Vell.
And I come from a planet called Hala
I would say that you're deluded but...
we just got shot down by a spaceship
and your blood is blue.
Listen. I spent half my life
fighting a shameful war.
Now skedaddle before you
give my any more regrets.
Just remember the coordinates, okay?
- You gotta save them without me!
- Save who? How?
- Now, I gotta...blow this engine before
they find it. - What are you doing?
We have no interest in hurting you.
No? Coz all the shooting kinda
gave me the wrong impression!
The energy core? Where is it?
Air rescue's on the way.
We have two minutes
until you're surrounded.
Then I see no reason to
prolong this conversation.
No, wait!
You mean that energy core?
Nooo!
Commander. She's still moving.
- Permission to fire.
- Hold your fire.
There's nothing left.
The core's been destroyed.
She absorbed its power.
She's coming with us.
He lied to me.
Everything that I knew was a lie.
- Now, you understand.
- What? What do I understand now?
Yon-Rogg killed Mar-Vell. He killed her.
'Cause she found out that she was on
the wrong side of an unjust war.
No.
Your people are terrorists.
They kill innocents.
I saw the ruins on Torfan.
Ruins that the accusers
are responsible for.
My people lived as refugees on Torfan.
Homeless. Ever since we resisted Kree
rule and they destroyed our planet.
And the handful of us that are left
will be slaughtered next, unless..
you help me finish
what Mar-Vell started.
The core that she found would've
powered a Lightspeed ship capable of
carrying us to safety, a new home...
where the Kree can't reach us.
Lawson always told us that our work at
Pegasus wasn't to fight wars.
But to end them.
She wanted you to help us.
Find, the core.
- Well I already destroyed it.
- No! You destroyed the engine.
The core that powered it
is in a remote location.
If you help us decode those coordinates
we could find it
- You'll use it to destroy us.
We just want a home.
You and I...lost everything, at the
hands of the Kree. Can't you see it now?
You're not one of them.
You don't know me.
You have no idea who I am.
I don't even know who I am.
You're Carol Danvers.
You are the woman on that blackbox
risking her life, to do the right thing.
My best friend.
Who supported me as a mother...
and a pilot when no one else did.
You're smart. And funny.
And a huge pain in the ass.
And you were the most
powerful person I knew.
Way before you could shoot fire from this.
Hear me?
Do you hear me?
Come here. Give me a hug.
I know I don't deserve your trust.
But you were our only lead.
We discovered that your energy
signature matched Mar-Vell's core.
Now we know why.
If only you knew the
importance of it to me.
I just need your help decoding
the coordinates to Mar-Vell's lab.
Those weren't coordinates.
They're state vectors.
Orbital positioning and velocity.
You didn't find her lab on
Earth coz it's not on Earth.
That was the location on the
day of the crash six years ago.
If we track its course,
we'll find it in orbit right now.
It's just basic physics.
In orbit.
Was that so difficult to figure out?
I mean, you're my science guy, right?
Yon-Rogg will catch up to me soon.
We've got to get to the
core before he does.
Hm. We're going to space?
In what?
A few tweaks to your vessel should do it.
I can handle the modification.
Hm! Your science guy.
Well, I could use a co-pilot.
No! No, I can't.
I can't leave Monica.
Mommy, it's okay.
I could stay with grandma and pawpaw.
There's no way I'm going baby.
It's too dangerous.
Testing brand new aerospace tech is
dangerous. Didn't you use to do that?
Your plan is to leave the atmosphere
in a craft not designed for the journey.
You anticipate hostile encounters with a
technologically superior foreign enemy.
Correct?
That's what I'm saying. You have to go!
Monica.
You have the chance to fly the coolest
mission in the history of missions.
And you're gonna give it up to stay on the
couch and watch "Fresh Prince" with me?
- What?
I just think you should consider what kinda
example you're setting for your daughter.
- What's goin on around here?
- I know. I know. I'll explain inside.
Thanks for being here.
Your mom's lucky.
When there were handing out kids,
they gave her the toughest one.
- Lieutenant Trouble.
- You remember.
Is that mine?
No! No. You hang on to
it until I come back.
But there is something
that I need your help with.
I can't wear these Kree colors anymore.
And since you're obviously the only person
around here with any sense of style...
Hmm?
Whoa!
No.
Uh-uh.
Definitely not!
Well since we're on the same team.
How do I look?
Flash.
What took you so long?
I'm fine. Thanks for asking.
-PRY46B...
- No. No codes.
That system is fallible as we learnt.
Okay. Then let's do this.
Who do I see when I commune
with the Supreme Intelligence?
The person you most admire and
respect, I guess.
But you would never tell me who.
And what is your earliest memory of Hala?
The transfusion.
Blue blood running through my veins.
Whose blood?
It's my blood
that's coursing through her veins.
- What've you done with her?
- You're too late.
Cheer up, (?).
Ronan, Skrulls have infiltrated C-53.
Come at once.
For the good of all Kree, Commander.
The infestation will be eradicated.
Rising 5-0-0 and climbing.
You know you really shouldn't
have that thing on your lap.
Our little alliance with you
is tenuous at best.
As long as he continues to freak you out.
Like that. Well...
I'm gonna keep givin' him all the
love and hugs that he needs, right?
Can I ask you something?
You just turn into anything you want?
Oh, well, I have to see it first.
Can you all do it?
Physiologically, yeah. But, uh,
it takes practice and uhm, dare I say...
Talent, to...do wa...
Can you turn into a cat?
What's a cat?
What about a filing cabinet?
Why would I...turn into a filing cabinet?
Venus Fly Trap? I'll give you fifty bucks
right now if you turn into a Venus Fly Trap.
*audibly annoyed sigh*
Switching engines from scram
jet to fusion. Buckle up, folks.
Hey. Is this normal?
Like, space turbulence?
Pretty much.
Locking in our coordinate grid.
Where is it?
It's here. It's gotta be here.
(?) ...nothing but behind.
Decloaking activated.
Is that it? The core?
In her notes, she called it,
the "Tesseract".
Whoa.
What was Lawson doing
with all these kid stuff?
Ehem.
We're not alone.
Talos.
He didn't come here for the Tessaract.
It's okay.
We didn't know what to do. Mar-Vell warned
us not to send a signal for any reason.
Or the Kree would find us.
You did the right thing.
It's okay. It's okay. She's alright. She's a friend.
I am not gonna hurt you.
She led me to you.
I'm so sorry.
- I didn't know.
- Carol, this is war.
My hands are filthy from it too.
But we're here now.
You found my family.
This is just the beginning. There are
thousands of us separated from each other.
Scattered...throughout the universe.
If I played the same pinball machine for
six years, I'd have some high scores too.
Fraternizing with the enemy.
Uh-uh
- What did you to your uniform?
- He got in her head.
- Just like we thought.
- The Supreme Intelligence will set her straight.
You can see they're not soldiers.
Let 'em go. You can have me.
And the core?
- You lied to me.
- I made you the best version of yourself.
What's given...can be taken away.
♪ Nirvana - Come As You Are ♪
There she is. Seems like your time
on C-53 jogged the old memory.
This jacket is killer, by the way.
Oh, the music. It's a nice touch.
- Let. me. out.
- No can do.
If you hurt them,
I will burn you to the ground.
With what exactly?
Your power comes from us.
You didn't give me these powers.
The blast did.
And yet you've never had the
strength to control them on your own.
Species. Flerken.
Threat. High.
It's a cat. Not Hannibal Lecter.
Species. Human Male.
Threat. Low to None.
That thing's clearly busted.
Load the Flerken onto the helio.
Jet the others into space.
You did good, ace.
Thanks to you, those insidious shapeshifters
will threaten our borders no more.
I used to believe your lies. But the
Skrulls are just fighting for a home.
You're talking about destroying them
because they won't submit to your rule.
- And neither will I.
- We found you.
- We embraced you as our own.
- You stole me.
From my home. My family. My friends.
It's cute how hard you try.
Remember
Without us...
Give it up kiddo!
Stay down!
You're weak.
You're going too fast.
Helpless.
We saved you.
Without us, you're only human.
You're right. I'm only human.
On Hala, you are reborn. Vers.
My name is Carol.
She's trying to break out.
I've been fighting with one
arm tied behind my back.
But what happens when...
I'm finally set free.
You know you're glowing, right?
I'll explain later.
Take the Tessaract.
Leave the lunchbox.
- Me?
- Yes.
I'm not touchin' that thing!
You want me to get you an oven mitt?
Oof!
Take the Skrulls in the Quad Jet and go.
Take the...Flerken with you.
- What about you?
- I'll buy you some time!
I'm...picking you up now.
I'm trusting you not to eat me.
O hey guys!
Arm wrestle for the Tesseract?
I used to find you amusing.
Let's put an end to this!
Mew...
- Uhm-kay(?).
- Good kitty.
♪ No Doubt - Just a girl ♪
♪ Take this pink ribbon off my eyes ♪
♪ I'm exposed
And it's no big surprise ♪
♪ Don't you think I know
Exactly where I stand ♪
♪  This world is forcing me
To hold your hand ♪
♪ 'Cause I'm just a girl, little ol' me ♪
♪ Well don't let me out of your sight ♪
♪ Oh, I'm just a girl ♪
You knew all along.
♪ All pretty and petite ♪
Does that mean (?) now?
No, I just never liked you.
Incoming!
Hey! In a hurry?
Don't make me do this.
Okay.
Unh! Come on! Do your thing!
Come on.
Come o-onn.
Damn it, Goose. Pick a side.
Take them to the hangar, too.
We'll blast them all into space.
(?)
Just like Havana.
Do you have the thing?
The Flerken kitty ate it.
Come on. Move. Move.
Follow my lead.
Cover her eyes.
Board the machine.
Let's go, let's go.
Nice diversion.
I could have swore I put it in there.
- Minn-Erva, take 'em down on a dropship.
- On it.
You alright, friend?
Never...
better.
We got a bogey. Comin' in hot.
- Ha ha ha!
- Yes! -Boom!
Whooo!
What the hell was that?
Deploy ballistic warheads.
That's impossible.
C-53 doesn't have the defense system
advanced enough to destroy our warheads.
That's not their defense system, Ronan.
Take her down.
Return to the jump point.
We'll be back for the weapon.
The core?
The woman.
I'm so proud of you.
You've come a long way since I
found you that day by the lake.
But can you keep your emotions in
check long enough to take me on?
Or will they get the
better of you as always?
I always told you.
You'll be ready the day you
can knock me down as yourself.
This is that moment. THIS!
Is that moment, Vers.
Turn off the lightshow and prove,
prove to me you can beat me a...
I have nothing to prove to you.
Destination. Hala.
I can't go back empty-handed.
You won't be empty-handed.
I'm sending you with a message.
Tell the Supreme Intelligence
that I'm coming to end it.
The war. The lies.
All of it.
You can't do this.
That was a close call, huh, Goosey? Huh?
Meow
Are the bad guys still
in there somewhere?
Owww!
MOTHER FLERKEN!
- You okay?
- Yeah. 'Tis just a scratch.
No.
I can't believe you got into the raddest god fight ever and you...
I'd say you arrived, just in time.
Some nifty flying you did out there.
S.H.I.E.L.D.
could always use a pilot like you.
I'll consider it. As long as you
don't call my flyin' "nifty" again.
- How's your eye?
- Mmm. It doesn't hurt this second(?).
Just so I'm clear.
You were Soh-Larr...AND
the S.H.I.E.L.D. agent?
Talos, tagged my boss up. Stole his identity.
I borrowed his likeness. I'm not a thief.
- It's a little like stealing.
- Whose side are you on?
You good to go here 'til you recover, but...
You and your family gonna need a new look.
I could go back to being your boss.
- Uh, please don't.
- Come on.
I loved sporting his beautiful blue eyes.
No way! You guys have the best eyes.
Don't ever change your eyes.
I'll help you find a home.
Finish what Mar-Vell started.
They can stay here with us.
Can't they, Mom?
They won't be safe here, baby.
Auntie Carol is right.
They need their own home.
I'll be back before you know it.
Maybe, I could fly up and meet you halfway?
Well, only if you learn to
glow like your Auntie Carol.
Or, maybe I'll build a spaceship.
You don't know!
He doesn't.
Keep the Tesseract on Earth. Hidden.
You sure that's what Mar-Vell would want?
- Mar-VELL
- That's what I said.
It's two words. MAR-VELL.
MAR-VELL. Marvel sounds a lot better.
You know, like the Marvelettes?
♪ Wait, oh yes, wait a
minute, Mr. Postman ♪
♪ Wai-ai-ai-aiiit Mr. Postman ♪
Not ringin' any bells?
Keep singing.
Maybe it will come back to me.
I upgraded it.
Range should be...couple
galaxies, at least.
What? Think I'm gonna prank call you?
For emergencies only, okay?
Well, if you're ever passing back through this galaxy
be sure to give a brother a shout.
We got the ketchup stain off.
Thanks, Lieutenant Trouble.
It's hard for me to say goodbye too.
Go on.
Glad to have you back, Sir.
This came for you.
So, is it true?
That the Kree burned your eye out because
you refused to give them the Tesseract?
I will neither confirm nor
deny the facts of that story.
Understood.
I'm sorry to report that we still
haven't found the Tesseract.
I'm sure it'll turn up somewhere.
- I'll let you know when it does.
- Then what?
Sir?
We have no idea what other
intergalactic threats are out there.
And our one-woman security force have a prior
commitment on the other side of the universe.
S.H.I.E.L.D. alone can't protect us.
We need to find more.
- More weapons?
- More...
heroes.
You think you could
find others like her?
Well, we found her and
we weren't even looking.
Get some rest, sir.
We got a big decision to make.
Sub by darelik
♪ Hole - Celebrity Skin ♪