[♪♪♪]
PETER [NARRATING]:
Tell me there's
something better.
Yee-haw!
PETER:
Go ahead. Try.
How I Spent
My Summer Vacation...
...by Peter Benjamin Parker.
I can sum it up in one
glorious, hyphenated word.
Spider-Man.
I am the
Spectacular Spider-Man.
Only one thing missing.
It's my last night
before school starts
and I could really
use some action.
[ALARM RINGS]
[♪♪♪]
Did I tell you?
One getaway jump
to the next building
and we're a million
bucks richer.
This ain't no
million-buck haul.
Not after the Big Man
takes his cut.
Ah, shut up and jump.
[SHOUTS]
Oh, no. Not again.
SPIDER-MAN:
Yep, again.
What is this, Marko,
the third time this summer?
GRUMBLING:
Just wait till I get
my hands on you,
you skinny little creep.
[♪♪♪]
SPIDER-MAN:
Okay, so, Marko, now tell me.
The new Spider-Signal.
Too much? It's my
first night trying it out.
And I'm just not
sure it screams
Friendly Neighborhood
Spider-Man.
Be brutal.
I mean, as a guy with a lot
of experience
getting thrashed
by, well, me...
I really value
your opinion.
This is a live
feed?
Then I've seen
enough.
Summon the Enforcers.
Already on their way.
[♪♪♪]
♪ Livin' on the edge ♪
Fighting crime, spinning webs ♪
♪ Swinging from
The highest ledge ♪
♪ He can leap
Above our heads ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah
Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Villains on the rise
And the city's victimized ♪
♪ Looking up with no surprise
Arriving in the speed of time ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Ah, ah, ah
Ah, ah, ah ♪
♪ Spectacular
Spectacular Spider-Man ♪
♪ Spectacular ♪
♪ Spectacular
Spectacular Spider-Man ♪
[♪♪♪]
I've never been so pumped
for the first day of school.
Because today
everything changes.
MAY:
It isn't getting any easier,
Anna.
We're almost out of money.
ANNA:
But May, I'm sure
Ben left you with--
MAY:
Ben Parker was many,
many wonderful things.
But a financial wizard
he was not.
[SIGHS]
I miss him so.
Oh, but listen to me go on.
We'll manage.
And, please,
not a word of this to Peter.
I wouldn't want him
to be concerned.
[PETER COUGHS]
Hey, Aunt May.
How's the most beautiful girl
in Forest Hills
this morning?
[LAUGHING]
Oh, Peter.
Now, hurry off. You don't wanna
be late on your first day.
No, ma'am.
[♪♪♪]
[DOOR CLOSES]
[HORN HONKING]
MAN [ANGRILY]:
I blame you for this.
You told me to bring
my Magnetic Air
Transport System to OsCorp.
I know--
You arranged the meeting
with Norman Osborn.
And I had the best intention.
He studied my ideas
and rejected them.
Then announces
OsCorp Tech-Flight
four months later.
[PLEADING]
I am sorry, Adrian--
OSBORN:
Don't you dare apologize,
doctor.
OsCorp has nothing
to apologize for.
Nothing to--
Osborn, you stole my work.
That's dangerous talk,
Mr. Toomes.
Dangerous and unsupportable.
Listen, you old buzzard.
You've been at this
for decades
without one success
to your name.
If you never accomplished
anything as a young man...
Who'd believe you created
Tech-Flight as an old one?
Boys,
show Mr. Toomes out.
Good news, I don't
blame you anymore.
[♪♪♪]
PETER:
All right,
the Parkers are desperate
for cold hard cash,
but I'm not letting that
spoil this moment.
Hey, Pete.
Harry. Gwen.
How'd summer treat you?
Science camp was fun.
Yeah, well,
the world tour stunk.
My dad spent the whole
trip locked in boardrooms.
So I spent mine
locked in boredom.
I should have stayed
in town with you, Pete.
Least we could have
done nothing together.
But now we're back.
So you ready for the
torture that is M-cubed?
It'll be different now.
[♪♪♪]
♪ Whoa, whoa ♪
Really? Because you spent
half of sophomore year
stuffed in a locker.
HARRY:
Ah, Pete? Where you going?
PETER:
To face my destiny.
Peter Parker's a wall-crawler,
not a wallflower.
And my life is about to change.
Ah... Eh...
PETER:
S-S-S-Sally?
What's he--?
Ah... Is he--?
I... I think he is.
SALLY:
Are you damaged?
[RECORD SCREECHES]
BOTH: He did.
Why in the world do you think
I'd ever go out
with Midtown High's
champion geek?
Hey, Rand, Puny Parker's
hitting on your girl.
Rand, I-- I didn't know
you two were--
It's cool.
Cool?
You don't care?
Why? You wanna go
out with him?
I want to walk on
a Parker-free planet,
thank you very much.
[LAUGHTER]
Lucky you didn't try this
with my girl, Parker.
If your geek sweat got
within one mile of Liz--
Back off, Flash.
I won't be your
punching bag anymore.
Things have changed.
Whoa!
[LAUGHTER]
Mm.
You hear him threaten me, dude?
The nerd thinks
he's Spider-Man.
Mm. Pound cake.
Oh, my lunch.
Come on. The Big Man
wants a word.
Enforcers all present
and accounted for, boss.
BIG MAN:
Thank you, Hammerhead.
Gentlemen, I'll get right
to the point.
For the last four months,
a pest has plagued
our operations.
At first, I could hardly
credit the reports.
Thought the boys were
trying to stiff us.
Had to get a little rough
to make sure they was sincere.
BIG MAN:
Establishing patterns of
movement took all summer.
But last night
we had confirmation.
The Spider-Man is real.
And you want the Enforcers
to wrangle up this here spider?
BIG MAN:
No, Montana.
I want you to squash it.
[♪♪♪]
[SCHOOL BELL RINGING]
Chapter one by tomorrow,
ladies and gentlemen.
Mr. Parker, Miss Stacy.
A word.
I wonder if either of you
remember
a field trip
we took last year
to the laboratory
of Dr. Curtis Connors
at Empire State
University?
[♪♪♪]
Ah!
Trust me, that's one field
trip I'll never forget.
Me neither. Dr. Connor's
research was thrilling.
I'm glad you feel
that way.
Because he's offering
two internships
to promising
high-schoolers.
I recommended
my two star pupils.
You start this afternoon.
[♪♪♪]
PETER:
Ah! Thanks for letting me
kill time at your place, Harry.
Ah! I'm not due at the
ESU lab for another hour.
HARRY:
I'm surprised you're not
at the school paper.
Aren't you their star
photographer or something?
Not anymore.
Someone else can take pictures
of Flash prancing around.
I'll be too busy
raking in the green.
Is this part of the
same reality
where Sally Avril's
your--
A minor setback.
But at least this lab job
solves the Parker
money problems.
I mean, look around. All
this belongs to your dad
and he's a scientist.
OSBORN:
Boys, come out here.
I couldn't help overhearing.
I'm sorry,
Mr. Osborn, I--
Don't you dare apologize, son.
I never do.
So, what's this
about a lab job?
At ESU,
working with Curt Connors.
Connors, huh?
Quite an opportunity.
Don't suppose you
were considered
for the honor, Harry?
Ah, no, sir.
It's totally not
a big deal, Mr. O, but thanks.
We'll, uh, we'll get out
of your way now.
[♪♪♪]
Osborn!
[BLADES SOUND]
[GASPS]
Dad.
OSBORN:
Argh!
What--?
What do we do?
Call the cops.
Do it. Go!
[♪♪♪]
Tell the truth, Osborn.
Can your Tech-Flight do this?
OSBORN:
Ahh!
Toomes?
Not Toomes now.
I'm what you called me.
I'm the Vulture.
I called you a buzzard.
What?
You can't even
get the name right.
Ahh!
Toomes, stop.
What will any
of this accomplish?
A means to an end, Osborn.
Something you know
all about.
VULTURE:
You will announce to the world
that Adrian Toomes is the
genius behind Tech-Flight.
You will pay me all
that I am owed.
And you will publicly apologize
for stealing my invention.
I never apologize, old man.
I may be an old man,
but I'm not a patient one.
[♪♪♪]
Ahh!
[YELLS]
SPIDER-MAN:
Oh, guys. You play
hot potato hard core.
What is this?
VULTURE:
These skies are mine now!
SPIDER-MAN:
He may be right.
I really just rent.
What are you babbling about?
Put me down.
Dude, you are the bossiest
damsel in distress
I have ever rescued.
Also the ugliest,
heaviest and the first.
Who are you?
Why, I'm your friendly
neighborhood Spider-Man,
of course.
Spider-Man?
I thought you were a myth.
SPIDER-MAN:
Man, I need a new press agent.
[♪♪♪]
POLICEWOMAN:
He's not helping, Stan.
The perps he nabs
always walk--
SPIDER-MAN: Heads up!
[GASPS]
[♪♪♪]
Ahh!
[BLADES SCRAPING]
What's going on?
Explanations inside.
Now.
Look, Beaky,
I admire anyone who dresses up
as their favorite animal.
Better still, you can fly.
So I gotta ask.
You heard the one
about great power
coming with great
responsibility?
Argh!
Whoa, Beaky,
don't fly away mad.
VULTURE:
The name is Vulture!
PETER:
That's great, Harry.
I-I'm glad that your dad's safe.
Me? Well, uh--
Y-You know,
I tried to follow him on foot,
and I ran for blocks, but--
Yeah, I guess
that was pretty useless.
Uh, hey, look, I'm late,
and, uh, Gwen's giving me
the look. So goodbye.
I so was not giving
you the look.
But I am late,
right?
Always, bro.
Eddie.
Hey, Gwen.
Bro, what are you doing here?
Work here. I'm Connors'
personal lab assistant.
Not bad for a frosh, huh?
Ha, ha.
Eddie Brock's a freshman.
College freshman,
little man.
But I'm guessing you're
missing me at Midtown High.
No one to keep
Flash Thompson off your back.
Stole your shoes again,
huh?
[♪♪♪]
Peter Parker, Gwen Stacy,
I'd like you to meet
Dr. Martha Connors.
Eddie's told us great things
about you both.
Said you wore clean underwear.
Lucky I didn't say socks.
MARTHA:
Curt, stop hiding
in the office.
New interns are here.
I'll be right out.
Peter, Gwen,
this is ESU's resident genius.
My husband, Curt.
It's an honor to meet you,
Dr. Connors.
You look familiar, son.
Weren't you the boy
that was bitten--?
By the science bug.
You know it.
MARTHA:
We won't overdo
it the first day.
Eddie'll show
you around the lab,
but the real work
can start tomorrow.
So questions welcome.
Here's one:
What does this gig pay?
Pete, you're a high school
kid with zero experience.
You're not
getting paid.
[♪♪♪]
[PETER SIGHS]
Aunt May needs my help.
I don't know what I'm gonna do.
Oh, Pete, don't angst,
okay?
It'll come to you.
Well, I'm waiting.
[♪♪♪]
You gotta admit,
the girl knows her stuff.
[♪♪♪]
PETER:
Today's been one-stop shopping
for disappointment.
No money at home.
No cool at school.
I nearly pavement splat
fighting a wacko with wings.
And now Daily Bugle security
won't even let me
use the elevator.
But May and Ben Parker
didn't raise no quitters.
Any quitters.
You get the idea.
[INDISTINCT CHATTER]
Robbie, where's my layout?
Foswell, I ordered that
rewrite 12 seconds ago.
Lee, I'm not paying you
to sit on your keister.
And you.
Me?
Yeah, you.
I sent you for my bagel
and schmeer nine minutes ago.
You sent Benny,
Mr. Jameson,
and it's only been
three minutes.
Uh, actually, sir, I've got
something better than a bagel.
Oh, yeah? What's that?
A proposal. I think
I can get you pictures.
Photos of Spider-Man
in action.
I bet it would
sell newspapers--
What do you know about
selling papers? You're a kid.
Worse, you're a teenager.
Miss Brant, call security.
Get this wailing infant
out of my face,
out of my city room,
out of my town!
Hey, what the Bugle
needs is photos.
Of Spider-Man.
In action.
Now, that would sell
newspapers, huh?
PETER:
Today officially reeks.
Not one thing's gone right.
And now the
Amazing Spider-Man
is reduced to sneaking
around for his shoes.
All clear?
VULTURE:
Osborn!
Go! Go!
You won't escape me again.
SPIDER-MAN:
My thought exactly.
MAN:
Target sighted
at last known location.
Boys, let's squash us a bug.
[RADAR BEEPING]
[♪♪♪]
SPIDER-MAN:
Trick or treat.
Ahh!
I mean, you are celebrating
Halloween in September, right?
Or am I not one to talk?
[♪♪♪]
Uh! Whoa!
[GRUNTS]
MAN:
Strangest darn gig
Big Man's ever slid our way.
We're flying with
the freaks now, boys.
I got no idea
what that big bird's about,
but I am mighty glad
he's keeping our bug busy.
Target locked.
Oh, my Spider-Sense
is ting--
[GRUNTS]
Ox, Fancy Dan.
You're up.
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
[PANTING]
Look, pal, if you
needed a breath mint,
you just had to ask.
[GRUNTING]
Ah!
[YELLS]
[♪♪♪]
[GRUNTS]
Oh, that's not good.
MAN [OVER PA]:
Uh-uh.
Boys need a workout.
Now, no turning tail.
Seriously, who are you guys?
I think we lost him.
[CRASH]
Argh!
It's not that I'm running,
but there's a vulture-guy.
So if we could just postpone--
You're strong.
Point taken.
But can you
do this?
Didn't think so.
Now, I know you can
tear right through that,
but I wouldn't
recommend it.
Son, you're making
the Enforcers look bad.
I can't have that.
[♪♪♪]
You will apologize.
I won't.
Man, this is a sweet ride.
That sunroof
come standard?
Why do you defend
that thief Osborn?
Uncool. Do you know what
these Spider-suits cost?
PETER:
Never fought anyone
like this group of bozos.
Only one thing
I know for sure.
I can't let Harry lose his
dad the way I lost Uncle Ben.
Surf's up!
[WHOOPS]
[♪♪♪]
There, the car park.
Go! Go!
No!
This is all your fault.
Two birds, one stone.
Where'd that varmint
get to now?
Did you really think you
could hide from me there?
My wing.
I can't steer.
Yeah, but you're
still airborne.
How does that
work exactly?
Vultchie,
your hump's humming.
You idiot.
You've doomed us both.
Ha, ha. You so have not been
paying attention.
Yee-haw!
[♪♪♪]
[SIRENS WAILING]
[GRUNTING]
Well, three out
of four ain't bad,
especially on bizarre
bad guy night.
Now, if I can just
get my shoes.
Oh, perfect end
to a perfect day.
Aunt May,
you're awake.
Sit down, Peter.
We need to talk.
I know you're
a good boy,
and growing up
to be a fine young man.
The man of the house now.
But you're still
my responsibility.
I can't have you
out till midnight.
You're to be home
by 10:00.
That's my bedtime.
But, Aunt May--
If you're late,
you call before 10.
If you do call,
it had better be to say
you're on your way home.
That's the law
in this house, Peter.
Do we understand
each other?
Sure, Aunt May. That's fair.
Lovely. Now, how about
a slice of banana cream pie?
Okay, nothing went
as planned today.
Understatement of the year.
But I'm still Spider-Man.
And still undefeated.
And I still have this amazing
person watching out for me.
Tell me there's
something better.
Go ahead.
Try.
[♪♪♪]