What's wrong?
They're foolish.
I just need to be prepared.
Must be buried elsewhere.
elsewhere.
Like what?
I'm gonna love her
more play to help with me.
Yeah!
Science!
I'm gonna leave you here.
Enter Kamala Khan.
It's ready for... I'm gonna
leave you here with my house.
Shina!
I'm gonna leave you here with me.
Christ, I'm just in here.
Because he may have enders me back up here.
I am!
Come back!
This is my chance.
Now that kid, what's your name?
The Marvel Dude.
Tomlinsi.
Hey, you wanna go party with your vendors?
Uh, yeah.
Uh, can you fly?
No, but I can do this.
Ta-da!
I'm gonna leave you here.
Okay.
You don't remember anything.
I see, I see, I see, I see, I see.
Flashes.
Little moments.
If I could just piece together what happens
in the morning, maybe it all makes me see.
You stole me, from my home, my family, my
friend, because I've been dead in trouble.
I have for the faster, baby, just me.
Tell us if you're from intelligence
that I'm coming to end it.
The war, the lies, all of it.
You can't do this.
I'll be back before you know it.
I can fly up and meet you that way.
I only feel it on the globe like
you're not to care about me.
Incoming cold, for me, fear it.
Oh, you expecting a call?
Maybe we just send it to voicemail.
He's next fury.
My favorite one I've made of entry.
They don't stand for us,
prodigal child of the Milky Way.
I'll go with it out there.
What the hell was that?
No?
Yeah.
What's up?
What about you?
How are you doing?
What do you know about the
surge in the jump point system?
Did you all have to go?
I didn't notice anything
unusual to go in now.
How about the whole system?
We're trying to get a
handle on what happened.
The entire network was affected?
Yeah, end to end.
Thankfully, our neural
network team was able
to trace the origin
back to MD for a team.
You're in the neighborhood, right?
Yeah.
Are you checking out?
I want it.
Appreciate you.
Monica, our team looks in
more and tells us they're acquired.
Monica?
What's she doing there?
I thought that she was on Earth.
Is she okay?
Yeah.
She's not that little kid you remember.
So, don't we think that we
can finish this before dinner?
Oh, my God.
What if it's in time to get
the reading of the jump point?
Oh, I'm doing so much superpowers and cool.
Oh.
I'm fine.
I'm low.
You guys had energy steps up the network.
I gotta find this damage
and see if we can reverse it.
Well, I got that.
Communications override.
Captain Ramville, Space Wolf.
Captain.
Ramville.
What the hell are you doing?
Seems the surge has had some
residual effect on the jump point.
I'm going to get you
some readings, Fearing.
Hello?
My car.
Is that Monica?
My Carol?
Fearing?
Was that Monica?
Why?
You want to talk to her?
I don't think I'm in the best...
I don't... I don't want...
I don't want... Look.
I don't want to talk to her like this.
Not after all this time.
You know, eventually you're
going to have to talk to her.
I know.
But say the family reunion
is still on back inside.
I think I found the source of the surge.
What do you see?
It's a jump point, but
it's not closing like...
It's stuck.
Dabbers.
Jump point is still thinking energy.
Hello?
How did you go?
Um... Hi.
How's my good living room?
Hello?
What is Dabbers doing?
It's too late.
As you find us already on Tommy.
You can't stop this.
Fury, it's the Cree.
They're going after this
rolled onto our necks.
Hold on.
Do not go in swinging this
little piece and reconciliation tool.
Fury, I got this.
So I switched with someone
named Kamala Khan?
Yeah.
She seemed to be as confused as you are.
There's nothing in her
power set about teleportation.
Not about her.
I don't know what happened
to you in me for a while.
Yes, sir.
Uh... I'm not afraid of this.
I'm not really sure.
Oh, I did not break my closet door.
Okay, I've seen space.
Oh, I should have broke it, sir.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
See, I disappeared.
So maybe Captain Marvel broke it?
What?
Yes.
Your friend, Captain Marvel,
she's walking up and down our living room.
And now you come back,
well, sing in with no apologies.
Is there Captain Marvel's in her house?
It's Captain Marvel
pressuring you in any way.
Look, I understand that she's
an important figure and all that,
but you don't have to do it.
No, no, they're clearly working together.
Look at her face and her smile.
She's being super secret.
Always not just looking at her.
Mother, you're lying again?
You can tell me.
My daughter has said
she's not going to leave her.
She's having so much fun.
Look at this happening!
This is not what we agreed.
See, pram, madame.
The scroll has been scattered
to every corner of the universe.
Made refugees wherever we go.
And still, we came into these
negotiations in good faith.
I hate it.
I perhaps more than anyone understand
what you and your people have been through.
After my predecessor was destroyed,
heretics Rose up to filth Lloyd.
The civil war has polluted our skies.
My people cannot breathe.
Our son is dying.
Howler is out of time.
I hope we can rebuild
together so much so that I'm
willing to put our ancient
animosities behind us.
and give you a chance
to protect your people.
To stop running.
The scroll will take their rightful
place in the Korean Empire.
And I will aid in a relocation.
I would hate for your people to
suffocate when I strip the atmosphere.
Let's see another island!
My son's on some freaky
spaceship and then I teleported here.
I don't know if that's my new powers,
but then that freaky cat ain't a man.
I don't know if that's gonna go wrong.
It goes come all the way out of the tent.
Oh, no, no, no, no.
Please rush.
I have to get here and
how are you involved in this?
The Cree jury rigged a wormhole on a 418.
Give me like a jump one.
I don't know, but I touched it.
Why'd you do that?
Because I was glowing a mysterious.
Okay, no rule.
No, I'm touching shit.
Especially glowing mysterious shit.
Okay, I'm feeling a lot of negative
energy for me and I don't like it.
That's not the point.
The point is, is that it was siphoning
off the atmosphere and it did this.
This is me painting.
Cury!
There was like energy
that went around my hand.
Focus!
Okay, maybe if I do this.
I don't like that anymore.
I don't like it no more than that.
I've got loads of creativity.
I wanted a modified puppets.
I wanna make it point.
Y'all can't do that whole,
doesn't mean it now.
All of that!
A style like it is happening.
315 years later I've seen a pretty big job.
I mean all of that.
I'm feeling all of that.
I'm feeling it wrong a lot of times
and I'm like... Without my human being.
We're alright?
Alright.
I don't like the rock sticks on us.
We kick everything,ank everything
And call it for initiative
Yeah, we're here.
Me.
And be it again to
Where the fuck you are?
We made it.
Let's go slowly.
Are you okay?
Oh, way!
I'lliano when we watchian.
Oh, my God!
No!
Come on!
Oh, my God!
Hey!
What the?!
Are you okay?
Oh, aah!
Oh, my God!
Boy, you're gonna bring it in.
Aah!
I think I switched when I use my power.
A straw Konradic!
Aah!
I'm still there.
I'm going to have you.
Hi.
Hi again.
I'm so sorry about early early.
We're looking for Kamala Khan.
No, I'm not there again!
There's just a new
iPad I haven't seen it yet.
I wish.
But if this is all Tom's secret
information, why is it on a clear case?
Well, just swipe it, I love it.
Oh, hi.
Can you believe it?
Intel on me?
Believe me!
Hi, I'm Intel.
Oh, my God.
Hey, what does that word stand for?
Strategic aerospace biophysics
and exolinguistic response.
It's classified.
Sorry.
The heartlight powers, yes.
Okay.
Why do you have Intel on her?
Is there some sort of surveillance on us?
The famous is a strong word.
Well, man, your daughter is
the hero of that same Jersey city.
So, of course, we would
have Intel on someone like her.
And you're also
electromagnetically altered.
What does that mean?
Oh, it just means that we
both have light-based powers.
What's your?
What's your code, man?
Oh, I don't have a code, man.
Oh, we're choppin'.
No, thank you.
I'm Karen.
Captain Marvel also has light-based powers.
Probably not coincidence.
Not to mention, the two of
you came into direct contact.
with some malfunctioning jump points.
I still cannot believe
that Captain Marvel
was here and I didn't
even get to meet her.
You know, we're supposed
to be all like twinsies.
You know, we have the same name.
I would obviously then, I don't know,
we just give it the letter that I wrote
for her and we would go out for lunch.
Did you sit on, Carol?
I said that Captain Marvel
can absorb light energy.
I can see it.
And you, you can turn light into physical
matter, which I have never heard of.
But my work... I
can totally show you.
No!
Hi.
They don't seem related.
Whatever use of families are complicated.
Monica, you want to build Carolina?
Carolina, on your working theory?
Yeah.
Hi, Captain Marvel.
It is so good to see you.
Lieutenant Trouble.
You too.
It's Captain Rebel now.
Right.
Sorry.
So, what's new?
Where is my sister?
I'm thinking that our joint exposure
to these unsteady jump points
and our susceptibility to
electromagnetic energy
has temporarily
entangled our world lines.
Everything.
Entanglement, our light
powers are entangled,
so we switch places whenever
we use them at the same time.
Which would mean Kamala.
What did you get powers?
I walked through a radiation
shielding barrier of a witch hex
and now I can manipulate and see all
wavelengths of the electromagnetic spectrum.
I'm very happy for you.
Where's our doctor?
Yes, please. Where is Kamala?
Where are you?
Where were you?
Who's Kamala?
The third person we're switching with.
Light powers, teenage girl.
How are you?
What are you doing?
I'm trying to switch.
Where is the version?
It's a work.
There are several, please,
tell them how to always switch.
Hey!
Where are we going?
Here we go!
Oh!
Monica?
You've got to fly.
No, no, no.
I mean, I know.
But technically, I have to take it.
Yeah, well, you got to now.
Oh, Kamala's not going to
graduate from high school.
Come on!
Here's your car!
Ah, it's cool, it's Carol.
They are associates of Captain Malcolm.
The Annihilator is here.
Yeah, well, she was.
And then these two just sort of appeared.
What about the band?
She's meddling, I need to straighten out.
Yeah, I still can't make out for
these imilitators in today before they...
This thing does...
Much more than
just... But it works.
Yes.
Yes, but if you give me
more time, I can make it safe.
No, no, we do it now.
Before the Annihilator appears.
Yeah, what should we do about...
These two?
I can't fly.
Do you guys have a spaceship I can borrow?
Mala, don't talk to them.
The Cree came here hopeful that
we could build a covenant of peace.
You don't know.
But then you sick the Annihilator on us.
Like we've earned it.
Once again, the Skrull
have betrayed the Cree.
And for that...
Okay.
Carol, we gotta give
peace to people out of here.
I'm her, Josh.
We need to evacuate your people now.
We have no way to go.
Carol, just sit.
I need some power so that I can help now.
No!
Charles missions.
It was a ruse.
If it were, your intervention failed.
We don't need your help, any more.
I called a friend.
She can find a safe place for you.
Is that okay?
We have no choice.
Incoming.
You're right.
Thank you again.
Always.
I see that you've finally
found yourself a team.
It is unintentional.
No, I've been on some
unintentional teams myself.
I know, but here can stand tall.
Without standing alone.
Take it from me, Mom.
Hey.
Councilor Oliver will fix this.
I promise.
May I next meet you and be joyful.
Breathe.
Do you remember?
When the sun used to shine on her.
How beautiful our home was.
Before her.
Before the annihilator.
I was there.
I heard her lies.
Claiming she was there to set us free.
But when she destroyed
the supreme intelligence.
She destroyed the dream.
For 30 years I have been
fighting alongside you.
Not only have I brought you peace.
But I have found a way
to return hell out of glory.
We need more power than that band
can provide if we to reignite our son.
Then a man of energy.
But it would kill you.
If my life is the cosobia.
We will find the other end times.
There is no more time.
That is out of time.
Need a hand?
Yeah.
Hey, have me that laser.
You're micrometers.
Wow.
So you can do that because
you walk through a witching?
Yep.
When I got blipped back they
weren't sending us to space anymore.
Grounded us to investigate
earthbound anomalies.
That must have been hard.
Your mom told you that you
always dreamed of going to space.
They had a lot of proof.
You said you'd be back before I knew it.
What?
When you left.
You said you'd be back before I knew it.
I meant what I said.
I didn't know what I
was getting myself into.
explained to a little girl.
A little girl that hung on you.
Every word.
If you knew.
I was going to come back.
I just.
There was people that needed me.
You need to be a girl.
Yeah!
Hey.
I hope you don't mind.
I didn't have any other clothes.
It's totally fine.
It looks good.
I knew.
I'm.
I'm really sorry.
By the way I spoke to you.
Thank you.
I know that this
situation is an ideal, but it
is actually nice having
people on board again.
It gets pretty lonely out here.
Anytime you need company I will be there.
I will drop everything.
I will.
I will drop high school.
Don't do that.
But can't we start again?
Hi.
I'm Carol Thampers.
I'm Kamala Khan.
But when I'm fighting
crime on the streets of Jersey
City I go by Miss Marvel
and I hope that's okay.
Like copyright wise because honestly
I never thought I'd ever get to be even.
I'm just happening and
we're like touching each other.
I realize I should have asked permission.
So.
Where's the twins?
Okay.
Alright.
Here's what we're going to do.
Captain Marvel.
You need to stop calling me that.
I used to change your diapers.
Oh, that was once.
And then I was told you
proceeded to vomit everywhere.
First of all, it's my ship.
So I make the game plan.
Oh, I'm sorry.
When's the last time you've met a team?
As early as last week.
Goose doesn't count.
Please.
You tried giving gooswers.
Like over a team?
No, no, no, no.
We're not a team.
Professor Marvel.
No.
No, no, no.
She will not.
Thank you.
Now that we've got
that out of the way team.
I've been trying to tell you, I think I
know how she's making the weird jump points.
She is one of these.
It's my nanny's bangle.
It started glowing really weirdly when
Darwin opened that first jump point.
Also, it once traveled
me through space in time.
It's probably related.
What you're describing is a quantum band.
I mean, I knew there were two of these.
I just did not expect the
other one to be in space.
They're a pair?
How do you have a quantum band?
Okay.
What is a quantum band?
A myth?
Or I thought it was a myth.
It's an ancient artifact.
So this is what Darwin
found on that before.
And then her and Kamala just
happened to stumble into each other?
What are the chances?
What you seek is seeking you.
It's inscribed on the bankle.
If the Cree legends are
true, the quantum bands were
used to create every
jump point in the universe.
It's a teleportation network.
Two quantum bands working
in unison to connect the galaxy.
She would now explain our
switchy entanglement situation.
Yeah, yeah, but Darwin only has one.
She must be overloading it with the
energy from her space hammer thingy.
It's called the universal weapon.
Oh, really?
I was going to call it Cosmo Rock.
Either way, she is using it to force
unstable jump points into the gray.
We have got to get to her
before she makes another one.
She has star charts and maps
on the screen's ownership.
Okay.
To where?
To the stars.
Okay.
It's fine.
I've got one.
We will use this as a
scroll torture device.
Can we put it on our heads?
Yes.
It's fine.
You use it to access memories.
I've been using it to regain the
memories that the create took for me.
So, yeah.
But, you know, it has a lot of other uses.
It's safe.
You might want to get comfortable.
This is weird.
Wait.
Go back.
Her band of swords, her
energy and redirects it.
It's like you gave her
power to use it against you.
Come on.
What about this?
There.
Those coordinates.
Can you read that?
Yes.
The matchline and galaxy.
All right.
I'll let you tell you.
That you want to go.
You're so cute.
No, wait.
Are you asking me to come, Maria?
Oh.
The cancer is back.
So, I need you to take care of Goose.
No.
I mean, you need it once.
You'll need it again.
I'm not taking the cat.
It's not a cat.
It should have been you that day.
That stupid race to the hangar.
I never want her to be Captain Rolfo.
Captain Rolfo sits here just fine.
And it's just until Monica gets back.
She bled me.
Girl, I don't want to relive this.
I'm sorry.
Stop now.
Please, Carol.
Remember why you're out there.
I'll look for a patient around.
What are they?
What do you tell them?
Remember to come home.
Your mom?
She died honey.
No.
I'll never do that again.
I'm sorry.
It wasn't on campus.
I'd say your mom passed
away while I was flipped.
When I came back, no one was there.
Okay.
Thank you.
She seemed really cool.
I'm sorry.
She was.
She was the best.
Well, we have to make deal
with what we know right now.
Here is what we do now.
The Universal Neural
Teleportation Network is a
system of wormholes through
the space-time continuum,
AKA junk points, which allows us to
hop between different planetary systems.
Basically, it stretches and reconfigures
space without rupturing the continuum.
Like, cracking.
The more holes you
drill, the more destabilize
the shell becomes,
and then earthquake.
Bottom line, if she
keeps creating these jump
points, it's going to get
really bad, really fast.
Question is, what does she want?
Tarnax used to be occupied by the
craze, so maybe the attack was a warning.
So she could be after
another former colony?
Is there a former craze
colony in the Magellanic?
At one point, the craze
colonized 25% of the galaxy.
If all she wanted was to
destroy Tarnax, why not bring
in an armarys of bomb or
something? Why a jump point?
You're right. Jump points aren't weapons.
They're means of transportation.
Every jump point has
two sides, so if it's Tarnax's
atmosphere was siphoned
away, you had to go somewhere.
The Kala?
The Cree Civil War basically
bankrupted Hala of its natural resources.
The air is barely breathable.
They're suffering from a drought.
A drought?
So she could be after water next?
Okay. We're in the Magellanic.
Can we find that?
Oceans cover 99.63% of the planet.
That is a very specific step.
You've been there.
No?
Yeah.
She's in there really weird.
Yeah, why are you being weird?
Okay. Consensus on Aladdin.
Aladdin.
Yeah, I say we do it. Get to Aladdin
and separate Dargan from their bingle.
We have our heading.
Kamala, you are not going
on any space adventures.
Nicholas has told me how
dangerous they can be.
It's just fury.
God.
Wait, where are you guys?
Where's Abu?
I don't know.
Really?
They insisted.
And your dad is not adjusting
very well to space travel.
Hey, babe.
So I'm in this crazy space
elevator and we're going up.
Or maybe we're going down.
Are there directions in space?
Yes, there are.
But no filming.
Smile.
You've had another series.
Reports are coming in across the network.
Seems everyone's been affected.
Oh, we need to stop for
making another one and we can't
risk intergalactic bodies
while being in the meantime.
This is Khan.
I'm sorry, but your daughter
will have to stay aboard by ship.
Oh, no.
And she'll go into the bottom of this.
Yes.
You wouldn't let her go.
Mrs. Khan, uh, is not that simple.
We need Kamala.
I mean, we found Nani's other bangle
and there's just where they're beautiful.
What kind of terrifying
woman using the other
one are her people
and we have to stop her.
They're telling me there's another bangle.
And they're going to use
that bangle to hurt you.
Monica, go take care of her.
We will and we will make sure
she gets back home in one piece.
I promise.
Stay the course.
We'll figure out how to
close those jumplings.
Kamala, you listen to me.
If anything happens to you, may I
ask you John Loonie, you tell her that.
I love you, Red.
I love you more.
Wait, what did she just say?
Nobody cares more than Captain Marvel.
Nobody gets more grief for it.
Trust me, Kamala is in
good hands with Carol.
It's wrong with that cat.
It's acting very weird.
Also, Mr. Furish is looking a little pudgy.
I think you're overfeiting her.
Googles.
No!
Firefly.
Nightlight.
Captain's Marvel.
Mr.'s Marvel.
Doctor.
Doctor Bright.
Mmm.
Professor Marvel.
You know us.
We know the girls.
Spectromation.
Oh, wait.
No.
How many times do I have to tell you
guys I do not want or need a code name?
Besides, none of it matters if
we're not coordinated out here.
Wanna figure out this one?
Do you think?
I would stay activated after a switch.
Good to know.
Okay.
Everyone together on three.
Ready?
One, two, three.
Now what?
She's saying go.
I'm going in three.
Now.
One, two, three.
She gave me eyes.
Now.
You hold on.
One, two, three.
Three.
That's why you will invest in index
funds rather than in individual stocks.
Of course.
Both the Roth IRA and 401K
are important for tax purposes.
You know I know we will fool about it.
I'm for autonomy.
Hey.
It's never too late.
And it's never too early.
Like I say.
How old are you?
26.
Wow.
Say name.
What's that?
You have to find out.
Can you send us a key?
Sweet thought.
Don't touch it.
What is that?
I have a foggiest idea.
I'm going to get it.
I don't know.
Should we tell fewer?
Twenty seconds.
To their job.
Do you guys realize how
crazy this is right now?
Like I'm, I'm in a spaceship
with two computers.
Also it's too late to go
to the bathroom because
I feel like it's going
to hit really soon.
No one will believe me like my nephew.
Yes, she would never.
No.
Okay.
Here we go.
Combs?
Wow.
I've always wanted to eat you.
Testing.
Testing what you're doing.
Mom, what are you?
Come on.
We hear you baby.
Thank you.
So, real quick, before we get sucked in.
What the was that?
I should warn you that
I'm kind of famous here.
Well, did you know you're
famous everywhere, right?
This one's kind of different.
I hope the prince with the legal issue.
Okay.
Mm-hmm.
Let's go.
No matter what.
Follow my lead.
A lot of culture is
very specific, so there's
going to be a bit of a
ceremony we have to do.
Like, just stay cool.
Hi, small child.
Hello.
As if no time has passed.
So exciting that you're home.
Our Princess is home.
Princess.
Whoa.
It's a technicality.
Carol, what is happening?
Their language is song.
Most of them won't
understand you unless you sing.
Come on.
Let's go.
Aren't you like dancing?
I am dancing.
And, yes, I am.
Don't think it's the
way that I... Wrong.
Ask him if someone... They're
having a... Can you tell anyone?
What?
That you're doing with this?
So, that's what you meant
when you said legal issue.
It is a barrage of convenience.
It's more of a diplomatic act.
You know, it's like there's a power
of trouble, a major equal society.
We are friends, hmm, it's a long story,
I need to stand, maybe not, we're here.
I can't trust, I'm a pleasure to announce
to this lovely room full, two new faces.
One could be more
cheerful, but none the last
we ring the bells to
Usher in whole bright days.
And another then, one, two, three.
The marbles!
Yeah!
Well, how is that even a thing already?
I'm kidding, what's really cool?
Where's the Princess?
What is she doing? She's respecting us all.
So many feelings right now.
Oh, well, I'm a snare afraid of her.
If I don't put her feet on the ground, give
me a chance here before it gets over me.
So many different things, I don't want.
And trust that you alone
can't stop her alone.
How many chapters have
you kept a Marvel fan fiction?
Is this gonna be him?
So many.
Don't forget.
Yeah!
My Princess... Roam the star!
We need to talk.
Okay, let's talk.
Oh wait, he doesn't have the same?
Yeah, he's bilingual.
We are severely underdressed, but could
you get us something real or bad already?
Of course.
Thank you.
Dear itself, our best one of best problems.
A worst enemy plot.
Some kind of infestation by one.
Oh, it could be from a traitor from within.
Well, let's not go there yet.
This egg, you say, let's just
continue to study it, if anything.
Morning. 29 new objects.
Detective.
Oh, my gosh.
What about lady of light?
Frequency.
Pulsar.
No.
Light lady.
Absolutely.
These are too much, right?
You made us quick.
Nothing grandiose.
Your three engines
disappear, but stay close.
Frustration to you.
This will work, beyond.
Remember, if you want to
keep unintentional switching
to a minimum, entertainer
as long as you possibly can.
Monica and I will get the jump
on her, and look at the bangle.
It's time.
Why have you called?
I've come here to pardon you.
For your crimes against the Korean Empire.
Neil.
To you?
I will live with you.
Okay.
Meet your scarf.
You're too late.
Why did you get that?
Grandma!
You think that is me in the mail?
Get into the car.
Right.
Get to the ship!
We've got to see a car.
This side is a final system.
Are we doing something about these?
The space of the players offline.
We'll come in here with good news.
But don't.
That's not good news.
You guys in?
Get down here!
You can't hold a thought.
Can you hurt this woman?
No, I can lose her.
And what about the other twenty shit?
I can do this.
I can't leave now.
I can't let this happen again.
I can do this.
And you'll tell us to try.
I can't treat you.
We left Atlanta to fend for themselves.
Darham was going to get my bagel, so
I made a tough call like you did on fire.
Don't try to be like me.
I messed this whole thing up.
If we weren't entangled, if we weren't here,
then you could be Darben and I'm sorry.
No, you don't understand.
The crew had been ruled by an AI
for a millennia that led them into a war.
I thought the only way
to stop it was to destroy it.
But I just made it worse.
I'm the reason why the Civil
War started in the first place.
I'm the reason why they
couldn't breathe the air.
That's how I got the name in the eye later.
And I never wanted you
to see that version of me.
Is that why you never came back?
I thought if I fixed it,
then I could come home.
That's not how family works.
I never expected you to be
the mighty Captain Marvel.
I just wanted you.
Not what.
I'm really glad that you're here now.
And you, too.
I'm glad to be here.
I hope that goes without
saying, and I am sorry
for coming out too
strong at the beginning.
I did not give you a lot of
space to be a real person.
I have to find her.
If anybody should be anywhere.
No.
Not anywhere.
She's targeting the
people that I care about and
stealing resources from
every place I call home.
We have to more fear me.
This is an emergency.
I'll save the person who is reporting
to evacuation time in the field.
What about you?
The reason why we have that is to
evacuate 350 personnel of 15 escape homes.
We've seen 5, 10, if you see
there's no one there enough.
We'll fill her in many ones, as many people
as you can, then come up with a plan V.
Please, operations.
I hope this.
Hey.
That's it.
It's you.
Come here.
Hey.
You.
It's coming.
It's you.
Oh, no.
We don't need help.
We do.
In the end, one of our students
always hugs us from this life to the next.
What?
No!
Could everyone do the evacuation day?
Can you imagine?
What is going on, fam?
Come on up.
You're so come on up.
You're not?
You look like a suker and
you're back safely written.
You're not dead.
I'm lost contact with Earth.
We're officially out of bed and shipping.
No, no, no, no, no.
That's the plan.
That's the plan?
Much easier to transport a family of
cats than hundreds of crew members.
So we're literally ready, guys?
Come here, kitty.
Attention, saver groups.
Alright.
You're still here today.
I'll be right back.
We'll be right back.
What are you doing?
Roger, I found her.
Hey, come on.
Drop it.
it. I'll go.
You've got to lift these home, baby.
How'd it just do?
Come on.
Stop it?
There's a new time of the early days.
It's time for me.
It's time for you to decide.
I'm going to be the president of all this.
I'm going to be the president.
I found our band.
What? She owns our son.
You leave it again?
Yeah. I mean, the universe is in space.
And if the universe isn't safe,
then we two guys aren't safe.
Listen to me.
You are chosen for a greater purpose, okay?
So of course you must go now.
That I will never let you cool.
You understand that, right?
I'm not counting on you.
You could basically be done.
You're better.
I don't want to be a only child.
Not again. Not with these two.
Take his wives, take a
net manual to the bad guy.
Yes, Mr. Fury.
He's trying to give it to me.
I will take it home.
Darwin's opened
another junk plant, and
we're going to need
both bangles to close it.
And I guess you better make damn shoes.
You don't get a hands-on.
Understand?
Are you right?
Hey, man!
It's a Berry!
There she is.
We annihilate the house out.
It's over, Dark Ben.
No, I'm not yet.
I know that you would do
anything to protect Hala.
This will be the end of the Kree.
It will be the end of everything.
It took for me.
You're simply repairing your favor.
Then, give me the bat.
You're forgetting something?
What? Me?
This could have been so much easier.
I don't know. I like our eyes.
Get out of here!
No!
You're living up to your name again.
I didn't want this.
That seems to fully shoot.
It doesn't have to end like this, Dark Ben.
Please, just give us the bangle.
We're what?
Hollis don't die because of you.
Why shouldn't you repass?
Maybe she should.
The reaction in your son's core has slowed.
And he's an incredible amount
of energy to jump-starting.
And that's what you have, Carol.
You can use your powers to save Hala.
I've never done anything like that before.
In the last couple of days, I have done
a lot of things I've never done before.
But you got this.
For Hala.
Try to knock you much
faster than you can make.
I won't survive this, Dark Ben.
Listen to me.
I need to show you.
So what are we looking at?
We're self-propagating singularity with
negative mass and non-Newtonian topology.
She tore a hole in space-time.
That is a different
reality, leading into ours.
You can even fix that in theory.
You and Carol can reproduce the same
amount of energy that was used to open it.
I will absorb it and then release
it, but from inside the tear.
But what about the switching?
Our powers aren't entangled anymore.
Oh.
Well, that's a good thing, I guess.
But wait, you want us to
blast you with the same amount
of power that punched a hole
in the fabric of space-time?
If we want to UN-punch it.
Yeah.
I'm gonna need this.
How are you feeling, Ms. Marvel?
These bagels are all but
there's space and time to find me.
I was born for this.
It has to be now.
Ms. Marvel.
It's closing, Monica.
Monica, you gotta get out of her.
Come on, you saved the world.
Why are you praying?
We lost Monica.
She couldn't stop on the other side.
And Carol.
We went to some full promise.
How would things?
This is kitchen, but
there are these hot
sauce bar tips and
then there's this veneet.
This is our looking tray, which I will say.
It's a very good quality though.
Oh, you can give it.
Oh, no, no, no.
Oh, yeah, yeah.
It works for me.
The vastness of it just gives you
a whole new perspective on life.
Yeah, it does, doesn't it?
And it was surprisingly cool.
This place is amazing.
Yeah, it is.
Hey, did you stop flying that thing?
You want to check it out?
Thank you.
Hey, wait, wait, wait, wait.
Come here, come here, come here.
Oh, I'm so happy that
you won't save the door.
Ahmed, it's gonna be a lovely
house to raise a family in, you know?
Ahmed.
This is so cool.
All right, let's see, it's all you.
What's the last thing?
I actually don't know the key.
I'm just looking after it.
She doesn't want to get against back.
Yeah.
Just until Monica gets back.
I really miss her.
We're good together.
She got me thinking.
Pizza delivery.
Can I help you?
Kate Bishop.
Did you think you were the
only kid superhero in the world?
23.
Oh, I know.
I've been running up on you.
Where did you fit that?
I found out of my couch.
Okay.
You just become part of
a much larger universe.
Which, at the moment, is just me, mostly?
I do have your lips out there.
Did you know Ahmed had a daughter?
What do you want?
I'm putting together a taking.
I know when you want it.
Please.
Mom, I've missed you so much.
I'm so sorry.
I'm not.
I'm not a mysterious visitor.
She's single disoriented.
Where are we?
What happened?
We were hoping you could tell us.
All we know is that binary found.
My theory?
You somehow crossed through.
You were like terror in space time.
You are now in reality
parallel to your own.
Which is, of course, impossible.
You think that we have
a confusion happening?
Confusion is but the first step
on the journey to knowledge.
I'll take it for you.
Charles asked for an update.
I'll combine and check out you later.